The Year of the Red Horse has finally come.
لقد حان أخيرًا عام الحصان الأحمر.
Since they established their plan on this land,
منذ أن وضعوا خطتهم على هذه الأرض،
it has already been 11 long years.
لقد مرت بالفعل 11 سنة طويلة.
They did not just found a school.
لم يجدوا مجرد مدرسة.
They established their mindset and spirit.
لقد أسسوا عقليتهم وروحهم.
However, they encountered a crisis that could harm the backbone of it.
لكنهم واجهوا أزمة قد تضر بعمودها الفقري.
Some transfer students came and declared a war of jokes.
جاء بعض الطلاب المنقولين وأعلنوا حرب النكات.
Could the members...
هل يمكن للأعضاء...
overcome the crisis with their initial mindset?
التغلب على الأزمة بعقليتهم الأولية؟
(The Joke Battle)
(معركة النكتة)
Make extraordinary jokes...
اصنع نكتة غير عادية...
and be on top of Brother School.
وتكون على رأس مدرسة الأخ.
Welcome to the Joke Battle.
مرحبا بكم في معركة نكتة.
(Welcome to the Joke Battle.)
(مرحبًا بكم في معركة النكتة.)
Hello. I'm your host today.
مرحبًا. أنا مضيفك اليوم.
I'm Shin Dong, the MC from the broadcasting club.
أنا شين دونغ، المقدم من نادي البث.
Shin Dong!
شين دونغ!
(Cheering)
(هتاف)
Looking at you from here,
أنظر إليك من هنا،
you look brave and strong.
تبدو شجاعًا وقويًا.
They say that the greatest weapon the human race has is laughter.
يقولون أن أعظم سلاح يمتلكه الجنس البشري هو الضحك.
We invited joke masters who make people laugh...
قمنا بدعوة خبراء النكتة الذين يجعلون الناس يضحكون...
whenever they open their mouths.
كلما فتحوا أفواههم.
Joke masters!
سادة نكتة!
First, I'll introduce the viewers to each team.
أولاً، سأقدم للمشاهدين كل فريق.
Here's the first team.
وهنا الفريق الأول.
Shin Bong Sun and Seo Jang Hoon.
شين بونج سون وسيو جانغ هون.
(The first team: Seo Jang Hoon, Shin Bong Sun)
(الفريق الأول: سيو جانج هون، شين بونج سون)
- Bong and Jang. - Bong Sun is here.
- بونج وجانج. - بونج صن هنا.
What's the name of your team?
ما اسم فريقك؟
- Our team name is...
- اسم فريقنا هو... - اسم فريقنا هو...
- Jang Hoon suggested the idea. - That's right.
- اقترح جانغ هون الفكرة. - هذا صحيح.
Named after Bong Sun...
سميت على اسم بونغ سون...
It's Sun Bong Jang.
إنه صن بونج جانج.
- Sun Bong Jang?
- صن بونج جانج؟ - صن بونج جانج؟
- Yes.
- نعم. - نعم.
It doesn't match our today's theme.
إنه لا يتناسب مع موضوعنا اليوم
It's not very funny.
هذا ليس مضحكا جدا.
My gosh. Come on. If you say something like that,
يا إلهي. تعال. إذا قلت شيئا من هذا القبيل،
- we feel pressured. - Is that so?
- نشعر بالضغط. - هل هذا صحيح؟
- Try to be open-minded. - It wasn't supposed to be funny.
- حاول أن تكون متفتح الذهن. - لم يكن من المفترض أن يكون مضحكا.
- That's right. - How funny...
- هذا صحيح. -كم هو مضحك...
- should a team name be? - Exactly.
- هل يجب أن يكون اسم الفريق؟ - بالضبط.
Pardon?
عفو؟
- We'll go with Sun Bong Jang. - All right.
- سنذهب مع صن بونج جانج. - حسنًا.
Forget about the Joke Battle.
ننسى معركة نكتة.
- Right. - You can never change his mind.
- يمين. - لا يمكنك تغيير رأيه أبداً.
- It's Sun Bong Jang. - Just let us go with the name.
- إنه صن بونج جانج. - فقط دعونا نذهب مع الاسم.
- Sun Bong Jang? - But...
- صن بونج جانج؟ - لكن...
Sun Bong Jang, it is. Their team name is Sun Bong Jang.
سون بونج جانج، إنه كذلك. اسم فريقهم هو Sun Bong Jang.
Moving on, the members of the next team are...
ننتقل الآن، أعضاء الفريق التالي هم...
Kim Hee Chul and Lee Jae Youl.
كيم هي تشول و لي جاي يول.
(The second team: Kim Hee Chul, Lee Jae Youl)
(الفريق الثاني: كيم هي تشول، لي جاي يول)
Their team name must be funny.
يجب أن يكون اسم فريقهم مضحكا.
Since both of us are the youngest in our group,
وبما أن كلا منا هو الأصغر في مجموعتنا،
our team name is Juniors with Rude Words.
اسم فريقنا هو Juniors with Rude Words.
- Juniors with Rude Words.
- الصغار مع الكلمات الوقحة. - الصغار مع الكلمات الوقحة.
- It's hard to pronounce.
- الصغار مع الكلمات الوقحة. - من الصعب النطق.
- That's even worse than ours. - That's not funny either.
- وهذا أسوأ منا. - وهذا ليس مضحكا أيضا.
That's too long for a team name.
هذا طويل جدًا بالنسبة لاسم الفريق.
- It was intentional. - Make it Rude Juniors.
- لقد كان متعمدا. - اجعلها وقحة للصغار.
Juniors with Rude Words.
جونيورز مع الكلمات الوقحة.
- Shorten it to Rude Juniors? - Rude Juniors.
- اختصرها إلى Rude Juniors؟ - فظ جونيورز.
- Rude Juniors sounds good. - Team Rude Juniors.
- "رود جونيورز" يبدو جيدًا. - فريق رود جونيورز .
Rude Juniors, it is.
فظ جونيورز، هو عليه.
Good. Rude Juniors.
جيد. جونيورز فظ.
Why would you name your teams Sun Bong Jang and Rude Juniors?
لماذا تسمي فريقك سون بونج جانج ورود جونيورز؟
What is that?
ما هذا؟
- You should make it catchy. - Exactly.
- يجب أن تجعلها جذابة. - بالضبط.
Let us tell you our team name. One, two, three.
دعنا نخبرك باسم فريقنا. واحد اثنين ثلاثة.
- Hey!
- يا! - يا!
- What's that? - That's funny.
- ما هذا؟ - هذا مضحك.
- You see... - Before...
- ترى... - قبل...
- Before the shoot... - Isn't Sun Bong Jang the best?
- قبل التصوير... - أليس سون بونج جانج هو الأفضل؟
- Bong Sun has something to say. - Sun Bong Jang was very funny.
- بونج صن لديه ما يقوله. - كان سون بونج جانج مضحكًا جدًا.
It's funny that they named their team "Hey."
من المضحك أنهم أطلقوا على فريقهم اسم "Hey".
But before we started the shoot,
لكن قبل أن نبدأ التصوير،
- we talked about the teams. - Yes.
- تحدثنا عن الفرق. - نعم.
I told Sang Gook that he'd be paired up with Ho Dong.
أخبرت سانغ جوك أنه سيتم إقرانه مع هو دونغ.
He said, "Gosh. That'll be uncomfortable."
قال: "يا إلهي. هذا سيكون غير مريح."
Unlike what he said, he shouted his team name so cheerfully. "Hey!"
وعلى عكس ما قاله، صرخ باسم فريقه بمرح شديد. "يا!"
I mean, I was sitting here quietly.
أعني أنني كنت أجلس هنا بهدوء.
Then he said we should name our team "Hey."
ثم قال أننا يجب أن نسمي فريقنا "مرحبًا".
I said, "Hey!" I just did as he told me to.
قلت: "مهلا!" لقد فعلت فقط كما قال لي.
- He named the team as he wanted. - I can't...
- سمى الفريق كما يريد. - لا أستطبع...
switch seats before we begin, can I?
تبديل المقاعد قبل أن نبدأ، هل يمكنني؟
- Why? Are you uncomfortable? - What?
- لماذا؟ هل أنت غير مريح؟ - ماذا؟
Asking if I'm uncomfortable makes me uncomfortable. You're right here.
السؤال عما إذا كنت غير مرتاح يجعلني غير مرتاح. أنت هنا.
We're friends, aren't we?
نحن أصدقاء، أليس كذلك؟
Don't talk casually to me. Talk casually to me.
لا تتحدث معي بشكل عرضي. التحدث عرضا معي.
- What does he want? - What does that mean?
- ماذا يريد؟ - ماذا يعني ذلك؟
- Do you want him to talk casually? - That was so scary.
- هل تريده أن يتحدث عرضا؟ - كان ذلك مخيفا جدا.
- That was really scary. - What does he want him to do?
- كان ذلك مخيفًا حقًا. - ماذا يريد منه أن يفعل؟
- "Don't talk casually to me." - What does he...
- "لا تتحدث معي بشكل عرضي." - ماذا هو...
- We're friends, aren't we? - want him to do?
- نحن أصدقاء، أليس كذلك؟ - تريد منه أن يفعل؟
You should either let me leave or switch partners.
يجب عليك إما السماح لي بالمغادرة أو تبديل الشركاء.
I feel so uncomfortable.
أشعر بعدم الارتياح.
- Gosh, seriously. - Stay there.
- يا إلهي، بجدية. - ابق هناك.
- Next up are Yeong Cheol and Beom! - He's not happy with his partner.
- التالي هم يونج تشول وبيوم! - إنه غير سعيد مع شريكه.
(The fourth team: Kim Yeong Cheol, Kwak Beom)
(الفريق الرابع: كيم يونج تشيول، كواك بيوم)
Our team name is Yeong Forty.
اسم فريقنا هو Yeong Forty.
Yeong Forty.
يونغ الأربعين.
- Yeong Forty. - All right.
- يونغ أربعين. - حسنًا.
- That is... - So far...
- هذا... - حتى الآن...
Hey, make it Yeongdeungpo. That's better.
مهلا، اجعله يونجديونجبو. هذا أفضل.
- Why Yeongdeungpo? - That's better than Yeong Forty.
- لماذا يونجديونجبو؟ - هذا أفضل من يونغ أربعين.
- You brat! - Then we're Yeongdeungpo.
- أنت شقي! - ثم نحن Yeongdeungpo.
- Yeongdeungpo is funnier. - Right. Yeongdeungpo.
- Yeongdeungpo أكثر تسلية. - يمين. يونجديونجبو.
- Why Yeongdeungpo? - We're Yeongdeungpo.
- لماذا يونجديونجبو؟ - نحن Yeongdeungpo.
- Thank you. Yeongdeungpo is better. - You're welcome.
- شكرًا لك. يونجديونجبو أفضل. - على الرحب والسعة.
Let us tell you our team name. "Head" from "head voice."
دعنا نخبرك باسم فريقنا. "الرأس" من "صوت الرأس".
- "Geun" from "Soo Geun." - We are...
- "جيون" من "سو جيون". - نحن...
- Head Geun.
- رئيس جيون. - رئيس جيون.
- That's a good one. - Nice.
- هذا فكرة جيدة. - لطيف - جيد.
- That sounds nice. - Head Geun.
- هذا يبدو لطيفا. - رئيس جيون.
Our team name is the second place so far.
اسم فريقنا هو المركز الثاني حتى الآن.
- I really like their team name. - I wish it were the best one.
- أنا حقا أحب اسم فريقهم. - أتمنى أن يكون الأفضل .
- "Hey" is not a bad one though. - Shouldn't we change our team name?
- "مرحبًا" ليست كلمة سيئة بالرغم من ذلك. - ألا يجب علينا تغيير اسم فريقنا؟
Hey! Sun Bong Jang must be hopeless.
يا! يجب أن يكون سون بونج جانج ميؤوسًا منه.
"Min" from "Seon Min..."
"مين" من "سيون مين..."
- and "Min" from "Sang Min." - That's right.
- و"مين" من "سانغ مين". - هذا صحيح.
"Min" from "Seon Min" and "Min" from "Sang Min."
"مين" من "سيون مين" و "مين" من "سانغ مين".
- We're Mini Mini.
- نحن ميني ميني. - نحن ميني ميني.
(Nervous)
(متوتر)
Last but not least, Seon Min and Sang Min!
وأخيرًا وليس آخرًا، سيون مين وسانغ مين!
- All right! - Oh, Seon Min and Sang Min.
- حسنًا! - أوه، سيون مين وسانغ مين.
Let us tell you our team name. "Min" from "Seon Min."
دعنا نخبرك باسم فريقنا. "مين" من "سيون مين".
- It'd better not be "Min Min." - "Min" from "Sang Min."
- من الأفضل ألا يكون "مين مين". - "مين" من "سانغ مين".
- We're Mini Mini.
- نحن ميني ميني. - نحن ميني ميني.
- What did you say? - That's the worst.
- ماذا قلت؟ - وهذا هو الأسوأ.
- Sang Gook. - We're Mini Mini.
- سانغ جوك. - نحن ميني ميني.
- Rather... - You're not ready to be here.
- بالأحرى... - أنت لست مستعدة لتكون هنا.
Shut your mouth.
اصمت.
I might hit you in the back of your head.
قد أضربك في مؤخرة رأسك.
- He said to shut his mouth. - No qualifications are needed...
- قال ليغلق فمه. - لا يشترط المؤهلات...
to be here.
أن أكون هنا.
- Are you kidding me? - Hold on a second.
- هل تمزح معي؟ - انتظر ثانية.
- Why are you so mean to Seon Min? - He's lost for words.
- لماذا أنت لئيمة جدًا مع سيون مين؟ - لقد ضاع بسبب الكلمات.
- Are we doing this right? - Get off your high horse.
- هل نفعل هذا بشكل صحيح؟ - النزول من الحصان العالي الخاص بك.
- What was that? - Is this right?
- ماذا كان هذا؟ - هل هذا صحيح؟
What on earth is "Mini Mini?"
ما هو "ميني ميني" بحق السماء؟
You said it took you two weeks to come up with the idea.
قلت إن الأمر استغرق أسبوعين للتوصل إلى الفكرة.
- I got cast two weeks ago. - That's right.
- لقد حصلت على الإدلاء منذ أسبوعين. - هذا صحيح.
What are you talking about?
ما الذي تتحدث عنه؟
- Mini... - Are they actually arguing or what?
- ميني... - هل هم فعلا يتجادلون أم ماذا؟
Bong Sun and I decided...
أنا وبونج سون قررنا...
- to improvise our team names. - That's right.
- لارتجال أسماء فريقنا. - هذا صحيح.
- The others said they'd plan this. - They planned this.
- قال الآخرون أنهم سيخططون لهذا. - لقد خططوا لهذا.
- I didn't name it in advance. - I didn't.
- لم أسميها مقدما. - لم أكن.
- Let me explain. - They planned all this.
- اسمحوا لي أن أشرح. - لقد خططوا لكل هذا.
- I'll explain to you. - Okay.
- سأشرح لك. - تمام.
Seon Min emptied his schedule, refusing all other offers.
أفرغ Seon Min جدول أعماله، ورفض جميع العروض الأخرى.
- He's all in for Men on a Mission. - Don't be ridiculous.
- إنه في متناول الرجال في مهمة. - لا تكن سخيفا.
- He planned everything. - Hear me out.
- لقد خطط لكل شيء. - اسمعني.
He said he'd become a star through this show.
قال إنه سيصبح نجماً من خلال هذا العرض.
- It took two weeks to think of it? - It took him a long time.
- استغرق الأمر أسبوعين للتفكير في الأمر؟ - استغرق الأمر منه وقتا طويلا.
- Seon Min will become a star. - Oh, he's ambitious.
- سيون مين سوف تصبح نجمة. - أوه، إنه طموح.
Before we officially begin...
قبل أن نبدأ رسميًا..
When you make jokes, the seniority doesn't matter.
عندما تلقي النكات، الأقدمية لا تهم.
But I'd like to check your experience as comedians.
لكني أود التحقق من تجربتك كممثلين كوميديين.
Tell us the network you're from and the batch you are.
أخبرنا بالشبكة التي تنتمي إليها والدفعة التي تنتمي إليها.
Let's find out.
دعونا معرفة ذلك.
Bong Sun, what about you?
بونغ صن، ماذا عنك؟
- I'm from KBS. - Yes.
- أنا من قناة KBS. - نعم.
- I'm the 20th batch. - I see.
- أنا الدفعة العشرين. - أرى.
- She's the 20th batch. - Is anyone here her senior?
- إنها الدفعة العشرين. - هل هناك أحد هنا كبار لها؟
- Yes. - Oh, we have her seniors here.
- نعم. - أوه، لدينا كبار السن لها هنا.
Yeong Cheol is my senior. I'm the 18th batch.
يونغ تشول هو أكبر مني. انا الدفعة 18
- I'm the 14th batch. - He's the 14th batch.
- أنا الدفعة 14. - وهو الدفعة 14.
- I forgot that Yeong Cheol...
- لقد نسيت أن يونج تشيول... - إنه الدفعة الرابعة عشرة.
started his career as a comedian.
بدأ حياته المهنية كممثل كوميدي.
- I'm a comedian. - He joined a network as a comedian.
- أنا ممثل كوميدي. - انضم إلى شبكة كممثل كوميدي.
- Oh, my. - What about Ho Dong?
- يا بلدي. - ماذا عن هو دونغ؟
I beat Lee Man Gi.
لقد تغلبت على لي مان جي.
(I beat Lee Man Gi.)
(لقد تغلبت على لي مان جي.)
- That's a good one. - That's funny.
- هذا فكرة جيدة. - هذا مضحك.
- He came up with it in advance.
- هذا مضحك. - لقد جاء به مقدما.
- I'm Lee Man Gi's junior. - He made a good joke.
- أنا أصغر لي مان جي. - لقد ألقى نكتة جيدة.
Was I supposed to stay quiet?
هل كان من المفترض أن أبقى هادئاً؟
"Don't act up."
"لا تتصرف."
- The timing was good. - "Don't act up."
- التوقيت كان جيداً. - "لا تتصرف."
I shouldn't miss my chance to make a good joke.
لا ينبغي لي أن أضيع فرصتي لإلقاء نكتة جيدة.
What about you, Sang Gook?
ماذا عنك، سانغ جوك؟
I'm from KBS. I beat 3,800 participants...
أنا من كي بي إس. لقد تغلبت على 3800 مشارك..
- to join KBS. - He startled me.
- للإنضمام إلى قناة KBS. - لقد أذهلني.
- I'm the 22nd batch. - He spoke in dialect.
- أنا الدفعة 22. - تحدث باللهجة.
- He "beat" many others. - It wasn't easy.
- لقد "تغلب" على كثيرين آخرين. - لم يكن الأمر سهلا.
Who else joined the network in the same year as you?
من آخر انضم إلى الشبكة في نفس العام الذي انضممت إليه؟
- Amazing stars did. - There are many of them.
- فعلت النجوم مذهلة. - هناك الكثير منهم.
- Heo Kyeong Hwan, - Many popular comedians did.
- هيو كيونغ هوان، - فعل ذلك العديد من الكوميديين المشهورين.
Kim Joon Hyun, Jang Do Yeon,
كيم جون هيون، جانغ دو يون،
- Park Sung Kwang. - Park Sung Kwang,
- بارك سونج كوانج . - بارك سونج كوانج،
Park Young Jin, and Kim Won Hyo.
بارك يونغ جين وكيم وون هيو.
- They're all very popular. - Indeed. The top star batch.
- انهم جميعا تحظى بشعبية كبيرة. - بالفعل. دفعة النجم الأعلى.
And you're among them.
وأنت من بينهم.
- The top star batch. - That's why he didn't stand out.
- دفعة النجم الأعلى . - ولهذا السبب لم يبرز.
He didn't stand out?
وقال انه لم تبرز؟
Only when the others are not with him...
فقط عندما لا يكون الآخرون معه..
- Hey, you brat! - Like finding a needle in sand?
- مهلا، أنت شقي! - مثل العثور على إبرة في الرمال؟
- Only then he was visible. - Hey.
- وعندها فقط كان مرئيا. - يا.
- Look. - What?
- ينظر. - ماذا؟
- Let's forget about the seniority.
- ماذا؟ - دعونا ننسى الأقدمية.
- Batch 22 became more successful...
- الدفعة 22 أصبحت أكثر نجاحا... - دعونا ننسى الأقدمية.
than Batch 20.
من الدفعة 20.
- Batch 20 became successful too. - I didn't say you didn't.
- أصبحت الدفعة 20 ناجحة أيضًا. - أنا لم أقل أنك لم تفعل.
- I said you didn't stand out... - Who else...
- قلت أنك لم تبرز... - ومن غيرك...
- among those... - Who else is in the 20th batch?
- ومن بين هؤلاء... - من آخر في الدفعة العشرين؟
- Yoo Min Sang. - Oh, Yoo Min Sang?
- يو مين سانغ. - أوه، يو مين سانغ؟
I can't really tell you about the others.
لا أستطيع حقاً أن أخبرك عن الآخرين.
- Is there a reason? - They caused controversies.
- هل هناك سبب؟ - لقد أثاروا الجدل.
- They caused some controversies. - Oh, I see.
- لقد تسببوا في بعض الجدل. - أوه، فهمت.
Is there anyone who joined KBS...
هل هناك أحد انضم إلى قناة KBS...
I'm next.
أنا التالي.
- Go ahead. - Beom...
- تفضل. - بيوم...
- I'm from KBS and the 27th batch. - He's the 27th batch.
- أنا من KBS والدفعة 27. - وهو الدفعة السابعة والعشرون.
- Oh, you're the 27th batch. - I'm the 27th batch.
- اه، أنتم الدفعة السابعة والعشرون. - أنا الدفعة 27.
- I debuted in 2012. - There's a big gap.
- ظهرت لأول مرة في عام 2012. - هناك فجوة كبيرة.
- Out of 3,500 people, 15 got hired. - Out of 3,500 people?
- من بين 3500 شخص، تم تعيين 15 شخصًا. - من بين 3500 شخص؟
- Who else joined KBS in that year? - Many people...
- من انضم أيضًا إلى KBS في ذلك العام؟ - كثير من الناس...
- apply for it every year. - There's only one person...
- التقدم بطلب للحصول عليه كل عام. - هناك شخص واحد فقط..
- I can tell you about proudly. - Who is that?
- أستطيع أن أخبرك بكل فخر. - من ذاك؟
Lee Su Ji.
لي سو جي.
(Shout out "Queen Su Ji.")
(أصرخ "الملكة سو جي.")
- The comedy minister. - She's incredibly popular.
- وزير الكوميديا. - إنها تحظى بشعبية لا تصدق.
It's the only batch from which only one person...
إنها الدفعة الوحيدة التي منها شخص واحد فقط...
became successful while we were on "Gag Concert."
أصبح ناجحًا أثناء وجودنا في "Gag Concert".
Lee Su Ji was the only one who became successful.
كان Lee Su Ji هو الشخص الوحيد الذي حقق النجاح.
I became famous later,
واصبحت مشهورا فيما بعد
- so I've been honored to be here. - Right.
- لذلك يشرفني أن أكون هنا. - يمين.
I'm the 27th batch.
انا الدفعة 27
Who's next?
من التالي؟
- I think it's me. - It's Jae Youl.
- أعتقد أنه أنا. - إنه جاي يول.
I'm from KBS and the 32nd batch.
أنا من KBS والدفعة 32.
- He's very young. - Jae Youl... I see.
- إنه صغير جدًا. - جاي يول... فهمت.
- Who else debuted in the same year? - It's the batch before...
- من آخر ظهر لأول مرة في نفس العام؟ - إنها الدفعة التي قبل...
Amazing comedians joined KBS in the same year as me.
انضم الكوميديون المذهلون إلى قناة KBS في نفس العام الذي انضممت إليه.
Kim Doo Hyeon, Min Sung Jun,
كيم دو هيون، مين سونغ جون،
- Jang Jun Hee, - Who are they?
- جانغ جون هي - من هم؟
- Song I Ji, Lee Jeong In... - Is this okay?
- سونغ آي جي، لي جيونغ إن... - هل هذا جيد؟
Stop it. It'll be hard for the staff to put their photos on the screen.
أوقفه. سيكون من الصعب على الموظفين وضع صورهم على الشاشة.
- My gosh. That's hilarious. - Sang Gook.
- يا إلهي. هذا فرحان. - سانغ جوك.
- There's Eomjirella too. - Hey.
- هناك Eomjirella أيضا. - يا.
- I bet you said... - That's right.
- أراهن أنك قلت... - هذا صحيح.
some of their names wrong.
بعض أسمائهم خاطئة
- Eom Ji Yoon is one of them. - He mentioned almost all of them.
- إيوم جي يون هي واحدة منهم. - ذكرهم جميعاً تقريباً.
- Oh, Ji Yoon. - We all know Eom Ji Yoon.
- أوه، جي يون. - كلنا نعرف إيوم جي يون.
- Eom Ji Yoon is one of them. - Ji Yoon is from the same batch.
- إيوم جي يون هي واحدة منهم. - جي يون من نفس الدفعة.
- They're all important to me. - That's...
- كلهم ​​مهمين بالنسبة لي. - هذا...
- Jae Youl is right about that. - We've checked everyone else.
- جاي يول محق في ذلك. - لقد فحصنا الجميع.
- Seon Min, what about you? - Won't you let me introduce myself?
- سيون مين، ماذا عنك؟ - لن تسمح لي أن أقدم نفسي؟
Did you join a network as a comedian?
هل انضممت إلى شبكة كممثل كوميدي؟
You're a YouTuber.
أنت من مستخدمي YouTube.
I...
أنا...
I'm the only one who's from a different network.
أنا الوحيد الذي من شبكة مختلفة.
- I'm from SBS. I'm the 16th batch. - Oh, SBS?
- أنا من SBS. انا الدفعة 16 - أوه، SBS؟
- You're the 16th batch? - Yes.
- أنت الدفعة 16؟ - نعم.
- I'm sorry to say this, but... - Who debuted in the same year?
- أنا آسف لقول هذا، ولكن... - من ظهر لأول مرة في نفس العام؟
You don't have the eyes of a comedian.
ليس لديك عيون الممثل الكوميدي.
I mean...
أعني...
- Hey! - But it's true that...
- يا! - ولكن صحيح أن...
- I'm sorry, but... - Hey.
- أنا آسف، ولكن... - مهلا.
- You brat. - Seon Min, you...
- أنت شقي. - سيون مين، أنت...
- Why are you so nervous? - You see...
- لماذا أنت عصبي جدا؟ - هل ترى...
- What kind of eyes do I have? - But he...
- أي نوع من العيون لدي؟ - لكنه...
- There's this look of a comedian. - What does he look like?
- هناك هذا المظهر للممثل الكوميدي. - كيف يبدو؟
But you shouldn't stop him.
لكن لا يجب أن توقفه.
He prepared this for two months. You should let him go on.
لقد أعد هذا لمدة شهرين. يجب عليك السماح له بالاستمرار.
- Right. He has something to say. - We should get back to SBS.
- يمين. لديه ما يقوله. - يجب أن نعود إلى SBS.
- I see only ambition in his eyes. - I still want to introduce myself.
- لا أرى في عينيه إلا الطموح. - ما زلت أريد أن أقدم نفسي.
- I see no comedy in his eyes. - The vibe from his eyes...
- لا أرى أي كوميديا ​​في عينيه. - البهجة من عينيه...
- He has no comedian vibes. - True.
- ليس لديه أي مشاعر كوميدية. - حقيقي.
- I see only ambition in his eyes. - Did I do something that wrong?
- لا أرى في عينيه إلا الطموح. - هل فعلت شيئًا خاطئًا؟
That's not what I mean. I'm saying that...
هذا ليس ما أعنيه. أنا أقول ذلك...
- He doesn't have such vibes. - It's amazing that...
- ليس لديه مثل هذه المشاعر. - من المدهش أن...
he became an entertainer despite that.
أصبح فنانًا على الرغم من ذلك.
- He doesn't look like a comedian. - That's an amazing thing.
- انه لا يبدو وكأنه الممثل الكوميدي. - وهذا شيء مدهش.
- You're right. - It's amazing.
- أنت على حق. - إنه لأمر مدهش.
- Look at his eyes.
- إنه لأمر مدهش. - انظر إلى عينيه.
All right. You're done talking. Let's move on.
حسنًا. لقد انتهيت من الحديث. دعونا نمضي قدما.
- Shut it. I will... - My gosh.
- اغلقه. سأفعل... - يا إلهي.
(Bitter)
(مر)
- So... - He looks rich yet ordinary.
- إذًا... - يبدو غنيًا لكنه عادي.
- Who debuted in the same year? - Oh, about that...
- من ظهر لأول مرة في نفس العام؟ - اه بخصوص ذلك...
- I'd like to mention someone. - Who is it?
- أود أن أذكر شخص ما. - من هذا؟
Kim Min Su from Psick Univ who came on this show recently.
Kim Min Su من Psick Univ الذي شارك في هذا العرض مؤخرًا.
- Oh, that's why... - Oh, Min Su?
- أوه، لهذا السبب... - أوه، مين سو؟
you appeared in a video of "Like Min Su."
لقد ظهرت في فيديو "Like Min Su".
- Right. - That wasn't the reason.
- يمين. - لم يكن هذا هو السبب.
Seon Min, you were the second best...
سيون مين، لقد كنت ثاني أفضل...
- among those from that batch. - That's right.
- من بين تلك الدفعة. - هذا صحيح.
How? Why?
كيف؟ لماذا؟
- What... What do you know? - I mean...
- ماذا... ماذا تعرف؟ - أعني...
- He sounded like Kim Sang Joong. - Don't be like that to my partner.
- بدا مثل كيم سانغ جونغ. - لا تكن هكذا مع شريكي.
What were the benefits of being hired with the second highest score?
ما هي فوائد التعاقد مع ثاني أعلى الدرجات؟
- Were there any benefits? - No, there were no benefits.
- هل كانت هناك أي فوائد؟ - لا، لم تكن هناك فوائد.
Actually,
في الحقيقة،
- SBS pays less... - You would only feel pressured.
- SBS تدفع أقل... - ستشعر بالضغط فقط.
than KBS does.
مما تفعله قناة KBS.
- They'd pay more if you do well. - If they pay less...
- سيدفعون أكثر إذا قمت بعمل جيد. - إذا دفعوا أقل...
- Sang Gook is hilarious today. - Seon Min.
- سانغ جوك مضحك اليوم. - سيون مين.
- Sang Gook, what's gotten into you? - Why are you so angry?
- سانغ جوك، ما الذي أصابك؟ - لماذا أنت غاضب جدا؟
It seems to me that Seon Min...
يبدو لي أن سيون مين...
- Seon Min, can I ask you something? - Sure.
- سيون مين، هل يمكنني أن أسألك شيئًا؟ - بالتأكيد.
Did you have that look on your face even before doing variety shows?
هل كانت لديك تلك النظرة على وجهك حتى قبل القيام ببرامج متنوعة؟
- I was born with a nervous look. - He's so hilarious.
- لقد ولدت بمظهر عصبي. - انه فرحان جدا.
Were you nervous even when you were born?
هل كنت متوتراً حتى عند ولادتك؟
- He's persistent as always. - Then let's...
- إنه مثابر كما هو الحال دائمًا. - ثم دعونا...
- Let's help Seon Min... - Ho Dong is persistent.
- دعونا نساعد سيون مين... - هو دونغ مثابر.
- relieve his nervousness. - Okay.
- تخفيف عصبيته. - تمام.
- You comedians have many stories... - Just relax.
- أنتم أيها الكوميديون لديكم العديد من القصص... - فقط استرخوا.
to share about one another, right?
لنتشارك عن بعضنا البعض، أليس كذلك؟
- Including heartwarming stories. - Some are bad rumors.
- بما في ذلك القصص الحميمة. - بعضها شائعات سيئة.
Bad things about one another will be even better.
الأشياء السيئة عن بعضها البعض ستكون أفضل.
- Share some good stories. - Good stories?
- شارك بعض القصص الجيدة. - قصص جيدة؟
- I have a good story to share. - Do you have one?
- لدي قصة جيدة للمشاركة. - هل لديك واحدة؟
- I'll go first. - Go ahead.
- سأذهب أولا. - تفضل.
Kyung Hoon, who's been devoted...
كيونغ هون، الذي كان مخلصًا...
to his family and the variety shows he's on,
لعائلته والعروض المتنوعة التي يقدمها،
finally released a new song.
أصدرت أخيرا أغنية جديدة.
- Really? - Kyung Hoon did?
- حقًا؟ - فعل كيونغ هون؟
- That's good news. - That's a good story.
- هذه أخبار جيدة. - هذه قصة جيدة.
- He's really great. - He works so hard.
- انه عظيم حقا. - إنه يعمل بجد.
- Kyung Hoon, can you... - He has a lot of work now.
- كيونغ هون، هل يمكنك... - لديه الكثير من العمل الآن.
- Can you sing a little bit for us? - Kyung Hoon works really hard.
- هل يمكنك الغناء قليلا بالنسبة لنا؟ - كيونغ هون يعمل بجد حقا.
The song is about being a sinner.
الأغنية تدور حول كونك آثمًا.
The song title is "Sin," isn't it?
عنوان الأغنية هو "الخطيئة"، أليس كذلك؟
- Right? - "Sin?"
- يمين؟ - "الخطيئة؟"
- Yes, the song title is "Sin." - It's "Sin."
- نعم عنوان الأغنية هو "الخطيئة". - إنها "الخطيئة".
- Isn't it a remade song? - The band...
- أليست أغنية متجددة؟ - الفرقة...
I remade "Sin," the song by the band called Lug.
لقد قمت بإعادة إنتاج أغنية "Sin"، وهي أغنية الفرقة التي تدعى Lug.
- Have you ever heard the song? - So there is an original song.
- هل سمعت الأغنية من قبل؟ - إذن هناك أغنية أصلية.
I'll let you hear the recorded version.
سأترككم تستمعون إلى النسخة المسجلة.
- Let's take a listen. - It's his new song, right?
- دعونا نستمع. - إنها أغنيته الجديدة، أليس كذلك؟
- Let's listen. - Yes, it's his new song.
- دعونا نستمع. - نعم، إنها أغنيته الجديدة.
("Sin" by Min Kyung Hoon)
("الخطيئة" بقلم مين كيونغ هون)
- This sounds... - He forgot to recycle the trash?
- يبدو هذا... - هل نسي إعادة تدوير القمامة؟
He conveys genuine feelings of guilt.
ينقل مشاعر حقيقية بالذنب.
Is it a message to his wife?
هل هي رسالة لزوجته؟
(If I could get you back after this painful breakup,)
(لو كان بإمكاني استعادتك بعد هذا الانفصال المؤلم،)
(I would do anything)
(سأفعل أي شيء)
- Many men will sing it at karaoke. - It's a good song.
- كثير من الرجال سوف يغنونها في الكاريوكي. - إنها أغنية جيدة.
Seon Min, what do you think?
سيون مين، ما رأيك؟
He's quite good at singing.
إنه جيد جدًا في الغناء.
- Why is he so nervous? - "He's quite good."
- لماذا هو عصبي جدا؟ - "إنه جيد جدًا."
Anyone who's not a comedian could replace you.
يمكن لأي شخص ليس ممثلًا كوميديًا أن يحل محلك.
Shut it.
اغلقه.
- Sang Gook, what would you say? - Sang Gook, what do you think?
- سانغ جوك، ماذا ستقول؟ - سانغ جوك، ما رأيك؟
"He's good at singing?" Anyone could say such a thing.
"إنه جيد في الغناء؟" يمكن لأي شخص أن يقول مثل هذا الشيء.
- Sang Gook, tell us what you think. - He's being harsh on him.
- سانغ جوك، أخبرنا برأيك. - إنه قاس عليه.
- Yang Sang Gook... - Sang Gook.
- يانغ سانغ جوك... - سانغ جوك.
- That was hilarious. - Here's what I think.
- كان ذلك فرحان. - وهذا ما أعتقده.
The last time Sang Gook came on the show,
آخر مرة ظهر فيها سانغ غوك في البرنامج،
Men on a Mission got the highest ratings of last year.
حصل فيلم "رجال في مهمة" على أعلى التقييمات في العام الماضي.
(Men on a Mission got the highest ratings in 2025.)
(حصل فيلم "رجال في مهمة" على أعلى التصنيفات في عام 2025).
- That gave him confidence. - That's right.
- وهذا أعطاه الثقة. - هذا صحيح.
So he's full of confidence right now.
لذا فهو مليء بالثقة الآن.
"You brat!" That's what cracked up the viewers.
"أنت شقي!" وهذا ما صدم المشاهدين.
(You brat!)
(أنت شقي!)
(Kang Ho Dong, you brat!)
(كانغ هو دونغ، أيها الشقي!)
(He intimidated Ho Dong,)
(قام بترهيب هو دونغ،)
(and helped us get high ratings at the same time!)
(وساعدنا في الحصول على تقييمات عالية في نفس الوقت!)
People liked it so much.
أحب الناس ذلك كثيرا.
I mean, they had never seen anyone...
أعني أنهم لم يروا أحداً من قبل
- who treated Ho Dong like that. - That's true.
- من عامل هو دونغ بهذه الطريقة. - هذا صحيح.
- A story just crossed my mind. - Okay.
- قصة طرأت على ذهني للتو. - تمام.
Ho Dong and I co-starred...
لقد شاركنا أنا و هو دونغ في البطولة...
- on "Cool Kiz on the Block." - "Cool Kiz on the Block."
- في "Cool Kiz on the Block". - ""كول كيز أون ذا بلوك.""
We worked together for two years.
لقد عملنا معًا لمدة عامين.
- One time, - They must be close.
- مرة واحدة - يجب أن يكونوا قريبين.
we played tennis, and I was so bad at it.
لقد لعبنا التنس، وكنت سيئًا جدًا في ذلك.
- He couldn't get better quickly. - Tennis was so difficult for me.
- لم يستطع أن يتحسن بسرعة. - التنس كان صعباً جداً بالنسبة لي.
During a shoot, I got mad at myself...
أثناء التصوير كنت غاضبة من نفسي..
- and cried. - Oh, no. Poor him.
- وبكى. - أوه لا. مسكين له.
Back then, Ho Dong didn't even have my phone number.
في ذلك الوقت، لم يكن لدى هو دونغ رقم ​​هاتفي.
We had never contacted each other.
لم نتواصل أبدًا مع بعضنا البعض.
But that day, he texted me, "Good job."
لكن في ذلك اليوم، أرسل لي رسالة نصية: "عمل جيد".
- That's cool. - He texted me.
- هذا بارد. - لقد أرسل لي رسالة نصية.
That evening, I was so touched by his text message.
في ذلك المساء، تأثرت كثيرًا برسالته النصية.
- It made me cry again. - Really?
- لقد جعلني أبكي مرة أخرى. - حقًا؟
He didn't even have my number...
ولم يكن لديه رقمي حتى..
and had never contacted me before then.
ولم يتصل بي قط قبل ذلك الحين.
- I asked around for your number? - Did he get the wrong number?
- لقد سألت حول رقمك؟ - هل حصل على الرقم الخطأ؟
- That's right. - He probably meant to say,
- هذا صحيح. - ربما كان يقصد أن يقول،
"Good job. Let's never see each other again."
"عمل جيد. دعونا لا نرى بعضنا البعض مرة أخرى."
I did get fired from the show.
لقد طردت من العرض.
"Good job."
"أحسنت."
- That's what he meant. - That's right.
- هذا ما كان يقصده. - هذا صحيح.
(It turned out to be a sad story.)
(اتضح أنها قصة حزينة).
That's what he meant.
هذا ما كان يقصده.
Let me add another story.
واسمحوا لي أن أضيف قصة أخرى.
- I have a story about Ho Dong. - What is it?
- لدي قصة عن هو دونغ. - ما هذا؟
- It was a show where we ate food. - Right.
- لقد كان عرضًا حيث تناولنا الطعام. - يمين.
I was told that I could be on Ho Dong's food show...
قيل لي أنه بإمكاني أن أكون في برنامج طعام هو دونغ...
if I went to Sokcho.
إذا ذهبت إلى سوكشو.
So I said I would go there no matter what.
لذلك قلت أنني سأذهب إلى هناك مهما حدث.
But there was one condition.
ولكن كان هناك شرط واحد.
I played this character, imitating Lee Kyoung Young.
لقد لعبت هذه الشخصية، مقلدًا Lee Kyung Young.
I was called Kwak Kyoung Young.
لقد تم استدعائي كواك كيونج يونج.
I was asked to speak in that tone...
طلبت مني أن أتكلم بهذه اللهجة..
- only at the opening. - Right. That's understandable.
- فقط عند الافتتاح. - يمين. هذا أمر مفهوم.
So I asked if I could get changed after the opening...
لذلك سألت إذا كان بإمكاني تغيير ملابسي بعد الافتتاح.
- and after that... - You could be Kwak Beom.
- وبعد ذلك... - يمكنك أن تكون كواك بيوم.
- Yes, I asked if I could be me. - Right. That's important.
- نعم، سألت إذا كان بإمكاني أن أكون أنا. - يمين. هذا مهم.
So I introduced myself like this.
لذلك قدمت نفسي هكذا.
(Shouting)
(صراخ)
"I've never seen you before. That's good."
"لم أرك من قبل. هذا جيد."
- Then he got hooked on it. - Right.
- ثم أصبح مدمن مخدرات عليه. - يمين.
He wanted me not to change my clothes.
أراد مني ألا أغير ملابسي.
- I needed to eat food, you know. - Right.
- كنت بحاجة لتناول الطعام، كما تعلمون. - يمين.
- He had to focus on the show. - I mean...
- كان عليه أن يركز على العرض. - أعني...
- Once he's hooked on something, - That's right.
- بمجرد أن يصبح مدمناً على شيء ما - هذا صحيح.
you should keep doing it forever.
يجب عليك الاستمرار في القيام بذلك إلى الأبد.
- You wanted to be yourself too. - We just finished the opening,
- أردت أن تكون نفسك أيضا. - لقد انتهينا للتو من الافتتاح،
and my voice was already hoarse.
وكان صوتي أجش بالفعل.
I asked the director if I could get changed and go to the restaurant.
سألت المدير إذا كان بإمكاني تغيير ملابسي والذهاب إلى المطعم.
But he said, "Ho Dong likes your character so much,"
لكنه قال: "هو دونغ يحب شخصيتك كثيراً"
"so we need you to keep playing the character."
"لذلك نحن بحاجة لك لمواصلة لعب الشخصية."
- I tried to speak in my own tone. - Right.
- حاولت أن أتكلم في لهجتي الخاصة. - يمين.
"Beom, how have you been?"
"بيوم، كيف حالك؟"
I spoke in my own tone of voice, and he said, "No!"
لقد تحدثت بنبرة صوتي، فقال: "لا!"
- Of course. - "Action!"
- بالطبع. - "فعل!"
I was like, "My life has been good!"
كنت مثل، "حياتي كانت جيدة!"
- You were still Kwak Kyoung Young? - "I've been doing great!"
- كنت لا تزال كواك كيونغ يونغ؟ - "لقد قمت بعمل رائع!"
- All day long? - "I ate it!"
- طوال اليوم؟ - "لقد أكلته!"
- That makes your voice hoarse. - "Chili sauce. Go for it!"
- وهذا يجعل صوتك أجش. - "صلصة الفلفل الحار. احصل عليها!"
I thought that was the end.
اعتقدت أن هذه كانت النهاية.
But we went to another restaurant.
لكننا ذهبنا إلى مطعم آخر.
I asked with a hoarse voice, "Can I get changed now?"
سألت بصوت أجش: "هل يمكنني أن أغير ملابسي الآن؟"
The director said Ho Dong liked it so much.
قال المخرج أن Ho Dong أحبه كثيرًا.
So I had to maintain the character.
لذلك كان علي أن أحافظ على الشخصية.
While grilling meat, I said, "I grilled it!"
وأنا أشوي اللحم قلت: لقد شويته!
- "It's cooked well! Go for it!" - You were still Kwak Kyoung Young?
- "إنه مطبوخ جيدًا! اذهب إليه!" - كنت لا تزال كواك كيونغ يونغ؟
When I said goodbye to him after the shoot,
عندما ودعته بعد التصوير،
I sounded like this. "Thank you for everything today."
لقد بدت هكذا. "شكرا لك على كل شيء اليوم."
- He helped me stand out. - That must've been hard.
- لقد ساعدني على التميز. - لابد أن ذلك كان صعباً.
When we were doing a show...
عندما كنا نقوم بالعرض...
- I didn't know when to stop. - The other...
- لم أكن أعرف متى أتوقف. - الآخر...
I'm sorry. That day, I enjoyed it so much...
أنا آسف. في ذلك اليوم استمتعت كثيرا..
- that I couldn't refrain myself. - He couldn't refrain himself.
- أنني لم أستطع أن أمنع نفسي. - لم يستطع أن يضبط نفسه.
Beom's story cracked all of us up...
قصة بيوم صدمتنا جميعاً..
except for one person.
باستثناء شخص واحد.
- I saw him. - Seon Min, are you all right?
- رأيته. - سيون مين، هل أنت بخير؟
What? What is wrong with you?
ماذا؟ ما هو الخطأ معك؟
- Wasn't his story funny? - He looks upset.
- ألم تكن قصته مضحكة؟ - يبدو مستاءً.
- You should respond to others too. - It was funny.
- يجب عليك الرد على الآخرين أيضا. - كان مضحكا.
It was funny. I found it funny.
كان مضحكا. لقد وجدت أنه مضحك.
It was funny, you punks!
لقد كان الأمر مضحكاً أيها الأشرار!
- What's wrong with him? - I said it was funny. Happy now?
- ما هو الخطأ معه؟ - قلت أنه كان مضحكا. سعيد الآن؟
You don't swear on this show.
أنت لا أقسم على هذا العرض.
- Aren't we all friends here? - Yes, but you don't swear here.
- ألسنا جميعا أصدقاء هنا؟ - نعم، ولكنك لا تقسم هنا.
- You don't swear here. - We're friends, but don't swear.
- أنت لا تقسم هنا. - نحن أصدقاء، ولكن لا أقسم.
- Oh, I thought it was okay. - No one swears here.
- أوه، اعتقدت أنه كان على ما يرام. - لا أحد يقسم هنا.
- I mean, if you swear... - Seon Min, you just got mad...
- أعني، إذا أقسمت... - سيون مين، لقد غضبت للتو...
- for no reason. - Hey, on this show...
- بدون سبب. - مهلا، في هذا المعرض...
Do it in your YouTube videos. This is JTBC!
افعل ذلك في مقاطع الفيديو الخاصة بك على YouTube. هذه جي تي بي سي!
Shut it, you donkey!
اصمت أيها الحمار!
What was that?
ماذا كان هذا؟
- That was random too. - I'm a donkey?
- وكان ذلك عشوائيا أيضا. - أنا حمار؟
- How could you call me a donkey? - A donkey?
- كيف يمكن أن تدعوني حمار؟ - حمار؟
- You have the face of a donkey. - That's so funny.
- لديك وجه حمار. - هذا مضحك جدا.
Shut your mouth, you hippo!
أغلق فمك، أنت فرس النهر!
(He was the Creator, but now, he's a hippo.)
(كان هو الخالق، ولكنه الآن فرس النهر).
- Seon Min, the donkey beat you. - That was a good one.
- سيون مين، الحمار ضربك. - تلك كانت فكرة جيدة.
That was totally raw.
كان ذلك خامًا تمامًا.
So many of our today's guests speak in dialect.
يتحدث الكثير من ضيوفنا اليوم باللهجة.
Many of you are...
كثيرون منكم...
- from Gyeongsang Province. - Gyeongsang Province.
- من مقاطعة جيونج سانج. - مقاطعة جيونج سانج.
- Bong Sun is from that area. - But from different areas, right?
- بونج صن من تلك المنطقة. - ولكن من مناطق مختلفة، أليس كذلك؟
- Where are you guys from? - I'm from Nampo-dong, Busan.
- من أين أنتم يا رفاق؟ - أنا من نامبو دونغ، بوسان.
- Oh, Nampo-dong? - I'm from Nampo-dong. Yes.
- أوه، نامبو دونغ؟ - أنا من نامبو دونغ. نعم.
I'm from Gimhae, South Gyeongsang Province.
أنا من كيمهاي، مقاطعة كيونغسانغ الجنوبية.
- Oh, Gimhae? - Gimhae, South Gyeongsang Province.
- أوه، جيمهاي؟ - كيمهاي، مقاطعة كيونغسانغ الجنوبية.
I'm from Namtong-dong, Gumi, North Gyeongsang Province.
أنا من نامتونج دونج، جومي، مقاطعة جيونج سانج الشمالية.
But why does your dialect sound awkward?
لكن لماذا تبدو لهجتك غريبة؟
- The Gumi dialect is different. - It's a little bit unique.
- لهجة جومي مختلفة. - إنها فريدة من نوعها بعض الشيء.
I've been living in Seoul for 19 years, so it faded.
لقد كنت أعيش في سيول منذ 19 عامًا، لذا فقد تلاشت.
- Who else is from Gumi? - "So it faded."
- من آخر من جومي؟ - "وهكذا تلاشت".
There are five top stars from Gumi.
هناك خمسة نجوم كبار من جومي.
- Top stars from Gumi... - Seon Min, I'm sorry,
- أفضل النجوم من غومي... - سيون مين، أنا آسف،
but you should speak formally to me.
ولكن يجب عليك التحدث معي رسميا.
Yes, sir.
نعم يا سيدي.
- He's our teacher. - Oh, right. He's our teacher.
- إنه معلمنا. - أوه، الحق. إنه معلمنا.
- He's hosting the show now. - Right.
- إنه يستضيف العرض الآن. - يمين.
- I'm sorry, sir. - He's practically a thug.
- أنا آسف يا سيدي. - إنه عمليا سفاح.
- Is he a thug? - He's scary.
- هل هو سفاح؟ - إنه مخيف.
- I'm sorry. - Who are those top stars?
- أنا آسف. - من هم هؤلاء النجوم الكبار؟
- There are these stars from Gumi. - You see...
- هناك هؤلاء النجوم من جومي. - هل ترى...
- Jang Woo Hyuk of H.O.T. - Jang Woo Hyuk?
- جانغ ووك من هيو من HOT - جانغ وو هيو؟
Kim Tae Woo of god.
كيم تاي وو من الله.
Kwon Jung Yeol of 10cm.
كوون جونغ يول 10 سم.
Hwang Chi Yeul.
هوانج تشي يول.
And Lee Seon Min.
و لي سيون مين.
- Aren't there 4 top stars? - There are only 4 of them.
- أليس هناك 4 نجوم كبار؟ - لا يوجد سوى 4 منهم.
- Shouldn't you call them 4 kings? - Aren't 5 too many?
- ألا ينبغي أن تسميهم 4 ملوك؟ - ليست 5 كثيرة جدا؟
I'm quite popular among young people these days.
أنا مشهور جدًا بين الشباب هذه الأيام.
- That's true. - Seon Min, step up your game a bit.
- هذا صحيح. - سيون مين، صعد لعبتك قليلاً.
- Just a bit. - All right.
- قليلا فقط. - حسنًا.
- "All right."
- "حسنًا." - حسنًا.
- "All right?" - We're friends here.
- "حسنًا؟" - نحن أصدقاء هنا.
What about Jae Youl?
ماذا عن جاي يول؟
Aren't you from Seoul, Jae Youl?
ألست من سيول، جاي يول؟
- Aren't you from Seoul? - I was born...
- ليست أنت من سيول؟ - لقد ولدت...
in Donghae, Gangwon Province.
(دونغهاي في مقاطعة جانج وون).
- Oh, Gangwon Province. - They're both from there.
- أوه، مقاطعة جانج وون. - كلاهما من هناك.
- We're both from Gangwon Province. - Right, he's also from there.
- نحن على حد سواء من مقاطعة جانج وون. - صحيح، وهو أيضا من هناك.
Me? I'm from Jeonju.
أنا؟ أنا من جيونجو.
- We barely have an accent. - That's right.
- بالكاد لدينا لهجة. - هذا صحيح.
Just add "now" to the Seoul accent, and it's the Jeonju dialect.
فقط أضف "الآن" إلى لهجة سيول، وستكون هذه لهجة جيونجو.
- What do you mean by that? - Really?
- ماذا تقصد بذلك؟ - حقًا؟
- "Now, let's eat." - "Hello..."
- "والآن، دعونا نأكل." - "مرحبًا..."
- "Now, let's go to bed." - Start a sentence with "now?"
- "والآن، دعونا نذهب إلى السرير." - ابدأ الجملة بـ "الآن؟"
If you want to sound more native, add "quite."
إذا كنت تريد أن تبدو أكثر أصالة، أضف "تمامًا".
- "Quite?" - Add "quite," and that's it.
- "تمامًا؟" - أضف "تماما"، وهذا كل شيء.
That's simple.
هذا بسيط.
People in Gumi say "got it" at the end of every sentence.
يقول الناس في غومي "فهمت" في نهاية كل جملة.
- It's unique. - Oh, that's right.
- إنها فريدة من نوعها. - أوه، هذا صحيح.
- Really? - "Eat up, got it?"
- حقًا؟ - "تناول الطعام، فهمت؟"
- Yes, that's right. - Really?
- نعم هذا صحيح. - حقًا؟
- Is that so? - Just add "got it."
- هل هذا صحيح؟ - فقط أضف "فهمت".
- "Got it?" - "Do it like this, got it?"
- "فهمتها؟" - "هل الأمر هكذا، فهمت؟"
"Do this and that, got it?"
"افعل هذا وذاك، فهمت؟"
- I found the Gumi dialect so funny, - It's true.
- لقد وجدت لهجة غومي مضحكة للغاية - هذا صحيح.
I learned how to speak in the Gumi dialect.
لقد تعلمت كيفية التحدث بلهجة غومي.
Adding "got it" while speaking in the Gyeongsang Province accent...
إضافة "فهمت" أثناء التحدث بلهجة مقاطعة جيونج سانج...
- is very unique. - I've never heard that before.
- فريدة جدًا. - لم أسمع ذلك من قبل.
People in Chungcheong Province add "got it" as well...
يضيف الناس في مقاطعة تشانج تشونج عبارة "فهمت الأمر" أيضًا...
I'm from Mungyeong, North Gyeongsang Province,
أنا من مونج يونج، مقاطعة شمال جيونج سانج،
and I add "got it" too.
وأضيف "فهمت" أيضًا.
- Right? - Right.
- يمين؟ - يمين.
- People in Mungyeong do it too. - We say "got it."
- الناس في Mungyeong يفعلون ذلك أيضًا. - نقول "فهمت".
- "Eat up, got it?" - "What's wrong? Got it?"
- "تناول الطعام، فهمت؟" - "ما المشكلة؟ فهمت؟"
"That's the way it is. Got it? Grandma, got it?"
"هذا هو الحال. فهمت؟ جدتي، فهمت؟"
You just say "got it" at the end of every sentence.
ما عليك سوى أن تقول "فهمت" في نهاية كل جملة.
- "It's like this. Got it?" - It's not a formal way of speaking.
- "الأمر هكذا. فهمت؟" - إنها ليست طريقة رسمية للتحدث.
- It's a casual way of speaking. - Exactly.
- إنها طريقة عارضة للتحدث. - بالضبط.
- It's a casual way of speaking? - It's a casual way?
- إنها طريقة عارضة للتحدث؟ - إنها طريقة عارضة؟
In Gyeongsang Province, we speak like this. "Granny."
في مقاطعة كيونغسانغ، نتحدث بهذه الطريقة. "الجدة."
After hearing Bong Sun speak in dialect,
بعد سماع بونغ سون يتحدث باللهجة،
- Seon Min's dialect sounds fake. - Right?
- لهجة Seon Min تبدو مزيفة. - يمين؟
- It sounds like a fake dialect. - "What are you blabbering about?"
- يبدو وكأنه لهجة وهمية. - "ما الذي تتحدث عنه؟"
That's really funny.
هذا مضحك حقا.
- That's funny. - "Hey, shut your mouth, you brat."
- هذا مضحك. - "مهلا، أغلق فمك، أيها الشقي."
- "Just shut it." Like this.
- هذا مضحك. - "فقط أغلقه." مثله.
"What are you blabbering about? Got it?"
"ما الذي تتحدث عنه؟ فهمت؟"
(Surprised)
(تفاجأ)
"Got it?"
"فهمتها؟"
"What are you blabbering about? Got it?"
"ما الذي تتحدث عنه؟ فهمت؟"
(He cracks everyone up!)
(إنه يكسر الجميع!)
- "Got it?" - "What are you saying? Got it?"
- "فهمتها؟" - "ماذا تقول؟ فهمت؟"
- That was good. Great job. - "Just shut it. Got it?"
- كان ذلك جيدًا. عمل عظيم. - "فقط أغلقه. هل فهمت؟"
"What are you blabbering about? Got it?"
"ما الذي تتحدث عنه؟ فهمت؟"
- That was good. - Seon Min finally looks happy.
- كان ذلك جيدًا. - سيون مين تبدو سعيدة أخيرًا.
- You made it. That was good. - He cracked us all up.
- لقد نجحت. كان ذلك جيدًا. - لقد قضى علينا جميعا.
He finally seems happy.
أخيرًا يبدو سعيدًا.
Keep at it. Got it?
استمر في ذلك. فهمتها؟
- I feel good. Got it? - Great job.
- أشعر أنني بحالة جيدة. فهمتها؟ - عمل عظيم.
- You've made it finally. - I did well, didn't I?
- لقد فعلت ذلك أخيرا. - لقد قمت بعمل جيد، أليس كذلك؟
Thank you. Got it?
شكرًا لك. فهمتها؟
- That was unexpected. - Good job, Seon Min.
- كان ذلك غير متوقع. - عمل جيد، سيون مين.
- Now that Seon Min... - Good job. Got it?
- الآن بعد أن سيون مين... - عمل جيد. فهمتها؟
That's a combination of different dialects.
هذا مزيج من اللهجات المختلفة.
- Now that Seon Min is on a roll... - Oh, really?
- الآن بعد أن بدأ Seon Min في النجاح... - أوه، حقًا؟
Can you do something funny like singing in dialect?
هل يمكنك أن تفعل شيئًا مضحكًا مثل الغناء باللهجة؟
- Can he do things like that? - Well... Yes.
- هل يستطيع أن يفعل أشياء من هذا القبيل؟ - حسنا... نعم.
- He planned this. - Sing a song in dialect.
- لقد خطط لهذا. - غناء أغنية باللهجة.
- Did you prepare a song for us? - He's good at it.
- هل أعددت لنا أغنية؟ - انه جيد في ذلك.
I want to stand out too, but I feel like only I'm failing to do so.
أريد أن أتميز أيضًا، لكني أشعر أنني الوحيد الذي أفشل في القيام بذلك.
- Where should I sing? - You're doing well.
- أين يجب أن أغني؟ - أنت بخير.
You can sing it there.
يمكنك غنائها هناك.
- Here? - Yes, there.
- هنا؟ - نعم هناك.
- Come on, Seon Min. - Go to the front.
- هيا سيون مين. - اذهب إلى الأمام.
- Seon Min.
- سيون مين. - اذهب إلى الأمام.
- Go or sit? - Go.
- اذهب أو الجلوس؟ - يذهب.
- Go?
- يذهب؟ - يذهب.
- What a funny dialect. - Sang Min.
- يا لها من لهجة مضحكة. - سانغ مين.
- What was that? - Are you jealous?
- ماذا كان هذا؟ - هل أنت غيور؟
He's using a fake dialect to be funny.
إنه يستخدم لهجة مزيفة ليكون مضحكا.
- No, but listen. - It's real.
- لا، ولكن استمع. - إنه حقيقي.
- I'll be singing like a guy... - Yes?
- سأغني مثل الرجل... - نعم؟
- full of bluff after breaking up... - Kind of like...
- مليئة بالخداع بعد الانفصال... - نوعاً ما...
- with his girlfriend in Gumi. - I see.
- مع صديقته في جومي. - أرى.
- Nice. - The song is "Emergency Room."
- لطيف - جيد. - الأغنية هي "غرفة الطوارئ".
"Emergency Room" by izi.
"غرفة الطوارئ" من تأليف إيزي.
- Comedy with a theme is funny. - It has a story.
- الكوميديا ​​مع موضوع مضحك. - ولها قصة.
This will hit 10 million views. No, 100 million views.
وهذا سيصل إلى 10 ملايين مشاهدة. لا، 100 مليون مشاهدة.
- One hundred million views? - Nice.
- مائة مليون مشاهدة؟ - لطيف - جيد.
- Let's reach 100 million views. - Yes.
- لنصل إلى 100 مليون مشاهدة. - نعم.
- Enjoy. - Good luck.
- يتمتع. - حظ سعيد.
- Give me a round of applause.
- أعطني جولة من التصفيق. - حظ سعيد.
"Emergency Room."
"غرفة الطوارئ."
Don't flop it.
لا تتخبط فيه.
(A specialty he worked on for two months while refusing all work)
(تخصص عمل به لمدة شهرين وهو يرفض كل الأعمال)
- "Give me a round of applause." - "Applause."
- "أعطني جولة من التصفيق". - "تصفيق".
Guys often sing a song like that.
غالبًا ما يغني الرجال أغنية كهذه.
(I'm currently in regret)
(أنا حاليا نادم)
(Got it?)
(فهمتها؟)
(The day)
(اليوم)
(We had a blow-up)
(حدث لنا انفجار)
- Do you actually say that? - Yes, "blow-up."
- هل تقول ذلك فعلا؟ - نعم "تفجير".
(Because)
(لأن)
(Of my pointless pride)
(من كبريائي الذي لا معنى له)
- Pride. - Yes, pride.
- فخر. - نعم فخر.
(I asked that)
(لقد طلبت ذلك)
(We break up, okay?)
(لقد انفصلنا، حسنًا؟)
- He said, "Okay." - You should've said, "Got it?"
- قال: "حسنا". - كان عليك أن تقول: "فهمت؟"
- He didn't say "got it." - But he gave it his all...
- ولم يقل "فهمت". - لكنه أعطى كل ما لديه ...
until that point.
حتى تلك النقطة.
That's it. It should be "got it."
هذا كل شيء. يجب أن يكون "فهمت".
(I hope you'll ask me to stay)
(أتمنى أن تطلب مني البقاء)
(Got it?)
(فهمتها؟)
Yes, keep that going.
نعم، استمر في ذلك.
(The lyrics are no longer in a dialect style.)
(لم تعد الكلمات بأسلوب اللهجة.)
(But no matter how many days have passed)
(ولكن مهما مرت الأيام)
(Got it?)
(فهمتها؟)
(Adding "got it" to everything)
(إضافة "فهمت" إلى كل شيء)
(I'm hearing nothing from you)
(لم أسمع منك شيئا)
(Got it?)
(فهمتها؟)
(His specialty has lost its course.)
(لقد فقد تخصصه مساره.)
- I could do it. - I could totally do it.
- أستطيع أن أفعل ذلك. - أستطيع أن أفعل ذلك تماما.
(Got it?)
(فهمتها؟)
(I must've underestimated it)
(لا بد أنني قللت من تقديره)
- Add "got it," and it's fine? - Keep it up.
- أضف "فهمت"، ولا بأس؟ - استمر.
(I finally know)
(أعرف أخيرا)
(Because of my persistence, got it?)
(بسبب إصراري، فهمت؟)
(You had it tough)
(لقد كان الأمر صعبا عليك)
(Got it?)
(فهمتها؟)
Nice.
لطيف - جيد.
(You fool, it's not true)
(يا غبي هذا ليس صحيحا)
(Got it?)
(فهمتها؟)
- Come on. - That's being ridiculous.
- تعال. - وهذا أمر مثير للسخرية.
(Even now)
(حتى الآن)
(His specialty is in a pinch.)
(تخصصه في السؤال.)
(Do you still)
(هل لا تزال)
(Not know me?)
(لا تعرفني؟)
(The ardent breakup dialect is hard to listen to without tearing up.)
(من الصعب الاستماع إلى لهجة الانفصال المتحمس دون تمزيقها).
(Please)
(لو سمحت)
(Don't leave me)
(لا تتركنى)
(Got it?)
(فهمتها؟)
Well done.
أحسنت.
(Exhaling)
(الزفير)
- Well done. - The song...
- أحسنت. - الأغنية...
- You're good at singing. - You're a great singer.
- أنت جيد في الغناء. - أنت مغنية عظيمة.
- Seon Min is good at singing. - Because...
- سيون مين جيد في الغناء. - لأن...
our reaction was dull,
ردة فعلنا كانت مملة
he kept singing full on throughout the song.
استمر في الغناء بالكامل طوال الأغنية.
I watched Seon Min...
لقد شاهدت سيون مين...
- during practice. - Is that so?
- أثناء الممارسة. - هل هذا صحيح؟
He just sang normally because he was...
لقد كان يغني بشكل طبيعي لأنه كان...
hooked on "got it?"
مدمن مخدرات على "فهمت؟"
- There were no dialects. - Right?
- لم تكن هناك لهجات. - يمين؟
- Originally... - You see,
- في الأصل... - كما ترى،
everyone saying "got it?" made it...
الجميع يقول "فهمت؟" صنعتها...
impossible for me to sing as practiced.
من المستحيل بالنسبة لي أن أغني كما أمارس.
"Got it?" isn't a dialect of Gumi.
"فهمتها؟" ليست لهجة غومي.
But you just sang it.
لكنك غنيتها للتو.
It's not Gumi's dialect.
إنها ليست لهجة غومي.
- Come back. - Seon Min.
- عد. - سيون مين.
Don't get the wrong idea, got it?
لا تفهم الفكرة الخاطئة، هل فهمت؟
- Okay. - Seon Min simply sang.
- تمام. - غنت سيون مين ببساطة.
- But he was good at it. - Jae Youl.
- لكنه كان جيدا في ذلك. - جاي يول.
Just now, Seon Min dramatized it.
الآن فقط، قام Seon Min بتمثيله.
But Jae Youl heard...
لكن جاي يول سمع...
- the original, right? - Yes.
- الأصلي، أليس كذلك؟ - نعم.
Is the original better or the earlier one?
هل الأصل أفضل أم الأقدم؟
The earlier one.
السابق.
- Is that so? - Thank goodness I changed it.
- هل هذا صحيح؟ - الحمد لله قمت بتغييره.
- Really? - Can I make another tip-off?
- حقًا؟ - هل يمكنني تقديم بلاغ آخر؟
I was looking forward to Seon Min...
كنت أتطلع إلى سيون مين...
breaking down while singing the original version.
الانهيار أثناء غناء النسخة الأصلية.
- It was good. - That one was better. Well done.
- لقد كانت جيدة. - هذا كان أفضل. أحسنت.
- Here's what surprised me. - It was better.
- وهنا ما فاجأني. - كان أفضل.
In the waiting room,
في غرفة الانتظار،
it seemed like Seon Min was going to mess it up,
يبدو أن Seon Min كان على وشك إفساد الأمر،
and Beom was supposed to cut in.
وكان من المفترض أن يتدخل بيوم.
- But Beom didn't do anything. - How mean of Seon Min.
- ولكن بيوم لم يفعل أي شيء. - كم يعني سيون مين.
- He didn't cut in. - Why didn't you cut in?
- لم يتدخل. - لماذا لم تدخل؟
Here was the plan.
هنا كانت الخطة.
If Seon Min were singing with the dialect,
لو كانت سيون مين تغني باللهجة،
Beom would intrude, grab Seon Min by the collar,
كان بيوم يتطفل، ويمسك سيون مين من ياقته،
and say, "What is wrong with him?"
فيقول: ما له؟
- What's wrong with this guy? - With that,
- ما هو الخطأ في هذا الرجل؟ - وبهذا،
- The plan... - the two were to wrap it up.
- الخطة... - كان على الاثنين أن يختتماها.
- It was a fail. - We were to end it with,
- لقد كان فاشلا. - كان علينا أن ننهي الأمر بـ،
"What's wrong with this guy?"
"ما خطب هذا الرجل؟"
It all went out the window.
لقد خرج كل شيء من النافذة.
You even planned this conversation, right?
لقد خططت حتى لهذه المحادثة، أليس كذلك؟
Of course.
بالطبع.
- It all went down the drain. - What a bummer.
- لقد ذهب كل ذلك هباءً. - يا لها من مشكله.
- Whatever. - By the way, Bong Sun...
- أيا كان. - بالمناسبة، بونغ صن...
is getting prettier every time we see her.
تصبح أجمل في كل مرة نراها.
- Today, you're... - Bong Sun...
- اليوم، أنت... - بونج صن...
- lost a lot of weight. - People keep telling me that...
- فقدت الكثير من الوزن. - الناس يستمرون في إخباري بذلك..
- I'm becoming prettier. - Right.
- أنا أصبحت أجمل. - يمين.
But the thing is, I started off without a clear feature.
لكن الأمر هو أنني بدأت بدون ميزة واضحة.
- Come on. - I started off with zero beauty.
- تعال. - لقد بدأت بجمال صفر.
There's a rumor that Bong Sun...
هناك إشاعة بأن بونغ سون...
was popular...
كانت شعبية...
when she was a comedienne on KBS.
عندما كانت ممثلة كوميدية على قناة KBS.
From what I know, even Sang Gook had feelings for her.
مما أعرفه، حتى سانغ جوك كان لديه مشاعر تجاهها.
- What? - Sang Gook did?
- ماذا؟ - هل سانغ جوك؟
- But... - Did the rumor go around?
- لكن... - هل انتشرت الإشاعة؟
- Yes. - The rumor about Sang Gook...
- نعم. - الشائعات حول سانغ جوك ...
circulated.
تعميمها.
Back then, Bong Sun was in her prime,
في ذلك الوقت، كانت بونغ صن في ريعان شبابها،
- and took good care of her juniors. - True.
- واهتمت بصغارها جيدًا. - حقيقي.
- Guys like Lee Won Goo... - Yes?
- رجال مثل Lee Won Goo... - نعم؟
and I liked her.
وقد أحببتها.
That's right. We were interested in her.
هذا صحيح. كنا مهتمين بها.
- Did you actually like her? - Back then,
- هل أعجبتك فعلا؟ - في ذلك الوقت،
- comedians who were pure, - I saw her as a woman.
- الكوميديين الذين كانوا طاهرين - رأيتها امرأة.
not witty and playful,
ليس ذكيًا ومرحًا ،
- liked me. - I get it.
- أعجبني. - أحصل عليه.
- Bong Sun. - Guys who were naive.
- بونج صن. - الرجال الذين كانوا ساذجين.
Sang Gook just confessed that...
سانغ غوك اعترف للتو بذلك...
- Yes? - he was interested in you...
- نعم؟ - لقد كان مهتماً بك..
as a girl.
كفتاة.
Did you not know?
هل لم تعلم؟
- Why didn't you accept him? - Why not?
- لماذا لم تقبليه؟ - ولم لا؟
Honestly, I also...
وبصراحة أنا أيضا...
(Did she also like me?)
(هل كانت تحبني أيضًا؟)
I also have my ideal type.
لدي أيضًا نوعي المثالي.
(Looking far away)
(ينظر بعيدا)
Back then, I acted as if I heard nothing.
في ذلك الوقت، تصرفت وكأنني لم أسمع شيئًا.
- Really? - You knew?
- حقًا؟ - هل تعلم؟
I may have heard about it.
ربما سمعت عن ذلك.
What do you think about me now?
ما رأيك بي الآن؟
You're more than good enough.
أنت أكثر من جيد بما فيه الكفاية.
(Look at these two.)
(انظر إلى هذين.)
- What's the age difference? - Was it 2 or 3?
- ما هو فارق السن؟ - هل كان 2 أو 3؟
- How old are you? - I was born in 1983.
- كم عمرك؟ - أنا من مواليد 1983.
I see. I was born in 1980.
أرى. لقد ولدت في عام 1980.
- In 1980? - It's a 3-year gap.
- في عام 1980؟ - إنها فجوة لمدة 3 سنوات.
You've become prettier since the last time I saw you ages ago.
لقد أصبحت أجمل منذ آخر مرة رأيتك فيها منذ زمن طويل.
Really?
حقًا؟
(Now, that's a man.)
(الآن، هذا رجل).
He's a real man.
إنه رجل حقيقي.
But you’ve really become prettier than before, Bong Sun.
لكنك أصبحت أجمل من ذي قبل يا بونج صن.
Sang Gook, you're really...
سانغ جوك، أنت حقًا...
(Sang Gook, you're really...)
(سانغ جوك، أنت حقًا...)
You're really the same.
أنت حقا نفس الشيء.
- Sang Gook's ears are beet red. - He hasn't changed.
- آذان سانغ جوك حمراء اللون. - لم يتغير.
- Bong Sun, he's unchanging. - Come on.
- بونج صن، إنه لا يتغير. - تعال.
- Honestly, since I'm still single, - No good?
- بصراحة، بما أنني مازلت أعزباً - ليس جيداً؟
my friends try to set me up with guys.
يحاول أصدقائي أن يضعوني مع الرجال.
Not long ago, on my personal YouTube channel,
منذ وقت ليس ببعيد، على قناتي الشخصية على اليوتيوب،
Yoo Min Sang and I...
يو مين سانغ وأنا...
- Right. - did a skit of us...
- يمين. - عملت مسرحية هزلية منا ...
- becoming a couple. - I remember.
- أن تصبح زوجين. - أتذكر.
Some comments said,
وقالت بعض التعليقات
"Now that there are articles, just get married."
"الآن بعد أن أصبح هناك مقالات، فقط تزوج."
"I'm a total stranger, but I would love to congratulate you."
"أنا غريب تمامًا، لكني أود أن أهنئك."
"May I send congratulatory money?"
"هل يمكنني إرسال أموال التهنئة؟"
Isn't it the same with Sang Gook?
أليس الأمر نفسه مع سانغ جوك؟
- Min Sang is a big no. - Why?
- مين سانغ هو لا كبير. - لماذا؟
Even if you two get married, it won't last long.
حتى لو تزوجتما، فلن يدوم الأمر طويلاً.
- How come? - Is that why...
- كيف ذلك؟ - هل هذا هو السبب...
- Why? - Tell us the reason.
- لماذا؟ - أخبرنا السبب.
- He's unhealthy. - What?
- إنه غير صحي. - ماذا؟
The marriage will end very soon.
وسوف ينتهي الزواج قريبا جدا.
- It's not okay. - Does that mean he's sick?
- لا بأس. -هل هذا يعني أنه مريض؟
Is it okay to expose...
هل يصح فضح...
- such a private matter? - He's unhealthy.
- مثل هذه المسألة الخاصة؟ - إنه غير صحي.
I'm much better than Min Sang.
أنا أفضل بكثير من مين سانغ.
- Sang Gook, do you honestly want... - Yes?
- سانغ جوك، هل تريد بصراحة... - نعم؟
to captivate me as a man?
لتأسرني كرجل؟
I'll think about it.
سأفكر في الأمر.
What?
ماذا؟
This conversation was meaningless.
وكانت هذه المحادثة لا معنى لها.
- Right? - Doesn't he have a girlfriend?
- يمين؟ - أليس لديه صديقة؟
No, I swear I don't.
لا، أقسم أنني لا أفعل ذلك.
You're red up to here.
أنت أحمر حتى هنا.
But trust me when I say you've always been charming.
لكن ثق بي عندما أقول أنك كنت دائمًا ساحرًا.
He's dead serious.
إنه جاد جدًا.
- Look at how red he is. - Right?
- انظر إلى مدى احمراره. - يمين؟
She's very charming.
إنها ساحرة للغاية.
- Now then, I think we've warmed up. - Yes.
- الآن بعد ذلك، أعتقد أننا استعدنا. - نعم.
We will now begin with the Joke Battle.
سنبدأ الآن مع معركة النكتة.
Out of the three battles, the team to get the highest score...
من بين المعارك الثلاث، الفريق الذي يحصل على أعلى الدرجات...
will rise to the Joke King throne.
سوف يرتقي إلى عرش ملك النكتة.
Here's the first battle.
ها هي المعركة الأولى.
We will be putting a price on your wit and brilliant jokes.
سنضع سعرًا على ذكائك ونكاتك الرائعة.
It's the so-called Joke Auction. Let's begin.
إنه ما يسمى بمزاد النكتة. لنبدأ.
(Joke Battle Round 1: Joke Auction)
(جولة معركة النكتة 1: مزاد النكتة)
After looking at the photo on the screen,
بعد النظر إلى الصورة على الشاشة،
discuss with your teammate...
ناقش مع زميلك في الفريق...
and come up with a funny title for it.
وتوصل إلى عنوان مضحك لها.
Throw in a price for the best title...
ضع سعرًا للحصول على أفضل عنوان..
in each round.
في كل جولة.
The team to earn the most money...
الفريق الذي حصل على أكبر قدر من المال..
will win the Joke Auction.
سيفوز بمزاد النكتة.
Is everyone ready?
هل الجميع جاهز؟
- Yes.
- نعم. - نعم.
Here's the first photo.
ها هي الصورة الأولى.
Gosh.
يا إلهي.
(Joke Auction: First Question)
(مزاد النكتة: السؤال الأول)
(Come up with a title for this photo.)
(اختر عنوانًا لهذه الصورة.)
- What's that? Jang Hoon... - Gosh, isn't it...
- ما هذا؟ جانغ هون... - يا إلهي، أليس كذلك...
- That... - I have eight in mind.
- هذا... - لدي ثمانية في الاعتبار.
- Nice. Let's write one down. - Really?
- لطيف - جيد. دعونا نكتب واحدة. - حقًا؟
- Give us one. - Let's go, Jae Youl.
- أعطنا واحدة. - دعنا نذهب، جاي يول.
- Give us one, please. -Write down...
- أعطنا واحدة من فضلك. -اكتب...
the title for each photo.
العنوان لكل صورة.
(Glancing)
(نظرة خاطفة)
- Nice. - Really?
- لطيف - جيد. - حقًا؟
- Give us one. - Let's go, Jae Youl.
- أعطنا واحدة. - دعنا نذهب، جاي يول.
(Getting emotional)
(تصبح عاطفية)
(The title is a tear-jerker.)
(العنوان هو المسيل للدموع.)
That's Anycall.
هذا Anycall.
- Anycall? - Yes. Down there.
- أي مكالمة؟ - نعم. هناك.
- Seo Jang Hoon as the model, - I had a feeling...
- سيو جانج هون كعارض أزياء - كان لدي شعور...
- not Lee Hyo Ri? - it'd be my photo.
- ليس لي هيو ري؟ - ستكون صورتي.
Really?
حقًا؟
(The teammate's horrible joke)
(نكتة زميله الرهيبة)
This is bad.
هذا سيء.
That must be years ago.
يجب أن يكون ذلك منذ سنوات.
- How about it? - Nice.
- ماذا عن ذلك؟ - لطيف - جيد.
Go, Jae Youl.
اذهب، جاي يول.
- All teams must write one down. - Okay.
- يجب على جميع الفرق كتابة واحدة. - تمام.
(Being mindful)
(أن نكون واعيين)
- We'll present it in order. - One.
- سوف نقدمها بالترتيب. - واحد.
- Firstly, Team Hey. - Jang Hoon?
- أولا، فريق يا. - جانغ هون؟
- Okay. - Why?
- تمام. - لماذا؟
What's your title?
ما هو عنوانك؟
"Divorce, Yes or No."
"الطلاق، نعم أم لا".
(Divorce, Yes or No)
(الطلاق نعم أم لا)
You see that foreigner next to him?
هل ترى ذلك الأجنبي بجانبه؟
"Divorce, Yes or No."
"الطلاق، نعم أم لا".
(Divorce, Yes or No)
(الطلاق نعم أم لا)
You see that foreigner...
ترى هذا الأجنبي..
- next to him? - That guy?
- بجانبه؟ - ذلك الرجل؟
- He's right. - Now that I look at it...
- إنه على حق. - والآن بعد أن نظرت إليه..
"Divorce, Yes or No."
"الطلاق، نعم أم لا".
- Jang Hoon. - Yes.
- جانج هون. - نعم.
The foreigner is saying "no."
الأجنبي يقول "لا".
But Jang Hoon is saying "yes."
لكن جانغ هون يقول "نعم".
How did you two make such hand signs?
كيف قمتما بعمل مثل هذه الإشارات اليدوية؟
- All right, Jae Youl's turn. - No.
- حسنًا، دور جاي يول. - لا.
Team Rude Juniors. One...
فريق رود جونيورز. واحد...
- Ours is nothing about divorce. - What is it?
- أمرنا لا يتعلق بالطلاق. - ما هذا؟
- In 1, 2, 3.
- ما هذا؟ - في 1، 2، 3.
- "Move It! The Bouquet is Mine!" - "The Bouquet is Mine!"
- "حركها! الباقة ملكي!" - "الباقة لي!"
Jang Hoon is trying to get the bouquet.
يحاول جانغ هون الحصول على الباقة.
"Move! It's mine!"
"تحرك! إنها ملكي!"
- Jang Hoon getting the bouquet. - Now that's new.
- جانغ هون يحصل على الباقة. - الآن هذا جديد.
- "Yes or No" was... - Up next is Team Yeongdeungpo.
- "نعم أو لا" كانت... - التالي هو فريق Yeongdeungpo.
- Yeongdeungpo is... - Ours is weak.
- Yeongdeungpo هو... - بلدنا ضعيف.
Reveal it.
كشف ذلك.
"A Round of Applause!"
"جولة من التصفيق!"
- We're in first place. - Come on.
- نحن في المركز الأول. - تعال.
- You must...
- نحن في المركز الأول. - يجب عليك أن...
- It's a tough one. - understand the key to the photo.
- إنها صعبة. - فهم مفتاح الصورة.
- Next. - Jang Hoon.
- التالي. - جانج هون.
- "Armpit Hair Removal." - Kyung Hoon...
- "إزالة شعر الإبط". - كيونغ هون...
- Nice one. - It feels nice.
- هذا لطيف. - إنه شعور لطيف.
- "Armpit Hair Removal" failed. - Mini Mini.
- فشل "إزالة شعر الإبط". - ميني ميني .
Seon Min. One,
سيون مين. واحد،
- Is it in vowels? - two, three.
- هل هو في حروف العلة؟ - اثنان، ثلاثة.
"Go In, Got It?"
"ادخل، فهمت؟"
(Go In, Got It?)
(ادخل، فهمت؟)
- Come on. - Really?
- تعال. - حقًا؟
- Mini Mini. - That's foul play.
- ميني ميني . - هذا اللعب الخبيث.
- Lame.
- هذا اللعب الخبيث. - عاجِز.
- Hey. - "Go In, Got It?"
- يا. - "ادخل، فهمت؟"
You should emphasize the photo.
يجب عليك التأكيد على الصورة.
That's weird.
هذا غريب.
Now then, Team Sun Bong Jang.
الآن بعد ذلك، فريق صن بونج جانج.
"It Hurts."
"إنه مؤلم."
That doesn't suit his expression.
هذا لا يناسب تعبيره.
- But that was... - What happened?
- ولكن ذلك كان... - ماذا حدث؟
when I was in pain.
عندما كنت أتألم.
- It must've really hurt. - "It Hurts."
- يجب أن لقد كان مؤلما حقا. - "إنه مؤلم."
I was about to shoot...
كنت على وشك إطلاق النار...
- when someone hit my hand. - You were hit?
- عندما ضرب شخص ما يدي. - لقد ضربت؟
I was actually in pain.
كنت في الواقع أتألم.
- But that... - The player hit your hand...
- لكن هذا... - اللاعب ضرب يدك...
when he was supposed to hit...
عندما كان من المفترض أن يضرب...
- the ball. - Yes.
- الكرة. - نعم.
- Now then, - Auction for Rude Juniors.
- الآن، - مزاد لـ "رود جونيورز".
it's time to auction the titles.
حان الوقت لبيع العناوين بالمزاد.
You can't place a bid on your own work.
لا يمكنك تقديم عرض على عملك الخاص.
Excluding your own team, write the title you liked the most,
باستثناء فريقك الخاص، اكتب العنوان الذي أعجبك أكثر،
- and your price. - That's...
- والسعر الخاص بك. - هذا...
It's a bit sad for Hey.
إنه أمر محزن بعض الشيء بالنسبة لـ Hey.
- It was fun. - Can we do that?
- كان ممتعا. - هل يمكننا أن نفعل ذلك؟
- But it's still... - Can we adjust it?
- لكنه لا يزال... - هل يمكننا تعديله؟
- It was inconsiderate. - Yes.
- لقد كان غير مدروس. - نعم.
- The icon of divorce. - Don't say it like that.
- أيقونة الطلاق . - لا تقل ذلك من هذا القبيل.
- You're right. - Come on.
- أنت على حق. - تعال.
You should have gone with remarriage.
كان يجب أن تذهب مع الزواج مرة أخرى.
I'm sorry, but...
أنا آسف، ولكن...
- Stop picking on Jang Hoon. - I'm sorry, but...
- توقف عن مضايقة جانغ هون. - أنا آسف، ولكن...
Are you in any position to say that?
هل أنت في وضع يسمح لك بقول ذلك؟
What do you mean?
ماذا تقصد؟
- The most important thing is... - You should search on YouTube.
- أهم شيء هو... - لازم تبحث في اليوتيوب.
There's an hour-long video of you...
يوجد فيديو لك مدته ساعة...
- making fun of me on that. - An hour?
- يسخر مني على ذلك. - ساعة؟
Yes. It's an hour long.
نعم. إنها ساعة طويلة.
- Just go with it. - Yes.
- فقط اذهب معها. - نعم.
- Encore. - Let's see which works you're on,
- الظهور. - دعونا نرى ما هي الأعمال التي تقوم بها،
- starting from Sun Bong Jang. - Okay.
- البدء من صن بونج جانج. - تمام.
- How much is it? - For Hey, 40 dollars.
- كم سعره؟ - ل مهلا، 40 دولارا.
- Hey, at 40 dollars? - What?
- مهلا، في 40 دولارا؟ - ماذا؟
We wanted to go all in on Hey as well,
أردنا أن ندخل في كل شيء على Hey أيضًا،
but seeing them mock Jang Hoon was really heartbreaking for me.
لكن رؤيتهم وهم يسخرون من جانغ هون كان أمرًا مفجعًا حقًا بالنسبة لي.
So, 20 dollars.
إذن 20 دولارًا.
You're not at a place to say that.
أنت لست في مكان لتقول ذلك.
- So, I say 20 dollars. - It's 20 dollars.
- لذلك، أقول 20 دولارا. - إنها 20 دولارًا.
We will place a bid for Mini Mini's "Go In, Got it?"
سنقدم عرضًا لشراء سيارة Mini Mini "Go In، Got it؟"
We will bid 10 dollars for Hey.
سنعرض 10 دولارات مقابل Hey.
We will bid 50 dollars for Mini Mini.
سنعرض 50 دولارًا مقابل Mini Mini.
- Wait, then it's going up. - Then it's Mini Mini.
- انتظر، ثم انها ترتفع. - ثم إنها ميني ميني.
- It's Mini Mini. - Team Mini Mini.
- إنها ميني ميني. - تيم ميني ميني.
For Hey, 40 dollars.
مهلا، 40 دولارا.
(Sold, Hey, 110 dollars)
(تم البيع يا 110 دولار)
It's 40 dollars for Hey.
إنها 40 دولارًا لـ Hey.
Hey is sold for 110 dollars.
يا يباع ل 110 دولارا.
(Hey is sold for a total of 110 dollars.)
(يتم بيعها بمبلغ إجمالي قدره 110 دولارات.)
- We were able to defend it. - We let them win.
- كنا قادرين على الدفاع عنه. - نسمح لهم بالفوز.
They deserved it.
لقد استحقوا ذلك.
- They did well. - It's deserved.
- لقد قاموا بعمل جيد. - إنه يستحق.
Let's see the next picture.
دعونا نرى الصورة التالية.
(Come up with a title for this photo.)
(اختر عنوانًا لهذه الصورة.)
- What? - This is...
- ماذا؟ - هذا هو...
Come on.
تعال.
- Can this really be aired?
- هذا... - هل يمكن بث هذا حقا؟
Why did it have to be this picture, out of all of them?
لماذا يجب أن تكون هذه الصورة، من بين كل منهم؟
"I'm free today."
"أنا حر اليوم."
That's so bad.
هذا سيء للغاية.
(Laughing)
(يضحك)
(Once again, Jae Youl shows no restraint.)
(مرة أخرى، جاي يول لا يظهر أي ضبط للنفس.)
- Okay. - Do you like it?
- تمام. - هل أحببت ذلك؟
Yes. The next sentence... Okay.
نعم. الجملة التالية...حسنا.
The book...
الكتاب...
The title of the book is "Summer - Marriage."
عنوان الكتاب هو "الصيف - الزواج".
It's nice to get married in the summer.
من الجميل أن نتزوج في الصيف.
(Gulping)
(البلع)
(I must make it funny this time.)
(يجب أن أجعل الأمر مضحكا هذه المرة.)
The book...
الكتاب...
Whoever wants to go first may go first.
من يريد أن يذهب أولاً يمكنه أن يذهب أولاً.
Okay, good job.
حسنا، عمل جيد.
- Team Rude Juniors.
- فريق رود جونيورز . - فريق رود جونيورز .
- I will go. - Yes.
- سأذهب. - نعم.
"The Smartest Monkey in the Group."
"أذكى قرد في المجموعة."
- "Monkey?" - Monkey.
- "قرد؟" - قرد.
He's not wearing anything,
إنه لا يرتدي أي شيء،
- so he looks like a monkey. - I see it.
- فهو يشبه القرد. - أرى ذلك.
- But he looks really smart. - Yes.
- لكنه يبدو ذكيا حقا. - نعم.
- I see it. - You look really smart.
- أرى ذلك. - تبدو ذكيا حقا.
- That's good. - An intellectual monkey.
- هذا جيد. - قرد فكري.
- I see it. - I know.
- أرى ذلك. - أنا أعرف.
That's good.
هذا جيد.
- Sun Bong Jang. - There's more.
- صن بونج جانج. - هناك المزيد.
- I'll keep it simple.
- صن بونج جانج. - سأبقي الأمر بسيطا.
- Simple. - Yes.
- بسيط. - نعم.
- "Pathetic." - What is that?
- "مثير للشفقة." - ما هذا؟
- That's funny. - That's good.
- هذا مضحك. - هذا جيد.
- It hits you instantly. - You're right.
- ويضربك على الفور. - أنت على حق.
- Is there anything better?
- هل هناك أي شيء أفضل؟ - أنت على حق.
- We all know it. - That's good. I love it.
- كلنا نعرف ذلك. - هذا جيد. أنا أحبه.
That's not trying to be funny.
هذا لا يحاول أن يكون مضحكا.
- It's just what you wanted to say. - Come on.
- هذا فقط ما أردت أن تقوله. - تعال.
- I just made the title. - What could be better?
- لقد صنعت العنوان للتو. - ماذا يمكن أن يكون أفضل؟
- Let's go, Yeongdeungpo. - That's so nice.
- دعنا نذهب، يونجديونجبو. - هذا لطيف جدا.
This is hard.
هذا صعب.
"Do you think I have nipples or not?"
"هل تعتقد أن لدي حلمات أم لا؟"
- You didn't pull it off. - He must not...
- أنت لم تسحبه. - لا يجب عليه...
- by the looks of it. - After being with me...
- من مظهره. - بعد أن كنت معي..
Why are you so tense today, Beom?
لماذا أنت متوتر جدًا اليوم يا بيوم؟
Let me file one tip-off.
اسمحوا لي أن أقدم بلاغًا واحدًا.
He's not giving me any ideas,
إنه لا يعطيني أي أفكار،
but only telling me which hotel that was in Singapore.
ولكن أخبرني فقط عن الفندق الذي كان في سنغافورة.
It's not letting me come up with any ideas.
إنه لا يسمح لي بالتوصل إلى أي أفكار.
Let's say it's the Andaz Hotel in Singapore.
لنفترض أنه فندق Andaz في سنغافورة.
"The Smartest Monkey in the Group."
"أذكى قرد في المجموعة."
What am I supposed to do?
ماذا يفترض بي أن أفعل؟
- I really didn't read. - That's cute.
- أنا حقا لم أقرأ. - هذا لطيف.
I think Beom is feeling down after Seon Min's big one.
أعتقد أن بيوم يشعر بالإحباط بعد حادثة Seon Min الكبيرة.
- He's tense. - Yes.
- إنه متوتر. - نعم.
He looks sad.
يبدو حزينا.
Seon Min was funny.
كان سيون مين مضحكا.
I didn't expect it to be funny.
لم أكن أتوقع أن يكون الأمر مضحكا.
Seon Min wasn't on Beom's rival list.
لم يكن Seon Min ضمن قائمة منافسي Beom.
He told him that he would help him in the beginning.
أخبره أنه سيساعده في البداية.
Beom said that...
وقال بيوم...
- "I will help you out." - he would help out.
- "سوف أساعدك." - سوف يساعد.
I said, "I will help you out."
فقلت: "سوف أساعدك".
- Help me out. - Now, Head Geun.
- ساعدني. - الآن، رئيس جيون.
Help me out, Seon Min.
ساعدني، سيون مين.
- We need to move on. - Should we help?
- نحن بحاجة للمضي قدما. - هل يجب أن نساعد؟
- Head Geun. - Ours is...
- رئيس جيون. - لنا هو...
- similar to Rude Juniors. - Okay.
- على غرار رود جونيورز. - تمام.
It's like an inspiration from nature.
انها مثل الإلهام من الطبيعة.
"Primitive Man."
"الرجل البدائي."
- What? - "Primitive Man."
- ماذا؟ - "الرجل البدائي."
A poetic primitive man.
رجل بدائي شاعري.
- The last... - That's nice.
- الأخير... - هذا جميل.
The anticipated one, Mini Mini.
المنتظر، ميني ميني.
Let's go, Seon Min. In 3, 2, 1.
دعنا نذهب، سيون مين. في 3، 2، 1.
Go.
يذهب.
"I can't think of a title."
"لا أستطيع التفكير في عنوان."
- Come on. - No.
- تعال. - لا.
- It was weak.
- تعال. - كان ضعيفا.
Still, you should have done something.
ومع ذلك، كان ينبغي عليك أن تفعل شيئًا ما.
I'm sorry, but Bong Sun said,
أنا آسف، ولكن بونج صن قال،
"It hasn't even been 30 minutes,"
"لم تمر حتى 30 دقيقة"
"and it's almost up for him."
"والأمر متروك له تقريبًا."
- He's starting to bottom out. - It's coming to an end.
- لقد بدأ في الانخفاض. - إنها تقترب من نهايتها.
We've been shooting for an hour, and his skills are running out.
لقد كنا نطلق النار لمدة ساعة، ومهاراته تنفد.
That's too much.
هذا كثير جدًا.
It might be an hour's worth of shooting,
قد يستغرق الأمر ساعة من التصوير،
but it's five minutes on the show.
لكنها خمس دقائق على العرض.
- He ran out in five minutes. - What a fleeting star!
- نفد في خمس دقائق. - يا له من نجم عابر!
It's the shortest I've seen during my broadcasting career.
إنه أقصر ما رأيته خلال مسيرتي الإذاعية.
- Running out in five minutes? - He's like a shooting star.
- نفاد في خمس دقائق؟ - إنه مثل نجم الرماية.
A legendary shooting star.
نجم الرماية الأسطوري.
- He's the Sugar Man. - Gosh.
- إنه الرجل السكر. - يا إلهي.
That's so funny.
هذا مضحك جدا.
Since Seon Min seems to be running out,
بما أن Seon Min يبدو أنها تنفد،
- Beom is loving it. - Look at him.
- بيوم يحبها. - أنظر إليه.
Yes.
نعم.
- He likes it. -Hey.
- يحب ذلك. -يا.
I will help out.
سوف أساعد.
Are you already letting your guard down?
هل تخليت عن حذرك بالفعل؟
- Seon Min. - I’ll stay on edge.
- سيون مين. - سأبقى على الحافة.
His glare is different.
وهجه مختلف.
Please write the title you liked the most...
من فضلك أكتب العنوان الذي أعجبك أكثر...
and the amount.
والمبلغ.
Can we add some more to the 50 dollars?
هل يمكننا إضافة المزيد إلى الـ 50 دولارًا؟
No. It has to be under 50 dollars.
لا، يجب أن يكون أقل من 50 دولارًا.
- It was neck and neck. - They were good.
- كان العنق والرقبة. - لقد كانوا جيدين.
How much is it, Team Hey?
كم المبلغ يا فريق هاي؟
For Sun Bong Jang, 50 dollars.
لسون بونج جانج 50 دولارًا.
- That's was nice. - Five dollars for Sun Bong Jang.
- لقد كان ذلك لطيفاً. - خمسة دولارات لسون بونج جانج.
Five dollars.
خمسة دولارات.
- And Team Sun Bong Jang? - Come on, use more money.
- وفريق صن بونج جانج؟ - هيا، استخدم المزيد من المال.
- Sun Bong Jang. - How much did you give?
- صن بونج جانج. - كم أعطيت؟
Three dollars for Rude Juniors.
ثلاثة دولارات لـ "رود جونيورز".
- See? You're not different. - Come on.
- يرى؟ أنت لست مختلفا. - تعال.
What about you?
ماذا عنك؟
The party involved was offended,
وقد أساء الطرف المعني،
so two cents for Sun Bong Jang.
إذن سنتان لسون بونج جانج.
- Two cents? - He's offended.
- سنتان؟ - لقد أساء.
Ten dollars for Sun Bong Jang.
عشرة دولارات لـ(سون بونج جانج).
We bid 50 dollars for Sun Bong Jang.
لقد عرضنا 50 دولارًا مقابل Sun Bong Jang.
(Sold, Sun Bong Jang, 115.02 dollars)
(تم بيعه، صن بونج جانج، 115.02 دولار)
Sun Bong Jang is sold...
تم بيع سون بونج جانج...
- for 115.02 dollars. - "Pathetic."
- مقابل 115.02 دولار. - "مثير للشفقة."
- That was the answer. - That was funny, Bong Sun.
- كان هذا هو الجواب. - كان ذلك مضحكا، بونج صن.
- That was great. - Congratulations.
- ًكان كبيرا. - مبروك.
- That was the answer. - Yes.
- كان هذا هو الجواب. - نعم.
Let's move on to the next picture.
دعنا ننتقل إلى الصورة التالية.
(Come up with a title for this photo.)
(اختر عنوانًا لهذه الصورة.)
- Gosh. - That's hard.
- يا إلهي. - هذا صعب.
He's a master at skits, so it's hard.
إنه محترف في التمثيليات، لذا فالأمر صعب.
(The hardest level)
(المستوى الأصعب)
Soo Geun.
سو جيون.
(Glancing)
(نظرة خاطفة)
(The one-hit wonder faces another hurdle.)
(العجب الذي حقق ضربة واحدة يواجه عقبة أخرى.)
Gosh...
يا إلهي...
(Will he be able to make a grand comeback?)
(هل سيكون قادرًا على العودة الكبرى؟)
We will just go first.
سنذهب أولاً.
- You can go first. - We will do it.
- يمكنك الذهاب أولا. - سنفعل ذلك.
This just came to my mind.
هذا جاء إلى ذهني للتو.
One, two, three.
واحد اثنين ثلاثة.
- "Adulterer."
- "الزنا". - "الزنا".
It's really...
انها حقا...
He's a complete mess.
انه فوضى كاملة.
It's so...
إنه هكذا...
(There’s something shady behind his looks.)
(هناك شيء مشبوه وراء نظراته.)
- I saw it in dramas. - You're right.
- رأيت ذلك في الأعمال الدرامية. - أنت على حق.
It looks like I'm in a hurry to leave.
يبدو أنني في عجلة من أمري للمغادرة.
Yes, but you even took all your clothes.
نعم، ولكنك حتى أخذت كل ملابسك.
Kyung Hoon wrote something as soon as he saw it.
كتب كيونغ هون شيئا بمجرد رؤيته.
- Head Geun. - Yes.
- رئيس جيون. - نعم.
Our answer is...
جوابنا هو...
It's not us, it's you.
هذا ليس نحن، بل أنت.
"All In."
"الكل في."
(The devastating result of going all in)
(النتيجة المدمرة لدخول كل شيء)
- Gosh. - Is that it?
- يا إلهي. - هل هذا هو؟
Don't laugh, Soo Geun.
لا تضحك، سو جيون.
You must not laugh yet.
يجب أن لا تضحك بعد.
Sang Gook.
الجوك.
(This man cannot afford to laugh.)
(هذا الرجل لا يستطيع أن يضحك.)
- Sang Gook. - Yes?
- سانغ جوك. - نعم؟
Team Hey.
فريق يا.
"Exhibit Number One of Kang Ho Dong's..."
"المعرض رقم واحد من أعمال كانغ هو دونغ..."
"Assault Allegations."
"مزاعم الاعتداء".
There are so many pieces of evidence for that.
هناك الكثير من الأدلة على ذلك.
There are many things that are too harsh to be aired on television.
هناك أشياء كثيرة قاسية جدًا بحيث لا يمكن بثها على شاشة التلفزيون.
Those things you lightly mention make it seem true.
تلك الأشياء التي ذكرتها باستخفاف تجعل الأمر يبدو صحيحًا.
These things are okay,
هذه الأشياء على ما يرام،
but the way you mention them on the side...
لكن الطريقة التي ذكرتهم بها على الجانب...
- make people think it is true. - Sun Bong Jang.
- جعل الناس يعتقدون أن هذا صحيح. - صن بونج جانج.
- We will go next. - Okay.
- سنذهب بعد ذلك. - تمام.
- We will go. - Two, three.
- سوف نذهب. - اثنان، ثلاثة.
"Why did you undress me?"
"لماذا خلعت ملابسي؟"
- What? - They did it first.
- ماذا؟ - لقد فعلوا ذلك أولا.
Why are you erasing it?
لماذا تقوم بمسحها؟
I need to erase it.
أحتاج إلى محوها.
Come on, wait.
هيا، انتظر.
- They did it first. - "Why did you undress me?"
- لقد فعلوا ذلك أولا. - "لماذا خلعت ملابسي؟"
- That's so funny. - Why did you?
- هذا مضحك جدا. - لماذا فعلت؟
- Yeongdeungpo.
- يونجديونجبو. - لماذا فعلت؟
"Can you scratch my back?"
"هل يمكنك خدش ظهري؟"
Come on.
تعال.
They did it first.
لقد فعلوا ذلك أولاً.
- Good job. - They used that.
- أحسنت. - لقد استخدموا ذلك.
- That's brutal. - "Why did you undress me?"
- هذا وحشي. - "لماذا خلعت ملابسي؟"
- You have no mercy at all. - Come on.
- ليس لديك رحمة على الإطلاق. - تعال.
- We have the original left. - Let’s go easy on Seon Min.
- لدينا اليسار الأصلي. - دعونا نتساهل مع سيون مين.
Seon Min won't end it there.
سيون مين لن ينهي الأمر عند هذا الحد.
"Why are you copying me?"
"لماذا تقلدني؟"
(Don't copy me.)
(لا تقلدني.)
- Now, choose the title you like, - It's going bland.
- الآن، اختر العنوان الذي يعجبك - سيكون الأمر لطيفًا.
It's a series.
إنها سلسلة.
and the amount for your bid.
ومبلغ العرض الخاص بك.
("Why did you undress me?" "Can you scratch my back?")
("لماذا خلعت ملابسي؟" "هل يمكنك خدش ظهري؟")
"Why are you copying me?"
"لماذا تقلدني؟"
- We will go. - You need to...
- سوف نذهب. - عليك أن...
- make it different. - Let's go.
- اجعلها مختلفة. - دعنا نذهب.
We will give Head Geun...
سوف نعطي الرئيس جيون...
- our bid of 50 dollars. - Thank you.
- عرضنا بقيمة 50 دولارًا. - شكرًا لك.
- A warm amount of 50 dollars. - Yes.
- مبلغ دافئ 50 دولار . - نعم.
I can't ruin myself,
لا أستطيع أن أدمر نفسي،
- so I will bid one cent. - A small amount.
- لذلك سأقدم سنتًا واحدًا. - كمية قليلة.
Two dollars for "All In."
دولاران مقابل "الكل في".
- Gosh. - You spent a lot.
- يا إلهي. - لقد قضيت الكثير.
For Rude Juniors, 25 dollars.
لـ Rude Juniors، 25 دولارًا.
(Rude Juniors, 25 dollars)
(رود جونيورز، 25 دولارًا)
Ten dollars for Rude Juniors.
عشرة دولارات لـ "رود جونيورز".
For Head Geun, 50 dollars.
لرئيس Geun، 50 دولارا.
- Head Geun? - Gosh.
- رئيس جيون؟ - يا إلهي.
"All In" is sold.
تم بيع "الكل في".
They're all putting in so much money.
كلهم يستثمرون الكثير من المال.
We don't have money, either.
ليس لدينا المال أيضاً.
(Title: "All In")
(العنوان: "الكل في")
Everyone, the last...
الجميع، الأخير..
- What? - This is the last question.
- ماذا؟ - هذا هو السؤال الأخير.
This is the last picture for the Joke Auction.
هذه هي الصورة الأخيرة لمزاد النكتة.
- Please show us. - The last one.
- من فضلك تبين لنا. - الأخير.
(Come up with a title for this photo.)
(اختر عنوانًا لهذه الصورة.)
(Gosh...)
(يا إلهي...)
I remember exactly what this scene was.
أتذكر بالضبط ما كان هذا المشهد.
(Sang Min looks desperate in this past.)
(يبدو سانغ مين يائسًا في هذا الماضي.)
Do you have anything for Seon Min?
هل لديك أي شيء لـ سيون مين؟
- Seon Min? - Seon Min.
- سيون مين؟ - سيون مين.
"Please help Seon Min recover."
"الرجاء مساعدة Seon Min على التعافي."
(He is still not in good condition.)
(وهو لا يزال ليس في حالة جيدة).
(He is not helping, either.)
(وهو لا يساعد أيضاً).
(On the other hand, Sang Gook gets to work instantly.)
(من ناحية أخرى، سيبدأ سانغ جوك العمل على الفور.)
- How is it? - Sang Gook, you're harsh.
- كيف هذا؟ - سانغ جوك، أنت قاس.
You are full of ambition.
أنت مليء بالطموح.
- Team Hey, please show us. - Let's try it.
- فريق يا، من فضلك تبين لنا. - دعونا نحاول ذلك.
"I hope it works out this time."
"آمل أن ينجح الأمر هذه المرة."
- Hey, erase it. - What?
- مهلا، امسحها. - ماذا؟
(Erase it!)
(امسحها!)
- We did that. - It's the same.
- لقد فعلنا ذلك. - إنه نفس الشيء.
- We wrote the same thing. - Erase it.
- لقد كتبنا نفس الشيء. - محوها.
He's full of ambition.
إنه مليء بالطموح.
- Please bear with him. - It felt like it.
- يرجى تحمله. - شعرت بذلك.
- We're ready. - Let's go, Yeongdeungpo.
- نحن جاهزون. - دعنا نذهب، يونجديونجبو.
"Please make Yeong Cheol leave the show."
"من فضلك اجعل يونج تشيول يغادر العرض."
(I'm praying...)
(أنا أصلي...)
That's not bad. That was good.
هذا ليس سيئا. كان ذلك جيدًا.
Let's compete.
دعونا نتنافس.
Let's see who is last.
دعونا نرى من هو الأخير.
We were nice with it.
لقد كنا لطيفين معها.
- Please show us. - "I hope Jang Hoon could remarry."
- من فضلك تبين لنا. - "آمل أن يتزوج جانغ هون مرة أخرى."
- That's heartwarming. - That's nice.
- وهذا يثلج الصدر. - هذا لطيف.
- That's funny.
- هذا مضحك. - هذا لطيف.
- They were always a pair. - That's very warm.
- لقد كانا دائمًا زوجًا. - هذا دافئ جدا.
You can tell from his face...
يمكنك معرفة ذلك من وجهه..
that it was when he was having a hard time before.
أنه كان عندما كان يمر بوقت عصيب من قبل.
"Please stop calling me."
"من فضلك توقف عن الاتصال بي."
- All right. - "Stop the constant calls."
- حسنًا. - "أوقف المكالمات المستمرة."
- Head Geun. - I remember that time.
- رئيس جيون. - أتذكر ذلك الوقت.
Sang Min would have thought,
كان "سانغ مين" يعتقد،
"Thank you for getting me through today safely."
"شكرًا لك على اجتياز اليوم بأمان."
That's true.
هذا صحيح.
- It's hard. - Everyone. It's finally...
- إنه صعب. - الجميع. انها أخيرا...
- It's Seon Min! - today's main guest.
- إنها سيون مين! - الضيف الرئيسي اليوم.
Finally!
أخيراً!
The best of the first half of 2026.
الأفضل في النصف الأول من عام 2026.
He's crying.
إنه يبكي.
The best-ever fleeting star.
أفضل نجم عابر على الإطلاق.
"I'm Seon Min."
"أنا سيون مين."
"I'm Lee Seon Min."
"أنا لي سيون مين."
- Revealing in one, two, - Two, three!
- الكشف في واحد، اثنان، - اثنان، ثلاثة!
- Revealing in one, two, three! - Two, three!
- الكشف في واحد، اثنان، ثلاثة! - اثنان، ثلاثة!
"I only need to pay back one million dollars now."
"أنا فقط بحاجة إلى سداد مليون دولار الآن."
That's...
هذا...
- People here are so cruel. - He's stubborn.
- الناس هنا قساة جدا. - إنه عنيد.
- They turn away from him like this. - He doesn't look at him.
- يبتعدون عنه هكذا. - ولا ينظر إليه.
The best-ever fleeting star.
أفضل نجم عابر على الإطلاق.
I pulled up the ratings to the first place in 2025,
ورفعت التصنيفات إلى المركز الأول في عام 2025،
but Seon Min ruined everything.
لكن سيون مين دمر كل شيء.
I came here to bring things up in 2026.
لقد جئت إلى هنا لطرح الأمور في عام 2026.
- It's all ruined. - They're...
- لقد دمر كل شيء. - إنهم...
Please write the title you like and the amount.
يرجى كتابة العنوان الذي تريد والمبلغ.
- Isn't this 1.5 cents? - You wrote it without focusing.
- أليس هذا 1.5 سنتا؟ - لقد كتبتها دون التركيز.
- We can't get it. - It looks funny.
- لا نستطيع الحصول عليه. - يبدو مضحكا.
- This one... - Don't be greedy.
- هذا... - لا تكن جشعاً.
Let's go. Team Hey.
دعنا نذهب. فريق يا.
We also hope Jang Hoon could remarry.
ونأمل أيضًا أن يتمكن جانغ هون من الزواج مرة أخرى.
We bid 50 dollars on Rude Juniors.
نحن نعرض 50 دولارًا على Rude Juniors.
It's going. Fifty dollars on Rude Juniors.
انها تسير. خمسون دولارًا على "رود جونيورز".
With our wishes.
مع أمنياتنا.
We also...
نحن أيضا...
placed our hopes along with the production crew's hopes.
وضعنا آمالنا جنبًا إلى جنب مع آمال طاقم الإنتاج.
- Seriously. - We bid 50 dollars on Yeongdeungpo.
- بجد. - نحن نعرض 50 دولارًا على Yeongdeungpo.
- Fifty dollars on them. - We bid money on Yeongdeungpo.
- خمسون دولاراً عليهم. - نحن نعرض المال على Yeongdeungpo.
"Please make Yeong Cheol leave the show."
"من فضلك اجعل يونج تشيول يغادر العرض."
Rude Juniors. "I hope..."
جونيورز فظ. "آمل..."
"Jang Hoon could remarry." Ten dollars.
"يمكن لجانغ هون أن يتزوج مرة أخرى." عشرة دولارات.
Let's think of it as congratulatory money.
دعونا نفكر في الأمر على أنه أموال تهنئة.
Let's do that.
دعونا نفعل ذلك.
- It's congratulatory money. - Let's gather them.
- إنها أموال التهنئة. - دعونا نجمعهم.
- There's trouble. - What is it?
- هناك مشكلة. - ما هذا؟
We wrote "congratulatory money" as a funny point,
لقد كتبنا "مال التهنئة" كنقطة مضحكة،
but they just mentioned it.
لكنهم ذكروا ذلك للتو.
- It's the worst. - I guess today isn't my day.
- إنه الأسوأ. - أعتقد أن اليوم ليس يومي.
- Everyone thinks the same.
- إنه الأسوأ. - الجميع يفكر بنفس الطريقة.
- We were talking about it. - We all have...
- كنا نتحدث عن ذلك. - لدينا جميعا...
- similar thoughts. - They're similar.
- أفكار مماثلة. - إنهم متشابهون.
- You should be fast. - I wrote this hoping to be funny.
- يجب أن تكون سريعا. - كتبت هذا على أمل أن يكون مضحكا.
There should be around two comedians.
ينبغي أن يكون هناك حوالي اثنين من الكوميديين.
- We all thought the same way. - Right.
- لقد فكرنا جميعا بنفس الطريقة. - يمين.
We place ten dollars on Hey.
نضع عشرة دولارات على Hey.
Fifty dollars on Rude Juniors.
خمسون دولارًا على "رود جونيورز".
(Rude Juniors wins the bid.)
(رود جونيورز يفوز بالمزايدة.)
- Jang Hoon's congratulatory money. - Team Rude Juniors...
- أموال التهنئة لجانغ هون. - فريق رود جونيورز ...
wins the bid at 160 dollars.
يفوز بالمزايدة بمبلغ 160 دولارًا.
- It was the best ever. - Right.
- لقد كان الأفضل على الإطلاق. - يمين.
(I hope Jang Hoon could remarry.)
(آمل أن يتمكن جانغ هون من الزواج مرة أخرى.)
The winner of the Joke Auction, the first match,
الفائز في مزاد النكتة، المباراة الأولى،
is Team Rude Juniors...
هو فريق رود جونيورز...
who won the bid at the highest amount, 160 dollars!
الذي فاز بالمزايدة بأعلى مبلغ وهو 160 دولارًا!
(Team Rude Juniors wins the Joke Auction.)
(فريق Rude Juniors يفوز بمزاد المزحة.)
- We have to dance. - Right.
- علينا أن نرقص. - يمين.
Dance.
الرقص.
He dances well.
يرقص بشكل جيد.
(Congratulating himself on winning)
(تهنئة بالفوز)
(Moves caught somewhere between dance and slapstick)
(التحركات تقع في مكان ما بين الرقص والتهريج)
He's good at slapstick.
إنه جيد في التهريج.
Good. Come on!
جيد. تعال!
Okay. That was nice.
تمام. كان ذلك لطيفا.
It was the best.
كان الأفضل.
He's talented.
إنه موهوب.
It was really great.
لقد كان رائعا حقا.
I never imagined.
لم أتخيل أبدا.
- He dances well. - We've gotten addicted to "got it."
- يرقص بشكل جيد. - لقد أصبحنا مدمنين على "فهمت".
- So? - The lyric went "fire,"
- لذا؟ - أصبحت القصيدة الغنائية "النار"،
but I heard it like, "Fire, got it?"
لكني سمعتها مثل "النار، هل فهمت؟"
Fire, got it?
النار، فهمت؟
- Fire, got it? - I heard it like that.
- النار، فهمت؟ - سمعت ذلك من هذا القبيل.
It sounds like, "Got it?"
يبدو الأمر مثل "فهمت؟"
You pointed that out well.
لقد أشرت إلى ذلك جيدًا.
Will Lee Seon Min recover?
هل سيتعافى لي سيون مين؟
Seon Min and Jae Youl...
سيون مين وجاي يول...
are the last comedians of KBS and SBS recruited...
هم آخر الكوميديين الذين تم تجنيدهم في KBS وSBS...
- through the open casting. - Yes.
- من خلال الصب المفتوح . - نعم.
- KBS has resumed it now. - That's right.
- استأنفت قناة KBS عملها الآن. - هذا صحيح.
KBS and SBS. This has been an issue since before.
كي بي إس و إس بي إس. لقد كانت هذه مشكلة منذ قبل.
Which company is the foundational one?
ما هي الشركة التأسيسية؟
Come on.
تعال.
The foundation of sketch comedy.
أساس رسم الكوميديا.
- First of all... - To talk about the foundation,
- أولا... - للحديث عن المؤسسة،
KBS started it, and it spread out.
بدأت قناة KBS ذلك وانتشرت.
"Gag Concert" was widely loved by the public.
"حفلة Gag" كانت محبوبة على نطاق واسع من قبل الجمهور.
- "Gag Concert" was powerful. - Right.
- "حفلة الكمامة" كانت قوية. - يمين.
He was ranked second in the open casting of SBS.
حصل على المركز الثاني في اختيار الممثلين المفتوح لقناة SBS.
- I don't give him credit for that. - Why?
- أنا لا أعطيه الفضل في ذلك. - لماذا؟
For SBS,
بالنسبة لقناة SBS،
- the application rate... - That's right.
- معدل التقديم... - هذا صحيح.
- is low. - It's low.
- منخفض. - انها منخفضة.
- Does everyone go to KBS? - For example,
- هل يذهب الجميع إلى KBS؟ - على سبيل المثال،
500 people apply,
500 شخص يتقدمون
and they pick 40 to 50 people.
ويختارون من 40 إلى 50 شخصًا.
- As for us... - Several thousand.
- أما نحن... - عدة آلاف.
- Goodness. - Around 4,000 people apply...
- الخير. - حوالي 4000 شخص يتقدمون...
- Around 4,000 people apply, - They apply.
- يتقدم حوالي 4000 شخص - يتقدمون.
- and 8 to 10 people get picked. - Right.
- ويتم اختيار 8 إلى 10 أشخاص. - يمين.
So the person in 2nd place there would be in the 400th place here.
وبالتالي فإن الشخص الذي في المركز الثاني سيكون في المركز 400 هنا.
(He'd be in the 400th place.)
(سيكون في المركز 400).
- Let me add... - You should be fair.
- دعني أضيف... - يجب أن تكون عادلاً.
You shouldn't criticize...
لا ينبغي لك أن تنتقد...
- other TV networks. - That was a dangerous remark.
- شبكات التلفزيون الأخرى. - لقد كانت تلك ملاحظة خطيرة.
I'm not criticizing them.
أنا لا أنتقدهم.
- It's the truth. - Senior Dong!
- إنها الحقيقة. - كبار دونغ!
- We should just say they're great.
- إنها الحقيقة. - يجب أن نقول فقط أنهم رائعون.
Sang Gook is right.
سانغ جوك على حق.
I was accepted by SBS and KBS at the same time.
لقد تم قبولي من قبل SBS و KBS في نفس الوقت.
- I went to KBS instead of SBS. - Why?
- ذهبت إلى KBS بدلاً من SBS. - لماذا؟
When I took the SBS exam,
عندما أخذت امتحان SBS،
thirty-six people came, and thirty-five got accepted.
حضر ستة وثلاثون شخصًا، وتم قبول خمسة وثلاثين شخصًا.
- Come on. - Hey!
- تعال. - يا!
- But... - That's not true.
- ولكن... - هذا ليس صحيحا.
- I got accepted to both places. - Who's that one person...
- لقد تم قبولي في كلا المكانين. - من هو ذلك الشخص...؟
- who didn't get in? - Did you join KBS?
- ومن لم يدخل؟ - هل انضممت إلى KBS؟
- What I said was the truth. - Fleeting star.
- ما قلته كان الحقيقة. - نجم عابر.
On that matter, Jae Youl...
في هذا الشأن، جاي يول...
is the best when it comes to mocking.
هو الأفضل عندما يتعلق الأمر بالسخرية.
- I do it a lot these days. - The deity of mocking.
- أفعل ذلك كثيرًا هذه الأيام. - إله السخرية.
He's the deity of mocking.
إنه إله السخرية.
I mock as a profession.
أنا أسخر كمهنة.
- That's right. - I don't like mocking normally.
- هذا صحيح. - أنا لا أحب السخرية عادة.
- Really? - If you did, that'd be a problem.
- حقًا؟ - لو فعلت، ستكون هناك مشكلة.
He used to mock so well ever since he was in EBS.
لقد اعتاد أن يسخر جيدًا منذ أن كان في EBS.
That was my work.
كان هذا عملي.
You know Buong Cheol, the owl?
هل تعرف بونج تشيول، البومة؟
That was him. He was the owl.
كان هذا هو. وكان البومة.
-Really? - Buong Cheol's voice.
-حقًا؟ - صوت تشيول كامل.
Hello, It's Buong Cheol.
مرحبًا، أنا بونج تشيول.
I used to do that.
اعتدت أن أفعل ذلك.
- It's an owl character. - Right.
- إنها شخصية البومة. - يمين.
Could you maybe mock someone here?
هل يمكن أن تسخر من شخص ما هنا؟
As a person who mocks...
كشخص يستهزئ...
as a profession,
كمهنة،
- Let's mock Ho Dong. - you have to mock the person...
- دعونا نسخر من هو دونغ. - عليك أن تسخر من الشخص...
with the most authority here.
مع السلطة الأكثر هنا.
That's right.
هذا صحيح.
-There are rules in mocking. - There is no difference...
-هناك قواعد في السخرية. - لا يوجد فرق..
in status here.
في الوضع هنا.
- Everyone is equal. - No. I can also read the room.
- الجميع متساوون. - لا، يمكنني أيضًا قراءة الغرفة.
- No. - You have the highest authority.
- لا. - لديك أعلى سلطة.
If I mocked Yeong Cheol,
إذا سخرت من يونغ تشول،
- no one would be satisfied. - We have to pay money.
- لن يكون أحد راضيا. - علينا أن ندفع المال.
I did something called...
لقد فعلت شيئاً اسمه...
- "Who is the Sinner?" - Yes.
- "من هو الخاطئ؟" - نعم.
- Who is the sinner? - It's a musical number.
- من هو المذنب؟ - إنه رقم موسيقي.
- That's right. - I mocked Beom.
- هذا صحيح. - لقد سخرت من بيوم.
("Who is the Sinner?")
("من هو المذنب؟")
(by Lee Jae Youl and META COMEDY CLUB)
(بقلم لي جاي يول وMETA COMEDY CLUB)
(Boasting around with a blue badge...)
(يتفاخر بشارة زرقاء...)
(when he didn't even have 10,000 followers)
(عندما لم يكن لديه حتى 10000 متابع)
(He showed off about his blue badge ever since he had 2,000 followers.)
(لقد تباهى بشارته الزرقاء منذ أن كان لديه 2000 متابع).
(The crime of stealing 120 dollars...)
(جريمة سرقة 120 دولاراً...)
(when Yeong Joon went to eat)
(عندما ذهب يونج جون لتناول الطعام)
(That's not true!)
(هذا ليس صحيحا!)
(The crime of asking Hyeon Seok and me...)
(جريمة سؤال هيون سوك وأنا...)
(to touch the vasectomy surgery area)
(لمس منطقة جراحة استئصال الأسهر)
He made fun of me and had tens of millions of views.
لقد سخر مني وحصل على عشرات الملايين من المشاهدات.
- It was around 27 million. - Really?
- كان حوالي 27 مليون. - حقًا؟
If you mock Ho Dong, and the views are below that,
إذا كنت تسخر من Ho Dong، وكانت المشاهدات أقل من ذلك،
- that means he's below Kwak Beom. - That's right.
- وهذا يعني أنه أقل من كواك بيوم. - هذا صحيح.
I judge people with that.
أنا أحكم على الناس بذلك.
- Nice. - I'll mock Ho Dong with that.
- لطيف - جيد. - سأسخر من هو دونغ بهذا.
Right. I'm sorry.
يمين. أنا آسف.
- This is new. - It's okay.
- هذا جديد. - لا بأس.
- Don't be sorry.
- لا تأسف. - لا تأسف.
If you're sorry, you can't mock him.
إذا كنت آسفًا، فلا يمكنك السخرية منه.
First of all, I apologize for mocking Ho Dong,
أولاً، أعتذر عن السخرية من هو دونغ،
the national MC.
مولودية الوطنية.
I'd like to take this opportunity, as a fan of Men on a Mission,
أود أن أغتنم هذه الفرصة، كمشجع لـ Men on a Mission،
to explain why I'm reporting him.
لشرح سبب الإبلاغ عنه.
The reasons are...
الأسباب هي...
("Who is the Sinner? Mocking Ho Dong" by Lee Jae Youl)
("من هو الخاطئ؟ السخرية من هو دونغ" بقلم لي جاي يول)
(The crime of being a national MC,)
(جريمة كونك MC وطني،)
(but can barely speak standard Korean)
(ولكن بالكاد يستطيع التحدث باللغة الكورية الفصحى)
(The crime of being over 50...)
(جريمة تجاوز الخمسين...)
(and still in the middle of celebrity fights)
(ولا يزال في منتصف معارك المشاهير)
(The crime of looking similar to Park Kwang Deok...)
(جريمة التشبه ببارك كوانغ ديوك...)
(that people had to tell him apart by his underwear color)
(حيث كان على الناس أن يفرقوه من خلال لون ملابسه الداخلية)
(The crime of wearing his own clothes in middle school...)
(جريمة لبس ملابسه الخاصة في المرحلة الإعدادية...)
(when he wears a uniform for Men on a Mission recordings)
(عندما يرتدي الزي الرسمي للرجال في تسجيلات المهمة)
(Who is the sinner?)
(من هو المذنب؟)
(The crime of eating 2 to 3 portions of food...)
(جريمة تناول 2 إلى 3 حصص من الطعام...)
(when he asked for one portion in "Dining Together")
(عندما طلب حصة واحدة في "تناول الطعام معًا")
(The crime of becoming a satisfied pig...)
(جريمة أن تصبح خنزيراً راضياً...)
(when he likes saying wise sayings.)
(عندما يحب قول الحكمة).
(The crime of being in SM,)
(جريمة التواجد في SM،)
(but has never worn the sizes S or M)
(لكنه لم يرتدي أبدًا المقاسات S أو M)
(The crime of debuting as a comedian...)
(جريمة الظهور لأول مرة كممثل كوميدي...)
(without listening to his senior and showing off for 30 years)
(دون الاستماع لكبار السن والرياء لمدة 30 عاما)
(The crime of destroying peace in Men on a Mission)
(جريمة تدمير السلام في رجال في مهمة)
(It's because of those sins!)
(إنه بسبب تلك الذنوب!)
Bravo!
برافو!
Who is the sinner?
من هو الخاطئ؟
That's a piece of art.
هذه قطعة فنية.
(It was a perfect mockery that listed Ho Dong's crimes.)
(لقد كانت استهزاء تامًا هو الذي أدرج جرائم هو دونغ).
- He sings well. - That was well-made.
- يغني جيدا. - لقد كان ذلك جيد الصنع.
Behead the sinner at once!
قطع رأس الخاطئ مرة واحدة!
- Kill him! - Behead him!
- اقتله! - قطع رأسه!
Kang Ho Dong, beheaded.
هود دوه، صفير.
- SM... - You should have added this.
- سم... - كان عليك إضافة هذا.
- Haven't worn the sizes S or M. - The crime of eating...
- لم أرتدي المقاس S أو M. - جريمة الأكل...
Pyongyang naengmyeon every day when he's not North Korean.
بيونج يانج ناينج ميون كل يوم عندما لا يكون كوريًا شماليًا.
(The crime of eating...)
(جريمة الأكل...)
(Pyongyang naengmyeon every day when he's not North Korean)
(بيونج يانج ناينج ميون كل يوم عندما لا يكون كوريًا شماليًا)
- Eating several meals. - The crime of eating...
- تناول عدة وجبات. - جريمة الأكل...
more Pyongyang naengmyeon than a North Korean
أكثر من بيونغ يانغ naengmyeon من كوريا الشمالية
When did you find such a talent?
متى وجدت مثل هذه الموهبة؟
I found it while working on Mocking Party.
لقد وجدته أثناء العمل في Mocking Party.
It was when Yong Jin and I worked together.
كان ذلك عندما عملت أنا ويونغ جين معًا.
That's when I found it.
وهذا عندما وجدت ذلك.
You don't overdo it.
لا تبالغ في ذلك.
I don't.
أنا لا.
But I did it through text at home.
لكنني فعلت ذلك من خلال الرسائل النصية في المنزل.
- How? - Beom was on "Cultwo Show."
- كيف؟ - كان بيوم في برنامج "Cultwo Show".
He wanted an acrostic poem with "milk."
أراد قصيدة أبجدية مع "الحليب".
- It was for the listeners. - Yes. They send those.
- كان للمستمعين. - نعم. يرسلون تلك.
I sent one with a stronger tone than usual.
لقد أرسلت واحدة بنبرة أقوى من المعتاد.
- I'll start with the letters. - Okay.
- سأبدأ بالحروف. - تمام.
O.
يا.
On impulse, Kwak Beom had a vasectomy.
على نحو مفاجئ، أجرى كواك بيوم عملية قطع القناة الدافقة.
- Y. - Your gene has ended.
- ي. - لقد انتهى جينك.
- Isn't that too much? - I'm really sorry.
- أليس هذا كثيرا؟ - أنا آسف حقا.
Beom is a bachelor.
بيوم عازب.
No. I've been married for 13 years.
لا، أنا متزوج منذ 13 عامًا.
(I've been married for 13 years.)
(أنا متزوج منذ 13 عامًا).
- He... - I got the vasectomy...
- هو... - لقد أجريت عملية قطع القناة الدافقة...
He has twins.
لديه توأمان.
No. They were born a year apart.
لا، لقد ولدوا بفارق عام.
- What are you talking about? - Hold on.
- ما الذي تتحدث عنه؟ - يتمسك.
- Weren't they twins? - One son and one daughter.
- ألم يكونوا توأمان؟ - ابن واحد وبنت واحدة.
No. I have two daughters.
لا، لدي ابنتان.
Wasn't one a boy?
لم يكن واحدا صبيا؟
We got everything wrong.
لقد أخطأنا في كل شيء.
It can't be a son and a daughter.
لا يمكن أن يكون ابنًا وابنة.
But...
لكن...
- We're learning a lot today. Nice. - But did you really...
- نحن نتعلم الكثير اليوم. لطيف - جيد. - ولكن هل حقا...
- get the vasectomy? - I really did.
- الحصول على قطع القناة الدافقة؟ - لقد فعلت حقا.
I actually got the vasectomy seven years ago.
لقد أجريت بالفعل عملية قطع القناة الدافقة منذ سبع سنوات.
- Was it eight? It's been a while. - Really?
- هل كانت الثامنة؟ لقد مضى وقت طويل. - حقًا؟
I have two kids, so we agreed, and I got it.
لدي طفلان، لذلك اتفقنا، وحصلت عليه.
Jae Youl dropped the vasectomy bomb...
جاي يول أسقط قنبلة قطع القناة الدافقة...
on the radio.
على الراديو.
Now I'm the celebrity with the most articles on vasectomy.
الآن أنا الشخصية المشهورة صاحبة أكبر عدد من المقالات حول قطع القناة الدافقة.
People don't usually tell others about it.
الناس عادة لا يخبرون الآخرين عن ذلك.
I keep telling people.
وأظل أقول للناس.
There are around 86 articles about me.
هناك حوالي 86 مقالة عني.
You might get a vasectomy commercial soon.
قد تحصل على إعلان تجاري لاستئصال الأسهر قريبًا.
- It's likely. - Right.
- من المحتمل. - يمين.
- It didn't come. - Sang Gook should have said that.
- لم يأت. - كان ينبغي على سانغ جوك أن يقول ذلك.
- You should have said that. - I'm sorry.
- كان يجب أن تقول ذلك. - أنا آسف.
Give me the opportunity.
أعطني الفرصة.
"Give me..."
"أعطني..."
When did you get married, Seon Min?
متى تزوجت يا سيون مين؟
I'm single.
أنا أعزب.
You didn't get married?
لم تتزوج؟
- What are you talking about? - Jang Hoon, you are a shaman.
- ما الذي تتحدث عنه؟ - جانغ هون، أنت شامان.
- You should have known. - I'm single.
- كان يجب أن تعرف. - أنا أعزب.
- You look like... - He looks reliable.
- تبدو وكأنك... - يبدو جديراً بالثقة.
- your child is in 8th grade. - The child would be in 8th grade.
- طفلك في الصف الثامن. - سيكون الطفل في الصف الثامن.
People often think like that.
الناس غالبا ما يفكرون بهذه الطريقة.
- They think you're married, right? - That's right.
- يعتقدون أنك متزوج، أليس كذلك؟ - هذا صحيح.
I look as though I drive a minivan with two car seats loaded.
أبدو كما لو أنني أقود شاحنة صغيرة محملة بمقعدين للسيارة.
- Anyone would think so. - I mean...
- أي شخص يعتقد ذلك. - أعني...
- Hey, Senior Dong. - Yes?
- مهلا، كبار دونغ. - نعم؟
Seon Min has something in common with Seo Jang Hoon.
لدى Seon Min شيء مشترك مع Seo Jang Hoon.
- What is it? - What?
- ما هذا؟ - ماذا؟
I heard about this too. Apparently, Seon Min...
سمعت عن هذا أيضا. على ما يبدو سيون مين...
owns a building.
يمتلك مبنى.
- Really? - That's cool, Seon Min.
- حقًا؟ - هذا رائع، سيون مين.
- That's right. - So, that's why...
- هذا صحيح. - إذن، لهذا السبب...
you're so relaxed on TV.
أنت مرتاح جدًا على شاشة التلفزيون.
I knew it.
كنت أعرف.
- He didn't seem hung up about it. - The rumors have gotten mixed up.
- لا يبدو أنه معلق بشأن ذلك. - لقد اختلطت الشائعات.
There is this small, apartment unit building...
هناك هذا المبنى السكني الصغير...
in Sillim-dong, Seoul,
في سيليم دونج، سيول،
and I feel like I might inherit it.
وأشعر أنني قد أرثها.
What do you mean, you feel like you might inherit it?
ماذا تقصد، هل تشعر أنك قد ترثها؟
I have three older sisters,
لدي ثلاث أخوات أكبر مني،
- Not to lose to others... - but I'm the eldest son.
- أن لا أخسر أمام الآخرين... - ولكنني الابن الأكبر.
So, I feel like I might inherit it.
لذا، أشعر أنني قد أرثها.
But it'll go to your sisters.
لكنها سوف تذهب إلى أخواتك.
No, you have to split it with your sisters.
لا، عليك أن تقسمها مع أخواتك.
- I'm curious about the price now. - No, but...
- أنا مهتم بالسعر الآن. - لا، ولكن...
If you purchased it a long time ago...
إذا اشتريته منذ زمن طويل..
Well, at the time, it was 2008.
حسنًا، في ذلك الوقت، كان عام 2008.
My father said he was going to invest in real estate.
قال والدي إنه سيستثمر في العقارات.
It's a small apartment unit, about 40m².
إنها وحدة سكنية صغيرة تبلغ مساحتها حوالي 40 مترًا مربعًا.
He invested in it by paying 105,000 dollars back then.
وقد استثمر فيها بدفع 105.000 دولار في ذلك الوقت.
Now, it's worth 85,000 dollars.
والآن تبلغ قيمتها 85 ألف دولار.
(Over 16 years, Seon Min's apartment unit is steadily dropping in value.)
(على مدى 16 عامًا، انخفضت قيمة الوحدة السكنية في Seon Min بشكل مطرد.)
- The price is dropping? - You know...
- السعر ينخفض؟ - أنت تعرف...
Our apartment unit is the only one in Seoul...
وحدتنا السكنية هي الوحيدة في سيول...
- that has decreased in value. - Did he say 850,000 dollars?
- التي انخفضت قيمتها. - هل قال 850 ألف دولار؟
- I thought I misheard you. - I thought it'd be over a million.
- اعتقدت أنني أخطأت في فهمك. - اعتقدت أنه سيكون أكثر من مليون.
- I thought you said 850,000. - I thought so too.
- أعتقد أنك قلت 850،000. - اعتقدت ذلك أيضا.
- No, it's 85,000 dollars. - Hey, did everyone else...
- لا، إنها 85 ألف دولار. - مهلا، هل الجميع ...
- feel their brains halt just now? - Hey, how can this happen?
- يشعرون أن أدمغتهم توقفت الآن؟ - مهلا، كيف يمكن أن يحدث هذا؟
- It's true! - Even when it's in Sillim-dong?
- هذا صحيح! - حتى عندما يكون في سيليم دونج؟
Even when it's in Sillim-dong?
حتى عندما يكون في سيليم دونج؟
- Can it drop that much in 16 years? - Also,
- هل يمكن أن تنخفض إلى هذا الحد خلال 16 عامًا؟ - أيضًا،
- it's even a semi-basement unit. - Hey, are you...
- إنها حتى وحدة شبه طابق سفلي. - مهلا، هل أنت...
Your father must've done a lot of research before buying it back then.
من المؤكد أن والدك قد أجرى الكثير من الأبحاث قبل شرائه في ذلك الوقت.
If it cost over 100,000 dollars for a semi-basement unit,
إذا كانت تكلفة الوحدة شبه السفلية أكثر من 100.000 دولار،
- it was probably overpriced. - At the time.
- ربما كان باهظ الثمن. - في ذلك الوقت.
- Right.
- في ذلك الوقت. - يمين.
Yes, so my family is quite upset now.
نعم، عائلتي منزعجة جدًا الآن.
Hey, then will it be worth 65,000 dollars in 20 years?
مهلا، إذن هل ستكون قيمتها 65 ألف دولار خلال 20 عاما؟
- Hey! - Come on, Sang Gook.
- يا! - هيا، سانغ جوك.
I mean, the price keeps going down.
أعني أن السعر يستمر في الانخفاض.
- I know. - How can it keep going down?
- أنا أعرف. - كيف يمكن أن تستمر في النزول؟
- Actually, - It might be free later on.
- في الواقع، - قد يكون مجانيًا لاحقًا.
the apartment unit costs 85,000 dollars,
الوحدة السكنية سعرها 85.000 دولار،
but it cost 20,000 to maintain it.
لكن صيانته كلفت 20 ألفًا.
Even the cost of jjajangmyeon is going up.
حتى تكلفة jjajangmyeon آخذة في الارتفاع.
From waterproofing work to fixing a leak on the rooftop...
من أعمال العزل المائي إلى إصلاح التسرب على السطح...
It's the price of my hard work.
إنه ثمن عملي الشاق.
- Don't you have any happy news? - As for happy news,
- ليس لديك أي أخبار سعيدة؟ - أما الأخبار السعيدة،
my spirit has risen again.
ارتفعت روحي مرة أخرى.
- Oh, right now? - Oh, your spirit?
- أوه، الآن؟ - اه روحك؟
- Right now? - His spirit, right now.
- الآن؟ - روحه، الآن.
- My spirit, right now. - By talking about your building.
- روحي الآن. - من خلال الحديث عن المبنى الخاص بك.
- Thanks to my mother... - The apartment price is dropping.
- شكرا لأمي... - سعر الشقة ينخفض.
- Yes. - The mood is lifting.
- نعم. - المزاج يتحسن.
All right, everyone. Now,
حسناً، الجميع. الآن،
- we'll start the battle. - Okay.
- سنبدأ المعركة. - تمام.
First, I'll ask the King of Mocking.
أولاً، سأسأل ملك السخرية.
What kind of ability do you need to mock others in a pleasant way?
ما نوع القدرة التي تحتاجها للسخرية من الآخرين بطريقة ممتعة؟
First, you have to be sensibly funny.
أولاً، عليك أن تكون مضحكاً بشكل معقول.
And the most important part is to hit and run.
والجزء الأكثر أهمية هو الضرب والهرب.
- Yes, that's right. - You must run before you get hit.
- نعم هذا صحيح. - يجب عليك الركض قبل أن تتعرض للضرب.
- So, we've prepared this battle. - We have to learn from him.
- لذلك، لقد أعددنا هذه المعركة. - علينا أن نتعلم منه.
It's the Sound of Mocking!
إنه صوت السخرية!
(Joke Battle Round 2: The Sound of Mocking)
(جولة معركة النكتة 2: صوت السخرية)
- The SM. - The Sound of Mocking.
- سم. - صوت السخرية.
From now on, one person from each team will come up...
من الآن فصاعدا، سيأتي شخص واحد من كل فريق...
hold water in his mouth...
حبس الماء في فمه..
as he sits in the chair in the middle.
وهو يجلس على الكرسي في المنتصف.
Everyone else on the other teams...
وكل من في الفرق الأخرى...
can mock that person as much as they want from behind.
يمكن أن يسخر من هذا الشخص بقدر ما يريدون من الخلف.
As this happens, the teammate...
وبينما يحدث هذا، زميله في الفريق...
will represent his teammate who's being mocked.
سيمثل زميله الذي يتعرض للسخرية.
The round ends when the player spits out the water in his mouth.
تنتهي الجولة عندما يبصق اللاعب الماء في فمه.
The team with the player who endures the mocking for the longest...
الفريق باللاعب الذي يتحمل السخرية لأطول فترة..
wins the game.
يفوز باللعبة.
I won't care about how funny this is.
لن أهتم بمدى مضحك هذا.
I'm going to endure this for as long as I can.
سأتحمل هذا لأطول فترة ممكنة.
Are there no time limits, then?
ألا توجد حدود زمنية إذن؟
Jae Youl, you've prepared a lot, haven't you?
جاي يول، لقد قمت بتحضير الكثير، أليس كذلك؟
- I haven't prepared anything. - I just have to defend him, right?
- لم أجهز أي شيء. - أنا فقط يجب أن أدافع عنه، أليس كذلك؟
Hey, it's boiled pork.
مهلا، إنه لحم الخنزير المسلوق.
People in their 40s and 50s...
الأشخاص في الأربعينيات والخمسينيات من عمرهم...
- He just called you boiled pork. - hate that action the most.
- لقد دعاك للتو لحم الخنزير المسلوق. - أكره هذا الفعل أكثر.
- Hey, don't drink it! - Don't drink it!
- مهلا، لا تشربه! - لا تشربه!
Why are you drinking it?
لماذا تشربه؟
- You know what I mean? - Don't swallow it.
- أنت تعرف ما أعنيه؟ - لا تبتلعها.
Okay. Ready, set...
تمام. جاهز، استعد...
Looking at you from behind, Ho Dong,
أنظر إليك من الخلف، هو دونغ،
you should get botox shots in your salivary glands.
يجب أن تحصل على حقن البوتوكس في الغدد اللعابية.
I think he's seriously immature.
أعتقد أنه غير ناضج بشكل خطير.
Come on. He is mature.
تعال. إنه ناضج.
Ho Dong's hat looks like it's going to burst.
يبدو أن قبعة Ho Dong سوف تنفجر.
I wish he would stop acting cute.
أتمنى أن يتوقف عن التصرف بلطف.
- He must think he's cute. - I know, right?
- يجب أن يعتقد أنه لطيف. - أنا أوافق؟
- He really must think so. - Are you here for the shoot...
- وقال انه حقا يجب أن يعتقد ذلك. - هل أنت هنا من أجل التصوير...
or just to eat naengmyeon?
أو مجرد أكل naengmyeon؟
Sang Gook, you should say something too.
سانغ جوك، يجب أن تقول شيئًا أيضًا.
Pig.
خنزير.
- Hey, what was that? - You should've defended him!
- مهلا، ماذا كان ذلك؟ - كان عليك أن تدافع عنه!
(Water pig)
(خنزير الماء)
(Sang Gook blatantly attacks his own teammate.)
(سانغ جوك يهاجم زميله في الفريق بشكل صارخ.)
- Hey, what was that? - You should've defended him!
- مهلا، ماذا كان ذلك؟ - كان عليك أن تدافع عنه!
Hey, how could you just spit it out like that?
مهلا، كيف يمكنك أن تبصقها بهذه الطريقة؟
- You just spat it all out! - I mean...
- أنت فقط بصق كل شيء! - أعني...
- That came out of nowhere! - Seriously...
- لقد جاء ذلك من العدم! - بجد...
I guess we can attack our own teammates.
أعتقد أنه يمكننا مهاجمة زملائنا في الفريق.
Gosh, Sang Gook. You should've defended him.
يا إلهي، سانغ جوك. كان عليك أن تدافع عنه.
- I just said one thing! - He made me seem funny.
- قلت شيئا واحدا فقط! - لقد جعلني أبدو مضحكا.
- Sang Gook, that was good. - It was funny.
- سانغ جوك، كان ذلك جيدًا. - كان مضحكا.
Hey, what's there to mock about Jae Youl?
مهلا، ما الذي يمكن الاستهزاء به بشأن جاي يول؟
- I'll protect you, Hee Chul. - Okay.
- سأحميك، هيي تشول. - تمام.
(Loading the water)
(تحميل الماء)
Ready, set...
جاهز، استعد...
Among the contacts on your phone, the ratio of men to women...
من بين جهات الاتصال على هاتفك نسبة الرجال إلى النساء...
Are there about five times more women?
هل هناك حوالي خمسة أضعاف عدد النساء؟
- Five times? - Aren't you literally just curious?
- خمس مرات؟ - ألست مجرد فضول حرفيًا؟
They're all women.
كلهم نساء.
The truth has no impact on him.
الحقيقة ليس لها تأثير عليه.
There aren't that many men.
ليس هناك الكثير من الرجال.
Right, there aren't that many men.
صحيح، ليس هناك الكثير من الرجال.
My wife told me this recently.
أخبرتني زوجتي بهذا مؤخرًا.
You sent my wife a DM.
لقد أرسلت لزوجتي رسالة مباشرة.
(Honey, what's up with this Kim Hee Chul guy?)
(عزيزتي، ما الأمر مع هذا الرجل كيم هي تشول؟)
Hey, Hee Chul.
مهلا، هي تشول.
I'm just making this up!
أنا فقط أختلق هذا!
- Gosh, that was funny. - Why would I DM your wife?
- يا إلهي، كان ذلك مضحكا. - لماذا أرسل رسالة مباشرة إلى زوجتك؟
- Hey, that was a strong blow. - What was that?
- مهلا، تلك كانت ضربة قوية. - ماذا كان هذا؟
- No, it's not true! - I made it up.
- لا، هذا ليس صحيحا! - لقد اختلقتها.
I don't know your wife! Hey!
أنا لا أعرف زوجتك! يا!
- His wife... - Made up stories are okay too.
- زوجته... - القصص المختلقة لا بأس بها أيضاً.
- Of course, that's okay. - Is that how it is?
- بالطبع، لا بأس. - أهكذا هو الأمر؟
- I don't even know who his wife is! - He was wrongly accused.
- أنا لا أعرف حتى من زوجته! - لقد اتهم خطأً.
Gosh, sending a DM to his wife was the best.
يا إلهي، إرسال رسالة مباشرة إلى زوجته كان الأفضل.
(The third player, Sun Bong Jang, Shin Bong Sun)
(اللاعب الثالث سون بونج جانج، شين بونج سون)
Oh, Bong Sun.
أوه، بونغ صن.
- Bong Sun. - Yes?
- بونج صن. - نعم؟
You honestly had a crush on me, right?
لقد كنت معجبًا بي بصراحة، أليس كذلك؟
What ridiculous nonsense.
ما هذا الهراء السخيف.
You know, I've seen Bong Sun for a long time too,
كما تعلمون، لقد رأيت بونج صن لفترة طويلة أيضًا،
but this is what I think. She's the youngest looking woman in her 50s.
ولكن هذا ما أعتقده. إنها أصغر امرأة في الخمسينيات من عمرها.
Bong Sun...
بونج صن...
Bong Sun looks like my grandma from behind.
بونغ صن تبدو مثل جدتي من الخلف.
(Just thinking about my grandma makes me feel good.)
(مجرد التفكير في جدتي يجعلني أشعر أنني بحالة جيدة).
- Bong Sun. - I know what you mean!
- بونج صن. - أعرف ماذا تقصد!
- Bong Sun, you do have that look.
- بونج صن، لديك تلك النظرة. - أعرف ماذا تقصد!
- You should've held it in! - Good job!
- كان يجب عليك الاحتفاظ بها! - أحسنت!
Jae Youl, you're doing so well!
جاي يول، أنت بخير!
You should've held it in for that.
كان يجب عليك الاحتفاظ به من أجل ذلك.
- Good job, Jae Youl. - Come on.
- عمل جيد، جاي يول. - تعال.
Hey, how many did Jae Youl finish off?
مهلا، كم عدد الذين أنهى جاي يول؟
Gosh, he's good.
يا إلهي، إنه جيد.
- Kwak Beom had one hit. - Seriously.
- كواك بيوم أصيب بضربة واحدة. - بجد.
I know what you mean.
أنا أعرف ماذا تقصد.
- Seon Min isn't saying anything. - I couldn't...
- سيون مين لا يقول أي شيء. - لم أستطع...
- I couldn't time it right. - I know what you mean.
- لم أتمكن من الوقت المناسب. - أعرف ماذا تقصد.
- I mean... - They each have one big punch.
- أعني... - كل منهم لديه لكمة واحدة كبيرة.
(The fourth player, Mini Mini, Lee Seon Min)
(اللاعب الرابع ميني ميني، لي سيون مين)
Seon Min isn't even funny. Why did we invite him today?
سيون مين ليست مضحكة حتى. لماذا قمنا بدعوته اليوم؟
- Oh, we haven't started yet. - He hasn't even started yet.
- أوه، لم نبدأ بعد. - ولم يبدأ حتى بعد.
- You just... - Sorry, Seon Min.
- أنت فقط... - آسف، سيون مين.
- All you did was hurt him. - I'm sorry.
- كل ما فعلته هو آذيته. - أنا آسف.
- Sorry, Seon Min. - You really meant what you said.
- آسف، سيون مين. - كنت تعني حقا ما قلته.
Ready, set...
جاهز، استعد...
Well, Seon Min is one thing.
حسنًا، سيون مين هو شيء واحد.
But Sang Min, are your pants the Michelin tire man's or what?
لكن سانغ مين، هل بنطالك هو البنطلون الخاص برجل إطارات ميشلان أم ماذا؟
Are your pants the Michelin tire man's or what?
هل بنطالك هو بنطال رجل إطارات ميشلان أم ماذا؟
(Just finding out about his teammate's style preferences)
(فقط للتعرف على تفضيلات أسلوب زميله في الفريق)
- What? I only just saw them! - I know, right?
- ماذا؟ لقد رأيتهم للتو! - أنا أوافق؟
- Hey, those pants... - What's up with your pants?
- مهلا، تلك السراويل... - ما الأمر مع السراويل الخاصة بك؟
- He's a comedian, for sure. - I only just saw them!
- إنه ممثل كوميدي، بالتأكيد. - لقد رأيتهم للتو!
- But what's up with your pants? - His pants...
- ولكن ما الأمر مع السراويل الخاصة بك؟ - بنطاله...
Why are you wearing those and not the uniform? Tell him something!
لماذا ترتدي تلك وليس الزي الرسمي؟ قل له شيئا!
Hey, if you get to wear those, we will also wear our own clothes!
مرحبًا، إذا ارتديت تلك الملابس، فسنرتدي أيضًا ملابسنا الخاصة!
- I just saw them now! - Hey.
- لقد رأيتهم الآن! - يا.
- He's blatantly wearing Stussy! - Yes.
- إنه يرتدي Stussy بشكل صارخ! - نعم.
I thought his pants were a musical instrument.
اعتقدت أن سرواله كان آلة موسيقية.
What's up with those pants?
ما الأمر مع تلك السراويل؟
I'm in the back seat! Go easy on me, will you?
أنا في المقعد الخلفي! كن سهلاً علي، أليس كذلك؟
- That's so funny. - Good job.
- هذا مضحك جدا. - أحسنت.
- Stop teasing him. - Do you want to face each other?
- التوقف عن إغاظة له. - هل تريدون مواجهة بعضكم البعض؟
You're sure you won't laugh, right?
أنت متأكد أنك لن تضحك، أليس كذلك؟
- Then, I'll go like this. - We're going to be serious.
- ثم، سأذهب مثل هذا. - سنكون جادين.
- He's defending you. - Both of you.
- إنه يدافع عنك. - كلاكما.
- We'll both do it. - Okay, then. Face each other.
- سنقوم على حد سواء القيام بذلك. - حسنًا إذن. واجهوا بعضكم البعض.
- Okay, face each other. - All right.
- حسنًا، واجهوا بعضكم البعض. - حسنًا.
- Face each other. - No dodging!
- مواجهة بعضهم البعض. - لا مراوغة!
- This is the first attempt. - Hey, man.
- هذه هي المحاولة الأولى. - يا رجل.
- If one of us seems to burst out... - Gosh, I don't know about this.
- إذا بدا أن أحدنا قد انفجر... - يا إلهي، لا أعلم شيئًا عن هذا.
- on purpose, - Let's go back.
- عمدا، - دعنا نعود.
- he has to get sprayed twice. - Okay, fine.
- يجب أن يتم رشه مرتين. - حسنًا، حسنًا.
(Enduring mocking while facing each other)
(السخرية الدائمة في مواجهة بعضهم البعض)
- Ho Dong is getting an earful. - For real.
- هو دونغ يتلقى انتقادات شديدة. - لريال مدريد.
Ready, set...
جاهز، استعد...
You get sprayed twice if you spit it out on purpose.
يتم رشك مرتين إذا بصقته عن قصد.
- Okay. - All right.
- تمام. - حسنًا.
- Soo Geun... - Kyung Hoon,
- سو جيون... - كيونغ هون،
buy my apartment unit. Got it?
شراء وحدة شقتي. فهمتها؟
You did that on purpose!
لقد فعلت ذلك عمدا!
Buy my apartment unit, please.
اشتري وحدتي السكنية من فضلك.
(That fatal "Got it?" guarantees laughs 100 percent.)
(هذه العبارة القاتلة "هل فهمت؟" تضمن الضحك بنسبة 100 بالمائة.)
(Soo Geun loses.)
(سو جيون تخسر.)
You did that on purpose!
لقد فعلت ذلك عمدا!
That was on purpose, wasn't it?
كان ذلك عن قصد، أليس كذلك؟
(Mother, today I'm bringing home popularity, not rent.)
(أمي، اليوم سأجلب الشعبية إلى المنزل، وليس الإيجار.)
- Ask him to buy it for 200,000. - Wasn't that on purpose?
- أطلب منه أن يشتريه بـ 200,000. - ألم يكن ذلك عن قصد؟
No!
لا!
- Buy it for 200,000 dollars. - Hey!
- اشتريه بمبلغ 200.000 دولار. - يا!
(Jokes are all about repetition.)
(النكات كلها تدور حول التكرار.)
- How about 120,000 dollars? - That was funny!
- ماذا عن 120.000 دولار؟ - كان ذلك مضحكا!
- Seon Min is back! - Nice!
- سيون مين عاد! - لطيف - جيد!
- That was awesome. - Seon Min is back!
- كان ذلك رائعا. - سيون مين عاد!
- That was good, wasn't it? - Yes.
- كان ذلك جيدًا، أليس كذلك؟ - نعم.
- Right, Beom. Your turn. - Well, Yeong Cheol...
- صحيح، بيوم. دورك. - حسنًا، يونج تشيول..
- As soon as they begin... - Yeong Cheol, help him out.
- بمجرد أن يبدأوا... - يونج تشول، ساعده.
- "You made it to the set today." - Yeong Cheol,
- "لقد وصلت إلى المجموعة اليوم." - يونج تشيول،
you have to help Beom a lot.
عليك أن تساعد بيوم كثيرًا.
- Okay? - Okay.
- تمام؟ - تمام.
- Ready?
- مستعد؟ - تمام.
What?
ماذا؟
Beom, your wife is pregnant.
بيوم، زوجتك حامل.
- Hang on. - Hey, you can't say that!
- انتظر. - مهلا، لا يمكنك أن تقول ذلك!
Your wife is pregnant.
زوجتك حامل.
(I'm sure I had everything tied up!)
(أنا متأكد من أن كل شيء كان مقيدًا!)
- Hang on. - Hey, you can't say that!
- انتظر. - مهلا، لا يمكنك أن تقول ذلك!
- You must be crazy! - Hey!
- لابد أنك مجنون! - يا!
(Sang Gook was determined, indeed.)
(كان سانغ جوك مصممًا بالفعل.)
- Hey, you know... - I can't believe this!
- مهلا، كما تعلمون... - لا أستطيع أن أصدق هذا!
- he had a vasectomy! - You're crazy!
- أجرى عملية قطع القناة الدافقة! - أنت مجنون!
(The vasectomy guy is angry.)
(رجل استئصال الأسهر غاضب.)
- Hey! - Gosh, what is this?
- يا! - يا إلهي، ما هذا؟
A pregnancy scandal...
فضيحة الحمل..
Why is his wife becoming pregnant considered mocking?
لماذا يعتبر حمل زوجته استهزاء؟
No, this is...
لا، هذا...
- Why is that considered mocking? - But... Hey!
- لماذا يعتبر ذلك استهزاء؟ - ولكن... مهلا!
- It could've come undone! - No, but this is...
- كان من الممكن أن يتم التراجع! - لا، ولكن هذا...
- A vasectomy can go wrong. - Right?
- من الممكن أن تسير عملية استئصال الأسهر بشكل خاطئ. - يمين؟
- It could've come undone. - My goodness.
- كان من الممكن أن يتم التراجع. - يا إلهي.
- It is possible! - What are you saying?
- من الممكن! - ماذا تقول؟
- It is a possibility. - Well...
- إنه احتمال. - حسنًا...
- It does happen for some people! - It is possible.
- هذا يحدث لبعض الناس! - فمن الممكن.
- There are such cases. - Yes.
- هناك مثل هذه الحالات. - نعم.
- It is possible. - There are such cases.
- فمن الممكن. - هناك مثل هذه الحالات.
- That was totally "Gag Concert." - You can't go crazy.
- كان ذلك "حفلة هفوة" تمامًا. - لا يمكنك أن تصاب بالجنون.
- TV shows are just TV shows! - Just TV shows!
- البرامج التلفزيونية هي مجرد برامج تلفزيونية! - البرامج التلفزيونية فقط!
- Don't get the wrong idea!
- لا تحصل على فكرة خاطئة! - لا تحصل على فكرة خاطئة!
- TV shows are just TV shows!
- البرامج التلفزيونية هي مجرد برامج تلفزيونية! - البرامج التلفزيونية هي مجرد برامج تلفزيونية!
Let me announce the winning team. The winners of the Sound of Mocking.
اسمحوا لي أن أعلن عن الفريق الفائز. الفائزون في صوت السخرية.
Hanging in there for the longest with 28.58 seconds,
البقاء هناك لأطول فترة مع 28.58 ثانية،
it's none other than Sun Bong Jang!
إنه ليس سوى صن بونج جانج!
- Sun Bong Jang won? - I thought I didn't last long.
- صن بونج جانج فاز؟ - اعتقدت أنني لم يدم طويلا.
Dance.
الرقص.
- Yes, show us a dance. - Dance!
- نعم، تبين لنا رقصة. - الرقص!
(We can't miss out on the dance ceremony.)
(لا يمكننا تفويت حفل الرقص.)
(Shaking her body to the melody from our memories)
(تهز جسدها على أنغام ذكرياتنا)
She's a good dancer.
إنها راقصة جيدة.
(Hey! I'm the Queen of enduring mockery!)
(مرحبًا! أنا ملكة السخرية الدائمة!)
(A perfect performance by the comedian-singer)
(أداء مثالي للمغني الكوميدي)
- She's a good dancer. - Wonderful!
- إنها راقصة جيدة. - رائع!
- Beautiful. - Nice.
- جميل. - لطيف - جيد.
- Wasn't that Capsai Shin's dance? - No.
- ألم تكن تلك رقصة كابساي شين؟ - لا.
Ho Dong is happy.
هو دونغ سعيد.
(Mr. "Star King" is beyond satisfied.)
(السيد "ستار كينج" غير راضٍ.)
An old dance.
رقصة قديمة.
- Then, Jae Youl... - It's free.
- إذن، جاي يول... - إنه مجاني.
(How did the joke masters get started in comedy?)
(كيف بدأ أساتذة النكتة في الكوميديا؟)
When did you first feel that people laughed when you did something?
متى شعرت لأول مرة أن الناس يضحكون عندما تفعل شيئًا ما؟
Oh, in middle school, there was a comedy competition.
أوه، في المدرسة المتوسطة، كانت هناك مسابقة كوميدية.
- Oh, really? - When I was in middle school,
- أوه حقًا؟ - عندما كنت في المدرسة المتوسطة،
it was around 2008 and 2009.
كان ذلك في حوالي عامي 2008 و 2009.
That was when Soo Geun was really popular.
كان ذلك عندما كانت Soo Geun تحظى بشعبية كبيرة.
I entered a comedy competition back then, and won second place.
دخلت في مسابقة كوميدية في ذلك الوقت، وحصلت على المركز الثاني.
- My gosh. - Just like that?
- يا إلهي. - فقط هكذا؟
- There was a comedy competition? - A national comedy competition.
- كانت هناك مسابقة كوميدية؟ - مسابقة وطنية كوميدية .
What about the others?
ماذا عن الآخرين؟
When did you think,
متى فكرت،
"Other friends laugh at my words?"
"الأصدقاء الآخرون يضحكون على كلامي؟"
- Me? No matter where I went, - Were you funny in your teen years?
- أنا؟ بغض النظر عن المكان الذي ذهبت إليه - هل كنت مضحكاً في سنوات مراهقتك؟
I was the funniest.
كنت أطرف.
- Even in your teen years? - Middle school,
- حتى في سنوات المراهقة الخاصة بك؟ - المدرسة المتوسطة،
high school, and university.
المدرسة الثانوية، والجامعة.
Then I entered the Marine Corps to complete my military service.
ثم دخلت مشاة البحرية لإكمال خدمتي العسكرية.
I thought, "If I try to be funny in here,"
فكرت: "إذا حاولت أن أكون مضحكاً هنا"
"it might be a good idea to become a comedian."
"قد تكون فكرة جيدة أن تصبح ممثلًا كوميديًا."
You can't be funny in the Marine Corps, right?
لا يمكنك أن تكون مضحكاً في مشاة البحرية، أليس كذلك؟
- You can't do that. - There's no chance to be funny.
- لا يمكنك أن تفعل ذلك. - ليس هناك فرصة لتكون مضحكا.
I didn't have specialties back then.
لم يكن لدي تخصصات في ذلك الوقت.
The movie, "Sunflower," was in vogue back then.
كان فيلم "عباد الشمس" رائجًا في ذلك الوقت.
- Right. - There wasn't a specialty time,
- يمين. - لم يكن هناك وقت التخصص،
but I was so desperate to be funny...
لكني كنت يائساً جداً لأكون مضحكاً..
that I did an impression...
بأنني فعلت انطباعا...
- of Kim Rae Won. - You did an impression of him.
- لكيم راي وون. - لقد فعلت انطباعا عنه.
- It was so funny... - Okay.
- كان مضحكا جدا... - حسنا.
that each barracks called me over before lights-out.
أن كل ثكنة اتصلت بي قبل إطفاء الأنوار.
"Hey, tell Kwak Beom to come over."
"مرحبًا، أخبر كواك بيوم أن يأتي."
- You were too funny. - It isn't easy to achieve that.
- لقد كنت مضحكا جدا. - ليس من السهل تحقيق ذلك.
They burst out laughing whenever I did the specialty.
لقد انفجروا من الضحك كلما قمت بالتخصص.
- Then I turned off the lights. - Was it the same as...
- ثم أطفأت الأنوار. - هل كان هو نفسه...
- Show us. - Ho Dong's...
- تبين لنا. - هو دونغ...
- What's the specialty? - "Leave if you want to live?"
- ما هو التخصص؟ - "اترك إذا كنت تريد أن تعيش؟"
- It was different. - Okay.
- كان مختلفا. - تمام.
Let's say it was Barracks Number Five.
لنفترض أنها كانت الثكنة رقم خمسة.
Knock, knock. "Permission to enter?"
اطرق، اطرق. "الإذن بالدخول؟"
"It's Kwak Beom, right? Come on in."
"إنه كواك بوم، أليس كذلك؟ تفضل بالدخول."
"It's me, you punk."
"هذا أنا، أنت فاسق."
- I see. - Kim Rae Won's famous line.
- أرى. - جملة كيم راي وون الشهيرة.
I just did that.
لقد فعلت ذلك للتو.
- Out of nowhere. - I just did that out of nowhere.
- من العدم. - لقد فعلت ذلك من العدم.
Then I went to Barracks Number Six.
ثم ذهبت إلى الثكنة رقم ستة.
Knock, knock. "Permission to enter?"
اطرق، اطرق. "الإذن بالدخول؟"
"Kwak Beom, come on in."
"كواك بيوم، تفضل بالدخول."
"It's me, you punk."
"هذا أنا، أنت فاسق."
- Did you do the rounds? - I did the rounds.
- هل قمت بالجولات؟ - لقد قمت بالجولات.
After saying, "It's me, you punk," at the last barracks,
بعد أن قال "هذا أنا أيها الشرير" في الثكنة الأخيرة،
- I went to bed. - Hey.
- ذهبت إلى السرير. - يا.
- You know, - People burst out laughing.
- كما تعلم - انفجر الناس بالضحك.
it has been two hours since I began my Men on a Mission shoot.
لقد مرت ساعتان منذ أن بدأت رجالي في مهمة التصوير.
When I feel like something isn't appropriate for TV,
عندما أشعر أن هناك شيئًا غير مناسب للتلفزيون،
I just need to look at Ho Dong's face.
أنا فقط بحاجة إلى إلقاء نظرة على وجه هو دونغ.
He pulls a straight face right away.
انه يسحب وجه مستقيم على الفور.
- Yes. - He doesn't know what it is.
- نعم. - لا يعرف ما هو.
I'm sorry. I didn't watch the movie.
أنا آسف. لم أشاهد الفيلم.
(The reason why he couldn't laugh)
(سبب عدم قدرته على الضحك)
- That was why. - It took me a while to understand.
- كان هذا هو السبب. - استغرق مني بعض الوقت لفهم.
- Laugh, you pig. - He has been dissatisfied...
- اضحك أيها الخنزير. - لقد أصبح غير راضٍ..
- for a while. - He made me do it.
- لفترة من الوقت. - لقد جعلني أفعل ذلك.
- Ho Dong, he made me do it. - That's right.
- هو دونغ، لقد جعلني أفعل ذلك. - هذا صحيح.
Seon Min, when did you think, "I should become a comedian?"
سيون مين، متى فكرت، "يجب أن أصبح ممثلًا كوميديًا؟"
To be honest, today was the first day when I felt,
بصراحة، اليوم كان أول يوم شعرت فيه،
"I'm someone who can make people laugh."
"أنا شخص يستطيع أن يجعل الناس يضحكون."
- Today? - The 1st 10 minutes of the shoot.
- اليوم؟ - الـ 10 دقائق الأولى من اللقطة.
Then I forgot about it.
ثم نسيت الأمر.
While it's nice to be relaxed...
بينما من الجميل أن تسترخي..
Seriously, your eyes...
بجد عيونك...
Are you sleepy? Go home and sleep.
هل أنت نعسان؟ العودة إلى المنزل والنوم.
Go home and sleep.
العودة إلى المنزل والنوم.
It looks like Seon Min has many lookalikes.
يبدو أن Seon Min لديه العديد من التشابهات.
- I love that. - What?
- أنا أحب ذلك. - ماذا؟
One lookalike is Actor Jung Man Sik.
أحد مشابهيه هو الممثل Jung Man Sik .
- You look like him. - I see the resemblance.
- أنت تشبهه. - أرى التشابه.
One lookalike is Moon Hee Joon of H.O.T.
أحد الشبيهين هو Moon Hee Joon من HOT
- Hey.
- أرى التشابه. - يا.
- Hey, there's... - I see the resemblance.
- مهلا، هناك... - أرى التشابه.
- no resemblance!
- لا يوجد شبه! - أرى التشابه.
- No way.
- أرى التشابه. - مستحيل.
Seon Min is full of charms today.
Seon Min مليئة بالسحر اليوم.
- Is there resemblance? - I resemble Cho Hye Lyun too.
- هل هناك تشابه؟ - أنا أشبه تشو هاي ليون أيضًا.
- Cho Hye Lyun. - Kim Sook too.
- تشو هاي ليون. - كيم سوك أيضاً.
- I see the resemblance. - You also resemble Noh Joo Hyun.
- أرى التشابه. - أنت أيضًا تشبه نوه جو هيون.
- People say that I resemble him. - Yes. I absolutely love it.
- الناس يقولون أنني أشبهه. - نعم. أنا أحب ذلك تماما.
- I really enjoyed watching it. - What is it?
- لقد استمتعت حقا بمشاهدته. - ما هذا؟
He starred in...
وقام ببطولة...
- "Why Can't We Stop Them." - That's right.
- "لماذا لا نستطيع إيقافهم." - هذا صحيح.
People say that I resemble him from that era.
يقول الناس أنني أشبهه من تلك الحقبة.
- Yes. You really do. - Show us.
- نعم. أنت حقا تفعل. - تبين لنا.
Hello, I'm Noh Joo Hyun.
مرحبًا، أنا نوه جو هيون.
I visited Men on a Mission...
قمت بزيارة رجال في مهمة...
twenty-one years after starring in "Why Can't We Stop Them."
بعد مرور واحد وعشرين عامًا على بطولة فيلم "لماذا لا يمكننا إيقافهم".
- Many people don't know him. - It's so good...
- كثير من الناس لا يعرفونه. - إنه جيد جدًا ...
to see Ho Dong again.
لرؤية هو دونغ مرة أخرى.
He sounds like Kim Sang Joong.
يبدو مثل كيم سانغ جونغ.
Hee Chul, have you been well?
هي تشول، هل كنت بخير؟
- Yes, Joo Hyun. Long time no see. - I see that you've been well.
- نعم، جو هيون. وقت طويل لا رؤية. - أرى أنك بخير.
- Only Hee Chul knows. - Sang Min, you paid off your debts.
- فقط هي تشول يعرف. - سانغ مين، لقد سددت ديونك.
Yes, I did.
نعم فعلت.
- What's this? - So...
- ما هذا؟ - لذا...
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
Are you sleepy?
هل أنت نعسان؟
Seriously.
بجد.
- Are you sleepy? - Only Gen Zers can understand.
- هل أنت نعسان؟ - لا يفهمه إلا الجيل Z.
- What was that? - Seriously.
- ماذا كان هذا؟ - بجد.
- Give me a chance to enter. - Sang Gook.
- أعطني فرصة للدخول. - سانغ جوك.
(He makes me laugh.)
(إنه يجعلني أضحك).
- For goodness' sake. - Make a decision.
- في سبيل الخير. - اتخاذ القرار.
What was that?
ماذا كان هذا؟
- I also resemble... - Okay.
- أنا أيضًا أشبه... - حسنًا.
the outsider in "The Wailing."
الدخيل في "النحيب".
- That's right. "It's a demon." - You do resemble him.
- هذا صحيح. "إنه شيطان." - أنت تشبهه.
- "It's a demon." - I'll deliver that line.
- "إنه شيطان". - سأقوم بتسليم هذا الخط.
"It's a demon."
"إنه شيطان."
- In a cave, - That's right.
- في الكهف، - هذا صحيح.
- a priest... - That's right. A priest.
- كاهن... - هذا صحيح. كاهن.
turns into a demon.
يتحول إلى شيطان.
- That's right. - I'm sorry,
- هذا صحيح. - أنا آسف،
but Ho Dong doesn't know the movie.
لكن هو دونغ لا يعرف الفيلم.
- Do it for us. - That's right.
- افعل ذلك من أجلنا. - هذا صحيح.
- He doesn't know many movies.
- لا يعرف الكثير من الأفلام. - هذا صحيح.
Don't look at him.
لا تنظر إليه.
- Look at us. - It'll be fascinating.
- أنظر إلينا. - سوف يكون رائعا.
- Here I go. - Okay.
- ها أنا ذا. - تمام.
(Blocking Ho Dong's eyes)
(حجب عيون هو دونغ)
- How scary. - He resembles him.
- كم هو مخيف. - يشبهه.
- He really resembles him. - I'm...
- إنه يشبهه حقًا. - أنا أكون...
a demon.
شيطان.
- Kunimura Jun.
- كونيمورا يونيو. - كونيمورا يونيو.
It was a bit similar.
لقد كان مشابهًا بعض الشيء.
- His facial expressions change. - You know,
- تتغير تعابير وجهه. - أنت تعرف،
while Seon Min can be funny,
بينما يمكن أن تكون Seon Min مضحكة،
his eyes have a solemn look.
عيناه لها نظرة مهيبة.
- His eyes have a trustworthy look. - Yes.
- عيونه فيها نظرة ثقة. - نعم.
I heard that a lot.
سمعت ذلك كثيرا.
I played a character...
لقد لعبت شخصية...
who was a reporter in the 80s.
الذي كان مراسلا في الثمانينات.
I played a character with the old-fashioned accent.
لقد لعبت شخصية بلهجة قديمة الطراز.
Do you want to see it?
هل تريد رؤيته؟
- Sang Gook, the news is on. - The news.
- سانغ جوك، الأخبار موجودة. - الأخبار.
- The news is on. - We need to watch the news.
- الأخبار موجودة. - نحن بحاجة لمشاهدة الأخبار.
They're pressuring him.
إنهم يضغطون عليه.
Hello, viewers.
مرحبا أيها المشاهدين.
This is Reporter Lee Seon Min at the scene of Men on a Mission,
هذه هي المراسلة لي سيون مين في مسرح فيلم Men on a Mission،
JTBC's new comedy show of 1988.
العرض الكوميدي الجديد لقناة JTBC لعام 1988.
- He sounds like a man of the past.
- يبدو وكأنه رجل من الماضي. - يبدو وكأنه رجل من الماضي.
All right. It's hard...
حسنًا. انه صعب...
to believe that these members are high schoolers.
للاعتقاد بأن هؤلاء الأعضاء هم من طلاب المدارس الثانوية.
Firstly, there's Kang Ho Dong who was on "Johnny Yune Show."
أولاً، هناك كانغ هو دونغ الذي كان في برنامج "Johnny Yune Show".
And there's Seo Jang Hoon who only competes with his skills...
وهناك سيو جانج هون الذي لا يتنافس إلا بمهاراته...
in the handsome Yonsei Basketball Team.
في فريق يونسي لكرة السلة الوسيم.
(The representative star of Yonsei Basketball Team)
(النجم التمثيلي لفريق يونسي لكرة السلة)
He attacked Jang Hoon just to be funny.
لقد هاجم جانغ هون فقط ليكون مضحكا.
He came prepared.
لقد جاء مستعدا.
- He came prepared. - And there's...
- لقد جاء مستعدا. - وهناك...
Lee Sang Min who recently made a four-member mixed-gender group,
لي سانغ مين الذي قام مؤخرًا بتشكيل مجموعة مختلطة من الجنسين مكونة من أربعة أعضاء،
and began spouting indecipherable, alien language rap.
وبدأت في نطق موسيقى الراب بلغة غريبة لا يمكن فك شفرتها.
- Alien language rap. - Yes.
- لغة الراب الغريبة. - نعم.
And other underlings have gathered around.
وتجمع مرؤوسون آخرون حولها.
- Underlings.
- التابعون. - التابعين.
And other underlings have gathered around...
وتجمع حوله رفاق آخرون..
- to make up Men on a Mission. - Underlings.
- لتعويض الرجال في مهمة. - التابعين.
I hope Men on a Mission will go past the 500th, 1,000th episodes,
أتمنى أن يتجاوز مسلسل Men on a Mission الحلقات الـ 500 أو الـ 1000.
- and become... - Go past...
- وتصبح... - تمضي...
a show that discovers many new talents.
عرض يكتشف العديد من المواهب الجديدة.
You've listened to Reporter Lee Seon Min.
لقد استمعت إلى المراسل لي سيون مين.
- That's right. It was like news. - He has that tone.
- هذا صحيح. كان مثل الأخبار. - لديه تلك النغمة.
- It was hard. - My goodness.
- كان الأمر صعبا. - يا إلهي.
- It was fun. - You know,
- كان ممتعا. - أنت تعرف،
Seon Min's specialty was great.
كان تخصص Seon Min رائعًا.
We have many people with great specialties in here.
لدينا الكثير من الأشخاص ذوي التخصصات الرائعة هنا.
The thing is, Jae Youl...
الأمر هو، جاي يول...
- Jae Youl doesn't disappoint. - That's right.
- جاي يول لا يخيب. - هذا صحيح.
Can you do that impression now?
هل يمكنك أن تفعل هذا الانطباع الآن؟
I officially received permission.
لقد حصلت على الإذن رسميًا.
You received permission.
لقد حصلت على إذن.
I met him in person and received permission.
التقيت به شخصيًا وحصلت على الإذن.
Since I only used one line,
وبما أنني استخدمت سطرًا واحدًا فقط،
- he told me to utilize other lines. - Right.
- قال لي أن أستخدم خطوطًا أخرى. - يمين.
- I'm jealous. - It's a Cha Seung Won impression.
- أنا غيور. - إنه انطباع تشا سيونج وون.
He's really good.
انه جيد حقا.
Assistant Manager Seo Yeong Rak,
مساعد المدير سيو يونج راك،
you must be very angry.
يجب أن تكون غاضبًا جدًا.
All you need is faith.
كل ما تحتاجه هو الإيمان.
(Laughing)
(يضحك)
(It was the same as the line directed at Assistant Manager Seo.)
(كان هذا هو نفس الخط الموجه إلى مساعد المدير Seo.)
- He's good. - Yes.
- انه جيد. - نعم.
At Seung Won's gym,
في صالة الألعاب الرياضية الخاصة بـ سيونغ وون،
the trainers teased him a lot.
لقد أزعجه المدربون كثيرًا.
When he lifted weights,
عندما رفع الأثقال،
they went, "Assistant Manager Seo Yeong Rak,"
لقد ذهبوا، "مساعد المدير سيو يونج راك"
"you must be struggling."
"يجب أن تكافح."
He said, "I won't let Jae Youl be..."
قال: "لن أسمح لجاي يول أن يكون..."
- at an event. - That's right.
- في حدث ما. - هذا صحيح.
- But I still imitate him.
- ولكن ما زلت أقلده. - هذا صحيح.
- I'm jealous. - It has gotten to this point.
- أنا غيور. - لقد وصل الأمر إلى هذا الحد.
When Super Junior goes on tours,
عندما يذهب سوبر جونيور في جولات،
Choi Si Won practices acting...
تشوي شي وون يتدرب على التمثيل...
by watching Cha Seung Won's performances.
من خلال مشاهدة عروض Cha Seung Won.
But instead of imitating Seung Won,
لكن بدلاً من تقليد سيونغ وون،
he imitates Jae Youl. He does that, right?
إنه يقلد جاي يول. هو يفعل ذلك، أليس كذلك؟
Throughout the tours...
طوال الجولات...
- "Assistant Manager." - He does that all day long.
- "مساعد المدير". - يفعل ذلك طوال اليوم.
- That's right.
- يفعل ذلك طوال اليوم. - هذا صحيح.
Today,
اليوم،
- for Kyung Hoon, - Okay.
- لكيونج هون، - حسنًا.
I'll sing Kyung Hoon's song in Cha Seung Won's voice.
سأغني أغنية كيونغ هون بصوت تشا سيونغ وون.
(An impression of Cha Seung Won singing Kyung Hoon's song)
(انطباع عن تشا سونغ وون وهو يغني أغنية كيونغ هون)
- How? - I think...
- كيف؟ - أظن...
Cha Seung Won will be unhappy.
سيكون تشا سيونغ وون غير سعيد.
("Thorn (Cha Seung Won Ver.)" by Lee Jae Youl)
("ثورن (تشا سيونغ وون فير.)" بقلم لي جاي يول)
- Seung Won doesn't usually sing. - It'll be hard.
- سونغ وون لا يغني عادة. - سيكون من الصعب.
(Excited)
(متحمس)
He changed the key to the women's key.
قام بتغيير المفتاح إلى مفتاح النساء.
(Come into my body, Cha Seung Won.)
(تعال إلى جسدي، تشا سيونغ وون.)
No way.
مستحيل.
My goodness.
يا إلهي.
He's good.
انه جيد.
Assistant Manager Seo Jang Hoon.
مساعد المدير سيو جانج هون.
(Memories)
(ذكريات)
(Love)
(حب)
(Thorn)
(شوكة)
(Vocalizing)
(النطق)
(Go)
(يذهب)
(Laughing)
(يضحك)
(The memories of Assistant Manager Seo Yeong Rak...)
(ذكريات مساعد المدير سيو يونج راك...)
(are like a thorn.)
(مثل الشوكة).
Jae Youl.
جاي يول.
- Jae Youl. - It was great.
- جاي يول. - كان رائعا.
Listen.
يستمع.
Hey, did you...
مهلا، هل...
Did you ridicule Cha Seung Won,
هل سخرت من تشا سونغ وون؟
Seo Jang Hoon,
سيو جانج هون,
- or Min Kyung Hoon? - I don't know.
- أو مين كيونغ هون؟ - لا أعرف.
- Everything got mixed. - He killed 3 people with 1 stone.
- اختلط كل شيء. - قتل 3 أشخاص بحجر واحد.
He did it.
لقد فعل ذلك.
I laughed so hard that I shed tears.
ضحكت بشدة لدرجة أنني ذرفت الدموع.
- You'll get another call from him. - It'll be a popular video.
- ستأتيك مكالمة أخرى منه. - سوف يكون الفيديو شعبية.
"Jae Youl, I won't let you be."
"جاي يول، لن أسمح لك بذلك."
Sang Gook and Seon Min became depressed.
أصبح سانغ جوك وسيون مين مكتئبين.
Beom too.
بيوم أيضا.
- Beom became depressed. - It was so good.
- أصبح بيوم مكتئبا. - لقد كانت جيدة جدًا.
I can do many impressions,
أستطيع أن أفعل العديد من الانطباعات،
but all of them got tied.
لكن تم ربطهم جميعًا.
- That happens. - Like a vasectomy.
- يحدث ذلك. - مثل استئصال الأسهر.
All of them got tied like a vasectomy.
تم ربطهم جميعًا مثل قطع القناة الدافقة.
I recently got a call from Jang Hyuk.
لقد تلقيت مؤخرًا مكالمة من جانغ هيوك.
He asked me to stop.
طلب مني أن أتوقف.
- He was actually angry. - Yes.
- كان غاضبا في الواقع. - نعم.
This time,
هذه المرة،
we'll check out...
سوف نتحقق...
the comradeship of the fierce Joke Battle.
رفقة معركة النكتة الشرسة.
The next round is...
الجولة القادمة هي...
Secret Hunt.
الصيد السري.
(Joke Battle Round 3: Secret Hunt)
(جولة معركة النكتة 3: الصيد السري)
Everyone submitted a secret before the shoot.
قدم الجميع سرًا قبل التصوير.
Now, I'll reveal...
والآن سأكشف...
(Laughing)
(يضحك)
one of the secrets.
أحد الأسرار.
- It must be funny. - The ones who know...
- يجب أن يكون مضحكا. - الذين يعرفون...
are me and the owner of the secret.
أنا وصاحب السر .
The partner will find out as well.
سوف يكتشف الشريك ذلك أيضًا.
- Now, the team of the secret... - How will the partner know?
- الآن فريق السر... - كيف سيعرف الشريك؟
will act like...
سوف يتصرف مثل...
the secret doesn't belong to them...
السر ليس لهم..
by feigning innocence.
بالتظاهر بالبراءة.
I'll reveal the secret first.
سأكشف السر أولاً.
- This is the secret. - It'll be fun.
- هذا هو السر. - سوف يكون ممتعا.
Is this even possible?
هل هذا ممكن حتى؟
(What's the secret?)
(ما السر؟)
This is the secret.
هذا هو السر.
"My breasts keep getting bigger."
"ثديي يستمر في التزايد."
(My breasts keep getting bigger.)
(ثديي يستمر في التزايد.)
What?
ماذا؟
Put your head down.
ضع رأسك للأسفل.
Make a sound.
اصنع صوتا.
If this secret is yours, raise your head,
إذا كان هذا السر لك، ارفع رأسك،
and touch your partner.
والمس شريك حياتك.
(Reveal the secret of the breasts to the partner.)
(كشف سر الثديين للشريك).
- And touch your partner. - Really?
- والمس شريك حياتك. - حقًا؟
All right. It's done.
حسنًا. لقد تم ذلك.
Everyone, get up.
الجميع، انهضوا.
Now, the Secret Hunt will begin.
الآن سوف تبدأ عملية المطاردة السرية.
It has to be Jang Hoon.
يجب أن يكون جانغ هون.
Why do you think that?
لماذا تعتقد ذلك؟
I always give Jang Hoon a hug when I meet him.
أنا دائمًا أعانق جانغ هون عندما أقابله.
I don't know when it started,
لا أعرف متى بدأت،
but his chest has become bigger.
لكن صدره أصبح أكبر.
- Did you feel it with your chest? - It isn't like that.
- هل شعرت به بصدرك؟ - الأمر ليس كذلك.
Since 2 years or 1 and a half years ago,
منذ سنتين أو سنة ونصف،
- Did your breasts grow? - I've been exercising.
- هل كبر ثدييك؟ - لقد تم ممارسة الرياضة.
- That must be why. - Hold on.
- يجب أن يكون هذا هو السبب. - يتمسك.
Isn't it Bong Sun? She swims.
أليس كذلك بونج صن؟ هي تسبح.
- Who else in here... - Hey.
- من آخر هنا... - مهلا.
will have bigger breasts?
سيكون لها ثديين أكبر؟
It's my wish to have bigger breasts.
إنها رغبتي في الحصول على ثديين أكبر.
If there's a way,
إذا كان هناك طريقة،
I want to make my breasts bigger.
أريد أن أجعل ثديي أكبر.
- Maybe it isn't her. - Hey.
- ربما ليست هي. - يا.
- I... - Do you really think...
- أنا... - هل تعتقدين حقاً...
it's Bong Sun's secret?
إنه سر بونغ صن؟
You want it to be your secret.
تريد أن يكون سرك.
Yes, it's my dream.
نعم، إنه حلمي.
I don't know who it is, but I'm very jealous.
أنا لا أعرف من هو، ولكن أنا غيور جدا.
I didn't know who it was at first.
لم أكن أعرف من هو في البداية.
- Lee Sang Min. - I figured it out just now.
- لي سانغ مين. - لقد اكتشفت ذلك للتو.
- I got a hunch. - It's Kang Ho Dong.
- لدي حدس. - إنه كانغ هو دونغ.
- I have my reasons. Think about... - Then...
- لدي أسبابي. فكر في... - ثم...
who will make this secret...
من سيكشف هذا السر...
the funniest at this time.
الأكثر تسلية في هذا الوقت.
If Ho Dong's breasts got bigger, it's the funniest thing.
إذا أصبح ثديي هو دونغ أكبر، فهذا هو الشيء المضحك.
We'll get 500 articles tomorrow.
سنحصل على 500 مقالة غدًا.
Why would my breasts get bigger?
لماذا يصبح ثديي أكبر؟
- They could get bigger. - You know...
- يمكن أن تصبح أكبر. - أنت تعرف...
- He hides them by wearing black.
- يمكن أن تصبح أكبر. - يخفيهم بارتداء اللون الأسود.
- That's right. - Age...
- هذا صحيح. - عمر...
It isn't Ho Dong.
إنه ليس هو دونغ.
- I... - When he was a ssireum wrestler,
- أنا... - عندما كان مصارعًا في السيريوم،
he was shirtless. His breasts were bigger then.
كان بلا قميص. كان ثدييه أكبر في ذلك الوقت.
- But... - That's right.
- ولكن... - هذا صحيح.
- He was in his best shape then. - Did his breasts become smaller?
- لقد كان في أفضل حالاته حينها. - هل أصبح ثدييه أصغر؟
- He's right. - All of us saw them.
- إنه على حق. - كلنا رأيناهم.
- His breasts were bigger then. - That's right.
- كان ثدييه أكبر حينها. - هذا صحيح.
- Your breasts get smaller with age. - My breasts were bigger then.
- ثدييك يصبحان أصغر مع التقدم في السن. - كان ثديي أكبر حينها.
- I remember old videos of Ho Dong. - His breasts became smaller.
- أتذكر مقاطع الفيديو القديمة لـ Ho Dong. - أصبح ثدييه أصغر.
- Shall I be honest with you?
- أصبح ثدييه أصغر. - هل أكون صادقا معك؟
- It's Hee Chul. - When this secret got revealed,
- إنها هي تشول. - عندما تم الكشف عن هذا السر،
I wondered who had submitted it...
تساءلت من الذي قدمها..
and took a look around.
وألقى نظرة حوله.
One person's neck muscles were especially stiff.
وكانت عضلات رقبة أحد الأشخاص متيبسة بشكل خاص.
Who was it?
من كان؟
- Seon Min. - From the beginning of the shoot,
- سيون مين. - منذ بداية التصوير
- When... - he has been stiff.
- عندما... - لقد كان قاسيا.
- this secret got revealed, - From the beginning of the shoot?
- تم الكشف عن هذا السر - منذ بداية التصوير؟
- his neck muscles became stiff. - She's right.
- أصبحت عضلات رقبته متصلبة. - إنها على حق.
- He has a secret. - When Ho Dong was talking,
- لديه سر. - عندما كان هو دونغ يتحدث،
he kept his face forward and rolled his eyes down.
أبقى وجهه إلى الأمام وأدار عينيه إلى الأسفل.
- You know... - It's his secret,
- كما تعلم... - إنه سره،
- so he has become nervous. - I think she's right.
- لذلك أصبح عصبيا. - أعتقد أنها على حق.
This is like the Mafia Game.
هذه مثل لعبة المافيا.
He's terrible at games.
إنه فظيع في الألعاب.
He isn't saying a thing right now.
إنه لا يقول شيئًا في الوقت الحالي.
He's usually a big flippant.
عادة ما يكون وقحا كبيرا.
- Seon Min... - I'll ask him outright.
- سيون مين... - سأسأله بصراحة.
Seon Min, is that your secret?
سيون مين، هل هذا سرك؟
I've had big breasts since childhood.
لقد كان لدي ثديين كبيرين منذ الطفولة.
Do you know why?
هل تعرف لماذا؟
I have three older sisters.
لدي ثلاث أخوات أكبر مني.
There were four bras at home.
كان هناك أربع حمالات صدر في المنزل.
- Hey. - I've always had big breasts.
- يا. - لقد كان لدي دائما ثديين كبيرين.
- Don't lie.
- لقد كان لدي دائما ثديين كبيرين. - لا تكذب.
- The explanation makes it certain. - Your sisters each needed...
- والتفسير يجعل من المؤكد. - أخواتك كل حاجة...
- at least two bras for washing. - That's right.
- صدريتين على الأقل للغسيل. - هذا صحيح.
From the beginning of the shoot,
منذ بداية التصوير،
Seon Min has rested his breasts on the table.
أراح Seon Min ثدييه على الطاولة.
(Joke Battle doesn't rest for a second.)
(نكتة المعركة لا تهدأ لثانية واحدة.)
I'm serious. Check the recorded video.
أنا جادة. تحقق من الفيديو المسجل.
- From the start, he has done that. - If you keep doing this,
- منذ البداية، لقد فعل ذلك. - إذا واصلت فعل هذا،
you'll get penalty points.
سوف تحصل على نقاط الجزاء.
Hold on. By next year, I’ll have been...
يتمسك. بحلول العام المقبل، سأكون...
- swimming for four years. - You've swum for a long time.
- السباحة لمدة أربع سنوات. - لقد سبحت لفترة طويلة.
I've noticed some things...
لقد لاحظت بعض الأشياء..
- because men only wear swim briefs. - Right.
- لأن الرجال يرتدون ملابس السباحة فقط. - يمين.
People who look like him have big breasts.
الأشخاص الذين يشبهونه لديهم أثداء كبيرة.
- They do. - But do they keep getting bigger?
- يفعلون. - ولكن هل يستمرون في التزايد؟
- Exactly. - I've always had big breasts.
- بالضبط. - لقد كان لدي دائما ثديين كبيرين.
- Now, they've become muscular. - I think it's Sang Min.
- الآن، لقد أصبحوا العضلات. - أعتقد أنه سانغ مين.
- No. - I think it's Beom.
- لا. - أعتقد أنه بيوم.
- Beom? - Ho Dong...
- بيوم؟ - هو دونغ...
- I don't mind having big breasts. - Jae Youl thinks it's Beom.
- لا أمانع أن يكون لدي ثديين كبيرين. - جاي يول يعتقد أنه بيوم.
His hormone levels might've changed...
ربما تغيرت مستويات الهرمون لديه...
- due to vasectomy. - That's right.
- بسبب استئصال الأسهر. - هذا صحيح.
- You're right. - It's connected.
- أنت على حق. - إنه متصل.
- He gets a lot of female hormones. - I asked the doctor about it.
- يحصل على الكثير من الهرمونات الأنثوية. - سألت الطبيب عن ذلك.
He said it was completely unrelated.
وقال إنه لا علاقة له على الإطلاق.
But if I consider the facts,
ولكن إذا نظرت إلى الحقائق،
- it's Beom. - That's right.
- إنها بيوم. - هذا صحيح.
I'm used to seeing everyone's face.
أنا معتاد على رؤية وجوه الجميع.
Beom gained the most amount of fat in his face.
اكتسب بيوم أكبر قدر من الدهون في وجهه.
- People with such a face... - That's right.
- الأشخاص الذين لديهم مثل هذا الوجه... - هذا صحيح.
- Yes. - People with such a face... Yes.
- نعم. - الأشخاص الذين لديهم مثل هذا الوجه... نعم.
I bet his breasts got bigger as he gained weight.
أراهن أن ثدييه أصبحا أكبر مع زيادة وزنه.
- Beom's face was half the size. - That's right.
- كان وجه بيوم نصف حجمه. - هذا صحيح.
Your body increases with your face.
جسمك يزيد مع وجهك.
- It's Beom. - I...
- إنها بيوم. - أنا...
- I mean... - Listen.
- يعني... - اسمع.
Beom is the culprit!
بيوم هو الجاني!
But the secret implies that it's a recent event.
لكن السر يوحي بأنه حدث حديث.
- Beom and I... - I gained weight many years ago.
- بيوم وأنا... - لقد زاد وزني منذ سنوات عديدة.
- Isn't it Kyung Hoon? - I personally think...
- أليس كيونغ هون؟ - أنا شخصيا أعتقد...
this secret belongs to someone...
هذا السر ينتمي إلى شخص ما.
who is the most bothered by this secret.
من هو الأكثر انزعاجا من هذا السر.
- I think it's you. - I think it's Yeong Cheol.
- أعتقد أنه أنت. - أعتقد أنه يونغ تشيول.
- Me? - The crew would've taken out...
- أنا؟ - الطاقم كان سيخرج...
Yeong Cheol's secret.
سر يونغ تشيول.
- Really? - They would've taken it out.
- حقًا؟ - لقد كانوا سيخرجونه.
- Why... - Yeong Cheol's secret...
- لماذا... - سر يونغ تشيول...
wouldn't have been the first question.
لن يكون السؤال الأول.
I see.
أرى.
- I think... - Why are you analyzing it?
- أعتقد... - لماذا تقوم بتحليله؟
- it's Sang Min. - It must be Sang Min.
- إنه سانغ مين. - يجب أن يكون سانغ مين.
Kyung Hoon, haven't your hormone levels changed...
كيونغ هون، ألم تتغير مستويات الهرمون لديك...
- since marriage? - No, not at all.
- منذ الزواج؟ - لا، على الإطلاق.
Didn't he release "Sin..."
ألم يطلق "الخطيئة..."
because his breasts became bigger?
لأن ثدييه أصبحا أكبر؟
- Why would I feel guilty about it? - Sin of having bigger breasts.
- ولماذا أشعر بالذنب حيال ذلك؟ - خطيئة كبر حجم الثديين.
- Is it Kyung Hoon? - Then...
- هل هو كيونغ هون؟ - ثم...
- If we call your name... - It isn't me.
- إذا نادينا اسمك... - ليس أنا.
Let me say this once more. It isn't me.
اسمحوا لي أن أقول هذا مرة أخرى. هذا ليس أنا.
- My breasts aren't big. - Okay.
- ثديي ليست كبيرة. - تمام.
Beom and I went to a urology clinic together.
ذهبت أنا وبيوم إلى عيادة المسالك البولية معًا.
After checking his hormones, the urologist told me...
وبعد فحص الهرمونات قال لي طبيب المسالك البولية...
to call Beom "Big Sister" on Mondays, Wednesdays, and Fridays.
للاتصال بيوم "الأخت الكبرى" أيام الاثنين والأربعاء والجمعة.
Same here.
نفس الشيء هنا.
(Beom's testosterone levels drop every other day.)
(تنخفض مستويات هرمون التستوستيرون لدى بيوم كل يوم).
He gets too much female hormones these days.
يحصل على الكثير من الهرمونات الأنثوية هذه الأيام.
What day is it? It's Thursday. It isn't me.
ما هو اليوم؟ إنه الخميس. هذا ليس أنا.
- One at a time. - We'll go first.
- واحدة في وقت واحد. - سنذهب أولا.
- I... - What do you personally think?
- أنا... - ما رأيك شخصيا؟
I initially thought it was Sang Min.
اعتقدت في البداية أنه كان سانغ مين.
But I ended up changing my mind.
لكن انتهى بي الأمر إلى تغيير رأيي.
- Kwak Beom. - Kwak Beom received a vote.
- كواك بيوم. - حصل كواك بيوم على التصويت.
- Sang Gook, do you agree?
- كواك بيوم. - سانغ جوك، هل توافق؟
- Team Hey chooses Kwak Beom. - Okay.
- فريق Hey يختار Kwak Beom. - تمام.
Say it with ease.
قل ذلك بكل سهولة.
I also think it's Kwak Beom.
وأعتقد أيضا أنه كواك بيوم.
Kwak Beom is suddenly getting all the votes.
حصل Kwak Beom فجأة على جميع الأصوات.
Beom usually has a muscular body,
بيوم عادة ما يكون له جسم عضلي،
but he hasn't worked out much recently.
لكنه لم يتدرب كثيرًا مؤخرًا.
So there's a chance of him getting bigger breasts.
لذلك هناك فرصة له للحصول على ثديين أكبر.
- He helped because it was Seon Min. - Right.
- لقد ساعد لأنه كان سيون مين. - يمين.
- That's right. - It could be Seon Min.
- هذا صحيح. - يمكن أن يكون سيون مين.
The person I'm jealous of...
الشخص الذي أغار منه...
is Seon Min.
هو سيون مين.
Seon Min received two votes.
حصل سيون مين على صوتين.
- I choose Seon Min. - Seon Min.
- اخترت سيون مين. - سيون مين.
It isn't me. It really isn't me.
هذا ليس أنا. انها حقا ليست لي.
We've just reached the same decision.
لقد توصلنا للتو إلى نفس القرار.
- Okay. - We've chosen the same person.
- تمام. - لقد اخترنا نفس الشخص.
- Seon Min.
- سيون مين. - سيون مين.
- Seon Min received more votes. - Now...
- حصل سيون مين على المزيد من الأصوات. - الآن...
- I feel like...
- أشعر بأن... - أشعر بأن...
- it's Beom. - Now, things have become certain.
- إنها بيوم. - الآن أصبحت الأمور مؤكدة.
Had the two of them...
كان اثنان منهم...
Had Beom's team not chosen Seon Min, I would've decided otherwise.
لو لم يختر فريق بيوم سيون مين، كنت سأقرر خلاف ذلك.
I'm certain it's Beom.
أنا متأكد من أنه بيوم.
- I choose Beom. - By the look of things...
- اخترت بيوم. - بنظر الأشياء..
After all, he was especially excited about this game.
بعد كل شيء، كان متحمسًا بشكل خاص لهذه اللعبة.
- Okay. - Big breasts are a funny topic.
- تمام. - الصدور الكبيرة موضوع مضحك.
So it's Beom.
إذن فهو بيوم.
- Yeong Cheol gave big reactions. - I don't have big breasts.
- أعطى يونغ تشيول ردود فعل كبيرة. - ليس لدي ثديين كبيرين.
Beom, I'm sorry,
بيوم، أنا آسف،
- but stop touching your breasts. - I know.
- لكن توقفي عن لمس ثدييك. - أنا أعرف.
You're touching them too much.
أنت تلمسهم كثيرًا.
I think it's Seon Min.
أعتقد أنه سيون مين.
- Okay. - Seon Min.
- تمام. - سيون مين.
- It's 6 to 4. - It isn't me.
- إنها الساعة 6 إلى 4. - لست أنا.
I think it's Beom.
أعتقد أنه بيوم.
- Gosh, Seon Min. - After all, it isn't me.
- يا إلهي، سيون مين. - في النهاية، ليس أنا.
I choose Hee Chul.
اخترت هي تشول.
Hee Chul.
هي تشول.
- I can't believe it. - He's obsessed with Hee Chul.
- لا أستطيع أن أصدق ذلك. - إنه مهووس بهي تشول.
Hee Chul wouldn't reveal a secret like that.
هي تشول لن يكشف سرًا كهذا.
All votes have been cast.
تم الإدلاء بجميع الأصوات.
Beom received 5 votes, Seon Min received 6 votes,
بيوم حصل على 5 أصوات، وسيون مين حصل على 6 أصوات،
and Hee Chul received 1 vote. After the 1st vote,
وحصل هي تشول على صوت واحد. بعد التصويت الأول
- Seon Min has been chosen. - I'm so curious.
- تم اختيار سيون مين. - أنا فضولي جدا.
- We'll kill him off right away. - All right.
- سوف نقتله على الفور. - حسنًا.
Is Seon Min the one...
هل سيون مين هو...
behind the secret?
وراء السر؟
Whose breasts keep getting bigger?
من الذي يستمر في زيادة حجم ثدييه؟
Seon Min...
سيون مين ...
(Did those who voted for Seon Min choose correctly?)
(هل أولئك الذين صوتوا لصالح سيون مين اختاروا بشكل صحيح؟)
isn't the one.
ليس هو واحد.
Seon Min isn't the one.
سيون مين ليس هو الشخص.
- I told you it wasn't me. - Is it Beom?
- قلت لك أنه ليس أنا. - هل هو بيوم؟
- That's right. - It isn't me.
- هذا صحيح. - ليس أنا.
Seon Min and Sang Min are out.
سيون مين وسانغ مين خارجا.
- So Sang Min isn't the one either. - All right.
- إذن سانغ مين ليس هو الشخص أيضًا. - حسنًا.
Seon Min's secret isn't...
سر سيون مين ليس...
"My breasts keep getting bigger."
"ثديي يستمر في التزايد."
It's "I wet my bed until third grade."
إنه "لقد بللت سريري حتى الصف الثالث"
(Seon Min's secret: I wet my bed until 3rd grade.)
(سر سيون مين: لقد بللت سريري حتى الصف الثالث.)
His secret got revealed.
لقد تم الكشف عن سره.
- Did I have to reveal my secret? - Hold on.
- هل كان عليّ أن أكشف سري؟ - يتمسك.
- What's up with the rules? - Why did you reveal it?
- ما الأمر مع القواعد؟ - لماذا كشفت ذلك؟
Hold on. Third grade in which school?
يتمسك. الصف الثالث في اي مدرسة ؟
- This is bad for me. - Why did you reveal it?
- وهذا أمر سيء بالنسبة لي. - لماذا كشفت ذلك؟
- College or high school? - Third year in college?
- الكلية أو المدرسة الثانوية؟ - السنة الثالثة في الكلية؟
- No.
- السنة الثالثة في الكلية؟ - لا.
- High school. - Summer Bible camp.
- المدرسة الثانوية. - معسكر الكتاب المقدس الصيفي.
- Not college. - Third year in college?
- ليست جامعية. - السنة الثالثة في الكلية؟
- All third graders wet their beds.
- جميع طلاب الصف الثالث يبللون أسرتهم. - السنة الثالثة في الكلية؟
- Did he wet his bed in his 20s? - Seon Min is out,
- هل بلل سريره في العشرينات من عمره؟ - سيون مين خارج،
- so he can't speak. - You can't speak.
- لذلك لا يستطيع الكلام. - لا يمكنك التحدث.
You wet your pants!
لقد بللت سروالك!
- He changed his pants. - Why do you pee so much?
- قام بتغيير سرواله. - لماذا تتبول كثيرا؟
- He wet his bed until 12th grade?
- كان يبلل سريره حتى الصف الثاني عشر؟ - لماذا تتبول كثيرا؟
I bet he was stressed out about CSAT.
أراهن أنه كان متوترًا بشأن CSAT.
That explains why he wet his bed until 12th grade.
وهذا يفسر سبب تبليله في فراشه حتى الصف الثاني عشر.
You lost your chance to receive 20 points.
لقد فقدت فرصتك في الحصول على 20 نقطة.
- It's the worst secret. - Now, five teams...
- إنه أسوأ سر. - الآن، خمسة فرق...
will have another round for ten points.
سيكون لها جولة أخرى لعشر نقاط.
Should we kill off Beom?
هل يجب أن نقتل بيوم؟
- No, it really isn't me. - It might be Jae Youl.
- لا، هذا ليس أنا حقا. - قد يكون جاي يول.
- His body is strange these days. - Jae Youl.
- جسمه غريب هذه الأيام. - جاي يول.
- It isn't him. - He's a bit...
- ليس هو. - هو قليلاً...
- I'm skin and bones. - Isn't Beom the most likely?
- أنا جلد وعظام. - أليس بيوم هو الأرجح؟
The vote was 6 to 5.
وجاء التصويت بأغلبية 6 مقابل 5.
- Recently, I gained more weight... - Soo Geun.
- مؤخرًا، اكتسبت وزنًا أكبر... - سو جيون.
- and lost some. - I think it's Soo Geun.
- وفقدت بعض. - أعتقد أنه سو جيون.
- Soo Geun keeps attacking people. - He's someone...
- يستمر Soo Geun في مهاجمة الناس. - هو شخص...
Yes, he keeps attacking people.
نعم، فهو يواصل مهاجمة الناس.
He's also someone...
وهو أيضاً شخص...
who doesn't hesitate to share a secret like this.
الذي لا يتردد في مشاركة سر مثل هذا.
Take a look, you punk!
نلقي نظرة، أنت فاسق!
Do they look bigger, you punk?
هل تبدو أكبر، أيها الشرير؟
(Observing)
(المراقبة)
(I saw his nipples.)
(رأيت حلماته.)
I saw them up close.
رأيتهم عن قرب.
- How could you pick me? - Here's what I think.
- كيف يمكنك أن تختارني؟ - وهذا ما أعتقده.
Hey, I'm annoyed that I didn't become taller.
مهلا، أنا منزعج لأنني لم أصبح أطول.
How could you say that my breasts became bigger?
كيف يمكنك القول أن ثديي أصبح أكبر؟
Hey.
يا.
When I turned around, I came face-to-face with his nipples.
عندما استدرت، واجهت حلماته وجهاً لوجه.
If I get bigger breasts with this body,
إذا حصلت على ثديين أكبر مع هذا الجسم،
it'll be the absolute worst.
سيكون الأسوأ على الإطلاق.
Right? It'll be the absolute worst.
يمين؟ سيكون الأسوأ على الإطلاق.
"Take a look, you punk!"
"ألقِ نظرة أيها الشرير!"
- I saw them up close. It isn't him. - I mean...
- رأيتهم عن قرب. إنه ليس هو. - أعني...
- It isn't him. - Listen.
- ليس هو. - يستمع.
- I stared for three seconds. - You know...
- حدقت لمدة ثلاث ثوان. - أنت تعرف...
Let's take this approach.
دعونا نتبع هذا النهج.
- Let's go over Jae Youl's words. - I think it's Jae Youl.
- دعنا نراجع كلمات جاي يول. - أعتقد أنه جاي يول.
"The doctor told me to call Beom 'Big Sister...'"
"أخبرني الطبيب أن أنادي بيوم بالأخت الكبرى..."
"on Mondays, Wednesdays,"
"في أيام الاثنين والأربعاء"
- "and Fridays." - That's right.
- "والجمعة." - هذا صحيح.
"He gets a lot of female hormones."
"إنه يحصل على الكثير من الهرمونات الأنثوية."
He wouldn't know those words unless he heard them himself.
لن يعرف هذه الكلمات إلا إذا سمعها بنفسه.
(Perhaps Jae Youl went to get a checkup on his hormones.)
(ربما ذهب جاي يول لإجراء فحص هرموناته).
Perhaps he got his hormones checked out recently...
ربما قام بفحص هرموناته مؤخرًا ...
and found a problem.
ووجدت مشكلة.
No. When I received a checkup,
لا، عندما تلقيت فحصًا طبيًا،
- my male hormone level was 9.8. - It was 8.3.
- مستوى الهرمون الذكري كان 9.8. - كان 8.3.
- Really? - You punk!
- حقًا؟ - أنت فاسق!
(His testosterone level makes Ho Dong's jaw drop.)
(مستوى هرمون التستوستيرون لديه يجعل هو دونغ يسقط الفك.)
(How could he doubt my mele hormone level?)
(كيف يمكن أن يشك في مستوى هرمون الميل الخاص بي؟)
- Hit his philtrum. - He has too much testosterone.
- ضرب النثرة له. - لديه الكثير من هرمون التستوستيرون.
Don't do that to my friend!
لا تفعل ذلك لصديقي!
- Don't do that to my friend! - Look at Sang Gook's breasts.
- لا تفعل ذلك لصديقي! - انظر إلى ثديي سانغ جوك.
- His breasts.
- انظر إلى ثديي سانغ جوك. - ثدييه.
Look at his breasts.
انظر إلى ثدييه.
Say that it isn't your secret. It'll be nasty.
قل أن هذا ليس سرك. سيكون الأمر سيئًا.
- He's skinny. - Take turns.
- انه نحيف. - يتناوبون.
- Rude Juniors, go first. - He takes off his top often.
- رود جونيورز، اذهب أولاً. - يخلع قميصه كثيرًا.
Shall we go the other way?
هل يجب أن نذهب في الاتجاه الآخر؟
I choose Beom.
اخترت بيوم.
- I think it's him. - One vote for Beom.
- أعتقد أنه هو. - صوت واحد لبيوم.
All right, Jae Youl.
حسنًا، جاي يول.
- It's Jae Youl. - I also choose Beom.
- إنه جاي يول. - أنا أيضا أختار بيوم.
- Right now... - I'm certain it's Jae Youl.
- الآن... - أنا متأكد من أنه جاي يول.
- Jae Youl.
- جاي يول. - جاي يول.
- Yes. - No.
- نعم. - لا.
- I still choose Beom. - It has to be Jae Youl.
- مازلت أختار بيوم. - يجب أن يكون جاي يول.
That's right. Beom.
هذا صحيح. بيوم.
Beom.
بيوم.
I choose Beom.
اخترت بيوم.
- Beom. - That's right.
- بيوم. - هذا صحيح.
At this point...
عند هذه النقطة...
I also choose Beom.
أنا أيضا أختار بيوم.
I'll go with my initial hunch.
سأذهب مع حدسي الأولي.
No matter the current size, I think it's him.
بغض النظر عن الحجم الحالي، أعتقد أنه هو.
- That's right. - Yes.
- هذا صحيح. - نعم.
- Beom. - One vote for Beom.
- بيوم. - صوت واحد لبيوم.
When we became suspicious, he kept attacking...
عندما اشتبهنا به، استمر في الهجوم...
- other people. - That's right.
- أشخاص آخرين. - هذا صحيح.
I choose Jae Youl.
اخترت جاي يول.
(Yeong Cheol chooses Jae Youl.)
(يونج تشيول يختار جاي يول.)
- See? He's protecting Beom. - It must be Beom.
- يرى؟ إنه يحمي بيوم. - يجب أن يكون بيوم.
- It's Beom. - That's right.
- إنها بيوم. - هذا صحيح.
No matter what I say, I'll get chosen.
بغض النظر عما أقوله، سيتم اختياري.
- It's bound to happen.
- هذا صحيح. - لا بد أن يحدث.
Kwak Beom.
كواك بيوم.
(Kwak Beom chooses Kwak Beom.)
(كواك بيوم يختار كواك بيوم.)
- Did Beom get all the votes? - If it's...
- هل حصل بيوم على كل الأصوات؟ - إذا كان...
- Beom... - It isn't me. Look at the crew.
- بيوم... - ليس أنا. انظر إلى الطاقم.
That's right.
هذا صحيح.
All teams except for the eliminated team...
جميع الفرق باستثناء الفريق المستبعد..
will get ten points.
سوف تحصل على عشر نقاط.
If it isn't Beom,
إذا لم يكن بيوم،
and someone else is behind the secret,
وشخص آخر وراء السر،
that team will receive 30 points...
سيحصل هذا الفريق على 30 نقطة.
for keeping the secret until the end.
لحفظ السر حتى النهاية.
It'll be incredible if we receive 30 points.
سيكون أمرًا لا يصدق إذا حصلنا على 30 نقطة.
Oh, my! What will you do if we receive 30 points?
يا بلدي! ماذا ستفعل إذا حصلنا على 30 نقطة؟
(Is the excited Team Hey the one behind the secret?)
(هل الفريق المتحمس هو الذي يقف وراء السر؟)
- No way. - Let's have a get-together then.
- مستحيل. - دعونا نجتمع بعد ذلك.
If we get...
اذا حصلنا...
- thirty points... - Whose breasts keep getting bigger?
- ثلاثون نقطة... - من الذي يستمر في كبر حجم ثدييه؟
Kwak Beom...
كواك بيوم...
(Is it Beom, the "Big Sister" on Mondays, Wednesdays, and Fridays?)
(هل هي بيوم، "الأخت الكبرى" أيام الاثنين والأربعاء والجمعة؟)
is the one.
هو واحد.
(Kwak Beom is the one whose breasts keep getting bigger!)
(كواك بيوم هو الذي يستمر ثدييه في الكبر!)
My initial hunch was correct.
كان حدسي الأولي صحيحا.
That's right.
هذا صحيح.
Are your breasts getting bigger?
هل أصبح ثدييك أكبر؟
(Since the moment his partner, Yeong Cheol, learned the secret)
(منذ اللحظة التي علم فيها شريكه يونج تشيول بالسر)
(Really?)
(حقًا؟)
(They kept attacking others from the back row.)
(لقد استمروا في مهاجمة الآخرين من الصف الخلفي).
(His breasts look strange.)
(ثدييه تبدو غريبة.)
(He was talking about himself.)
(كان يتحدث عن نفسه).
- Really? - Even if I lose weight...
- حقًا؟ - حتى لو نقص وزني..
- It happens if you gain weight. - Since I'm over 40,
- يحدث إذا زاد وزنك. - وبما أني تجاوزت الأربعين من عمري،
I get these lumps...
أحصل على هذه الكتل ...
around my nipples.
حول حلماتي.
- You get lumps. - Yes. My breasts get bigger.
- تحصل على كتل. - نعم. ثديي يكبر.
- My initial hunch was right. - So...
- حدسي الأولي كان صحيحا. - لذا...
back in the day, I didn't put on nipple patches...
في الماضي، لم أضع رقعة على الحلمة...
when I wore a denim shirt.
عندما ارتديت قميص الدنيم.
My nipples stuck out despite wearing a vest, so I put them on.
كانت حلماتي بارزتين على الرغم من ارتدائي سترة، لذلك ارتديتهما.
Is it because of vasectomy?
هل هو بسبب استئصال الأسهر؟
- That was funny. - Are you interested in it?
- كان ذلك مضحكا. - هل أنت مهتم به؟
- Hee Chul might need it. - Beom is the man whose secret is...
- هيي تشول قد يحتاجها. - بيوم هو الرجل الذي سره هو...
having the breasts that keep getting bigger.
وجود ثديين يكبران باستمرار.
- Many people suspected Jae Youl. - Okay.
- كثير من الناس يشتبهون في جاي يول. - تمام.
Jae Youl's secret is similar, but different.
سر جاي يول مشابه، لكنه مختلف.
It's "I don't have much space between my nipples."
إنه "ليس لدي مساحة كبيرة بين حلماتي."
(Men on a Mission has diverse breasts today.)
(الرجال في مهمة لديهم ثديين متنوعين اليوم.)
I see.
أرى.
- They're very close together. - They're like this.
- إنهم قريبون جدًا من بعضهم البعض. - إنهم هكذا.
The man no one suspected,
الرجل الذي لم يشك فيه أحد
Sang Gook's secret is...
سر سانغ جوك هو...
"I trim all of my body hair."
"أقوم بقص شعر جسمي كله."
Do you do it yourself?
هل تفعل ذلك بنفسك؟
- You groom yourself well. - With a razor?
- أنت تعتني بنفسك جيدًا. - بشفرة الحلاقة؟
- I don't have a lot of hair. - Okay.
- ليس لدي الكثير من الشعر. - تمام.
Since there's only a bit, I either pluck it or...
وبما أنه لا يوجد سوى القليل، فإما أن أقتطفه أو...
- With scissors? - Do you mean your armpit hair?
- بالمقص؟ - هل تقصدين شعر الإبط؟
I trim my body hair myself.
أقوم بقص شعر جسمي بنفسي
I guess you can't stand it.
أعتقد أنك لا تستطيع الوقوف عليه.
I only have a few strands,
ليس لدي سوى عدد قليل من الخيوط ،
- so it's unsightly. - I see.
- لذلك فهو قبيح. - أرى.
I only have a few strands.
ليس لدي سوى عدد قليل من الخيوط.
Bong Sun's secret is...
سر بونغ صن هو...
- "I've come to have..." - It happens.
- "لقد جئت لأحصل على..." - يحدث ذلك.
"a hobby I can't talk about."
"هواية لا أستطيع التحدث عنها"
- What? I'm curious. - What do you mean?
- ماذا؟ أنا فضولي. - ماذا تقصد؟
I've come to have...
جئت لأملك...
a hobby I can't talk about anywhere.
هواية لا أستطيع التحدث عنها في أي مكان.
When I talk about it, people don't respond favorably.
عندما أتحدث عن ذلك، الناس لا يستجيبون بشكل إيجابي.
- Do they become awkward? - You can tell us.
- هل يصبحون محرجين؟ - يمكنك أن تخبرنا.
- What is it? - I do it with seriousness.
- ما هذا؟ - أفعل ذلك بكل جدية.
- Do you play hwatu? - These days,
- هل تلعب الحواتو؟ - هذه الأيام،
I learn ballet.
أنا أتعلم الباليه.
- I see. - Ballet.
- أرى. - الباليه.
- It's in vogue these days. - Many people learn it.
- إنها رائجة هذه الأيام. - كثير من الناس يتعلمونها.
- Why do you keep it a secret?
- إنها رائجة هذه الأيام. - لماذا تبقي الأمر سرا؟
- Doesn't Yeong Cheol learn it? - I don't know.
- ألا يتعلم يونغ تشول ذلك؟ - لا أعرف.
When I say that I take ballet lessons, people laugh.
عندما أقول إنني أتلقى دروس الباليه، يضحك الناس.
Before the shoot, Bong Sun told me that she was taking ballet lessons.
قبل التصوير، أخبرتني بونج صن أنها كانت تتلقى دروسًا في الباليه.
I heard it as "valet."
سمعت ذلك باسم "خادم".
(Her hobby is valet parking.)
(هوايتها هي خدمة صف السيارات.)
That's why she can't talk about it.
لهذا السبب لا يمكنها التحدث عن ذلك.
I try not to stand at the entrance of a building.
أحاول ألا أقف عند مدخل المبنى.
Strangers keep giving me their car keys.
الغرباء يستمرون بإعطائي مفاتيح سيارتهم
If you do valet parking,
إذا كنت تقوم بخدمة صف السيارات،
can you park some cars in front of Seon Min's place?
هل يمكنك ركن بعض السيارات أمام منزل سيون مين؟
I'll give it a go.
سأجربها.
Do you know what's amazing about ballet?
هل تعرف ما هو المدهش في الباليه؟
- It improves your posture. - Show us.
- أنه يحسن الموقف الخاص بك. - تبين لنا.
You have bad circulation at this age, right?
لديك الدورة الدموية السيئة في هذا العمر، أليس كذلك؟
- Strike a pose. - Show us.
- اضرب وقفة. - تبين لنا.
- Then...
- ثم... - تبين لنا.
- Show us ballet. - I can't show you ballet.
- تبين لنا الباليه. - لا أستطيع أن أريك الباليه.
I brought these pants for a reason.
أحضرت هذه السراويل لسبب ما.
I've become flexible.
لقد أصبحت مرنة.
- How many months has it been? - About four month.
- كم شهر مضى؟ - حوالي أربعة أشهر.
It has been about four months.
لقد كان حوالي أربعة أشهر.
I bet you can stretch well in those pants.
أراهن أنك يمكن أن تمتد بشكل جيد في تلك السراويل.
We've filmed this show for about ten years.
لقد قمنا بتصوير هذا العرض لمدة عشر سنوات تقريبًا.
It's our first time seeing someone put on pants in the classroom.
إنها المرة الأولى التي نرى فيها شخصًا يرتدي بنطالًا في الفصل الدراسي.
No one is saying a thing.
لا أحد يقول شيئا.
- You look like my aunt. - I...
- أنت تشبه عمتي. - أنا...
I've become...
لقد أصبحت...
- very flexible. - Will your legs go up?
- مرنة للغاية. - هل سترتفع ساقيك؟
- Watch. - Go ahead.
- يشاهد. - تفضل.
(Stretching)
(تمتد)
- I can do this as well. - You've become very flexible.
- أستطيع أن أفعل هذا أيضا. - لقد أصبحت مرنة للغاية.
(She makes a perfectly straight line.)
(إنها ترسم خطًا مستقيمًا تمامًا.)
It's important to keep upright.
من المهم أن تبقى في وضع مستقيم.
- Do ballet. - Isn't she flexible?
- مارسي الباليه. - أليست مرنة؟
- My goodness. - Impressive.
- يا إلهي. - بديع.
- I can send my legs back. - Are you serious?
- أستطيع أن أرسل ساقي مرة أخرى. - هل أنت جاد؟
Did ballet make you flexible? Have you always been flexible?
هل الباليه يجعلك مرنة؟ هل كنت دائما مرنة؟
- I've always been flexible, but... - Lie on your stomach again.
- لقد كنت دائمًا مرنًا، لكن... - استلقي على بطنك مرة أخرى.
She has always been flexible.
لقد كانت دائما مرنة.
- You seemed like a water strider. - Really?
- لقد بدوت وكأنك راكب الماء. - حقًا؟
You're like an idol.
أنت مثل المعبود.
- Yes. So... - That's incredible.
- نعم. إذن... - هذا أمر لا يصدق.
(Bong Sun stretches her body like rubber.)
(تمد بونج صن جسدها مثل المطاط.)
- All right. - My grandma...
- حسنًا. - جدتي...
plays hwatu in that pose.
يلعب هواتو في تلك الوضعية.
(The genre changes naturally.)
(يتغير النوع بشكل طبيعي.)
- No one will sit next to her. - I'll do this...
- لن يجلس أحد بجانبها. - سأفعل هذا...
when I win money.
عندما أربح المال.
- You're good. - That's right. You've won money.
- أنت جيدة أو أنت طيب. - هذا صحيح. لقد فزت بالمال.
You're good. You're like my grandma.
أنت جيدة أو أنت طيب. أنت مثل جدتي.
- She's playing cards. - It's 30 cents each.
- إنها تلعب الورق. - إنها 30 سنتا لكل منهما.
- You've become very flexible. - Yes.
- لقد أصبحت مرنة للغاية. - نعم.
- So... - Put one leg on Sang Gook.
- إذن... - ضع ساقًا واحدة على سانغ جوك.
Sang Gook, do you want to help?
سانغ جوك، هل تريد المساعدة؟
- But Sang Gook... - Sang Gook is tall.
- لكن سانغ جوك... - سانغ جوك طويل.
- Hit his mouth to be funny. - Then...
- ضرب فمه ليكون مضحكا. - ثم...
sit down and get up slowly.
الجلوس والاستيقاظ ببطء.
Hit his mouth to be funny, Bong Sun.
اضرب فمه ليكون مضحكا، بونج صن.
That's right.
هذا صحيح.
(She puts one foot on him.)
(تضع قدماً واحدة عليه.)
(The atmosphere turns sexy.)
(الجو يتحول إلى مثير.)
They're hugging.
إنهم يتعانقون.
(Do you honestly want to captivate me as a man?)
(هل تريد بصدق أن تأسرني كرجل؟)
(But trust me when I say you've always been charming.)
(لكن ثق بي عندما أقول أنك كنت ساحرًا دائمًا.)
(The man and the woman become very close.)
(الرجل والمرأة أصبحا قريبين جدًا.)
(Will they finally realize the old love?)
(هل سيدركون أخيرًا الحب القديم؟)
They're hugging.
إنهم يتعانقون.
(Do you honestly want to captivate me as a man?)
(هل تريد بصدق أن تأسرني كرجل؟)
(But trust me when I say you've always been charming.)
(لكن ثق بي عندما أقول أنك كنت ساحرًا دائمًا.)
(The man and the woman become very close.)
(الرجل والمرأة أصبحا قريبين جدًا.)
(Will they finally realize the old love?)
(هل سيدركون أخيرًا الحب القديم؟)
(Bong Sun and Sang Gook can't stop hopping.)
(لا يستطيع بونج صن وسانج جوك التوقف عن القفز.)
- It's like a pogo stick. - What's this?
- إنها مثل عصا البوجو. - ما هذا؟
(Thus, the two of them made people laugh forever and ever.)
(فأضحك الاثنان الناس إلى الأبد).
What a perfect ending.
يا لها من نهاية مثالية.
Now, I'll announce the final winner.
والآن سأعلن عن الفائز النهائي.
We have co-winners.
لدينا فائزين مشاركين.
Two teams have the same score.
فريقان لديهم نفس النتيجة.
They're Team Sun Bong Jang and Team Rude Juniors.
إنهم فريق صن بونج جانج وفريق رود جونيورز.
(Final winners, Team Sun Bong Jang and Team Rude Juniors)
(الفائزان النهائيان، فريق سون بونج جانج وفريق رود جونيورز)
We did well.
لقد قمنا بعمل جيد.
(They do a ceremony of happiness.)
(يقيمون حفل السعادة.)
(Dancing)
(الرقص)
Do you want to put one leg up?
هل تريد وضع ساق واحدة؟
Put one leg up.
ضع ساق واحدة للأعلى.
(An encore ballet performance...)
(عرض باليه جديد...)
(becomes a hopping performance again.)
(يصبح أداء القفز مرة أخرى.)
There you go.
ها أنت ذا.
Do you want to put one leg up?
هل تريد وضع ساق واحدة؟
Put one leg up.
ضع ساق واحدة للأعلى.
(An encore ballet performance...)
(عرض باليه جديد...)
(becomes a hopping performance again.)
(يصبح أداء القفز مرة أخرى.)
There you go.
ها أنت ذا.
Okay.
تمام.
(Collapsing)
(انهيار)
Are you okay?
هل أنت بخير؟
(It was a gala show of the enthusiastic joke medalists.)
(لقد كان عرضًا احتفاليًا للحائزين على ميداليات النكتة المتحمسين.)
- How was it today? - Please take turns...
- كيف كان اليوم؟ - الرجاء التناوب...
- to talk about your experience. - Seon Min.
- للحديث عن تجربتك. - سيون مين.
It was an honor to meet the celebrities...
لقد كان شرفاً لي أن ألتقي بالمشاهير..
I've only seen on TV.
لقد رأيت فقط على شاشة التلفزيون.
If there's a good chance,
إذا كانت هناك فرصة جيدة،
- I'd like to come back and play. - Okay.
- أود أن أعود واللعب. - تمام.
- You were the best. - Let's go.
- كنت الأفضل. - دعنا نذهب.
I had fun.
لقد استمتعت.
- We had fun.
- لقد استمتعنا. - لقد استمتعنا.
I had a quick visit last time.
لقد قمت بزيارة سريعة آخر مرة.
- When we played soccer. - This time,
- عندما لعبنا كرة القدم. - هذه المرة،
I stayed throughout the shoot.
وبقيت طوال فترة التصوير.
So I had more fun.
لذلك كان لدي المزيد من المرح.
I hope the viewers will be entertained as well.
وآمل أن يكون المشاهدون مستمتعين أيضًا.
I had so much fun.
لقد استمتعت كثيرا.
- Next, Jae Youl. - All right.
- التالي، جاي يول. - حسنًا.
Among the shoots I've had recently,
من بين اللقطات التي قمت بها مؤخرًا،
- this one was the most fun. - Of course.
- كان هذا هو الأكثر متعة. - بالطبع.
I want to work hard and be like the Men on a Mission members.
أريد أن أعمل بجد وأن أكون مثل أعضاء فريق Men on a Mission.
Okay.
تمام.
I came back in 2026...
رجعت في 2026..
after visiting the show in 2025.
بعد زيارة المعرض في عام 2025.
I began the year on a happy note...
لقد بدأت العام بسعادة..
thanks to Men on a Mission.
بفضل الرجال في مهمة.
It'll be hard to surpass this episode in 2026.
سيكون من الصعب تجاوز هذه الحلقة في عام 2026.
It's only the beginning of 2026.
إنها بداية عام 2026 فقط.
- Come on. - Bong Sun.
- تعال. - بونج صن.
I saw the Men on a Mission members for the first time in a while.
رأيت أعضاء "الرجال في مهمة" لأول مرة منذ فترة.
It was hard for me to work with the juniors...
كان من الصعب علي العمل مع الشباب..
of different generations.
من أجيال مختلفة.
I had fun at a nice place with my young juniors...
لقد استمتعت في مكان جميل مع صغاري الصغار.
with enthusiasm.
بحماس.
- Thank you. - All right.
- شكرًا لك. - حسنًا.
We had fun.
لقد استمتعنا.
- Good luck. - Let's meet again.
- حظ سعيد. - دعونا نتقابل مرة أخرى.
(The top 7 contestants of "Sing Again 4" are here!)
(أفضل 7 متسابقين في "Sing Again 4" موجودون هنا!)
(Let's go!)
(دعنا نذهب!)
(Top 7 contestants of "Sing Again 4")
(أفضل 7 متسابقين في برنامج "Sing Again 4")
(Lee Oh Ouk, Dorado, Kim Jae Min, slowly, sEODo, KYURI, Kim Ye Chan)
(لي أوه أوك، دورادو، كيم جاي مين، ببطء، سيودو، كيوري، كيم يي تشان)
(It's the hottest.)
(إنها الأكثر سخونة.)
(The winner of "Sing Again 4," Lee Oh Ouk)
(الفائز ببرنامج Sing Again 4، لي أوه أوك)
(The man who is a famous singer now,)
(الرجل الذي هو مغني مشهور الآن،)
(Oh Ouk sings an emotional rock song.)
(أوه أوك تغني أغنية روك عاطفية.)
(I wanted 300,000 dollars too.)
(أردت 300 ألف دولار أيضًا).
(Dorado wanted the prize money too.)
(أراد دورادو الجائزة المالية أيضًا.)
(With soul,)
(بالروح)
(she sings Ho Dong's favorite song.)
(تغني أغنية هو دونغ المفضلة.)
(3rd place, Jae Min's nickname, Bruno Mars)
(المركز الثالث، لقب جاي مين، برونو مارس)
(He gives the legendary performance again!)
(يقدم الأداء الأسطوري مرة أخرى!)
(Jae Minno Mars has come to the Brother School.)
(جاء جاي مينو مارس إلى مدرسة الأخوة.)
(Bruno Nice rivals him.)
(برونو نيس ينافسه).
(Is 6th place, KYURI, Yang Hee Eun's 1st daughter?)
(هل المركز السادس، كيوري، الابنة الأولى ليانغ هي أون؟)
(I have a real mom.)
(لدي أم حقيقية.)
(Her name is Park Hyun Sook.)
(اسمها بارك هيون سوك.)
("U-Go-Girl," KYURI's song for the two moms)
("U-Go-Girl،" أغنية كيوري للأمتين)
(7th place, Ye Chan was the queen of part-timing.)
(المركز السابع، يي تشان كانت ملكة العمل بدوام جزئي.)
(Her popularity was explosive!)
(كانت شعبيتها متفجرة!)
(Even her singing skills are explosive.)
(حتى مهاراتها الغنائية متفجرة.)
(- Jang Hoon, what's your clan? - Dalseong!)
(- جانغ هون، ما هي عشيرتك؟ - دالسيونغ!)
(slowly's real name, Seo Hee and sEODo)
(الاسم الحقيقي لـ ببطء، Seo Hee وsEODo)
(Team Dalseong, let's go!)
(فريق دالسيونغ، لنذهب!)
(New Year's rock festival begins in the classroom.)
(يبدأ مهرجان موسيقى الروك للعام الجديد في الفصل الدراسي.)
(The lineup of the performances will give you chills!)
(تشكيلة العروض ستمنحك قشعريرة!)
(Music time with the top 7 contestants!)
(وقت الموسيقى مع أفضل 7 متسابقين!)
(This powerful vocalist is bad at rapping.)
(هذا المنشد القوي سيء في موسيقى الراب.)
(The biggest challenge in the musical career)
(التحدي الأكبر في مهنة الموسيقى)
(The crying rap of sadness)
( راب الحزن البكاء )
(Even a famous singer is no exception.)
(حتى المغني الشهير ليس استثناءً).
(Kim Hwan, Music teacher)
(كيم هوان، مدرس الموسيقى)
(Bulging veins)
(انتفاخ الأوردة)
(Brother School will be back with famous singers.)
(سيعود Brother School مع مطربين مشهورين.)
(Don't miss Men on a Mission on Saturday at 9pm.)
(لا تفوت الرجال في مهمة يوم السبت الساعة 9 مساءً.)